My disciple, Hinatsuru Ai, and I, Kuzuryu
Yaichi: our day starts with a checkmate shogi.
Monthly Checkmate Shogi Paradise
Ready...
Go!
Problem 1
Solved it! Checkmate from 3-1
Bishop to 2-5 Gold in 15 moves.
Next!
Problem 2
Checkmate from 5-6 Gold to
2-2 Dragon in 19 moves!
Darn it! Next!
Whoa, what the heck is this?!
I know! Capture Silver with 3-8 Silver,
play Gold from behind King,
move Bishop across 9 columns and guard
that from the perpendicular angle,
take the Gold with 2-8
King, then 3-8 Horse...
That's a drop pawn mate!
What?
It's not 3-8 Horse, but rather from 4-9 Horse
to 2-8 Horse and checkmate in 23 moves!
Damn it! I see, it's a drop pawn mate...
Drop pawn mate.
It's a foul move where you
checkmate with your pawn.
It feels great to evade a drop pawn mate.
Ai is really amazing during the end game.
Ai, how was practice today?
Oh! I won all my matches!
Great, keep up the good work!
Yes!
The Ryuo's Work
Is Never Done!
Shogi Association
That day, I was summoned by
the Kansai Shogi Association.
Kansai Shogi Association
Directory
5F
Edo Castle Keep Shogi Room
4F
Multi-purpose Rooms         Shogi Rooms
5F
Edo Castle Keep Shogi Room
4F
Multi-purpose Rooms         Shogi Rooms
3F
Office          Private Studio
Accommodation Rooms
4F
Multi-purpose Rooms         Shogi Rooms
3F
Office          Private Studio
Accommodation Rooms
2F
Shogi Club         Youth training group
3F
Office          Private Studio
Accommodation Rooms
2F
Shogi Club         Youth training group
1F
Café         Restaurant         Shop
Long time no see, Ryuo.
Game 4: The other Ai
Yes!
Same here, nice to see you again.
This person is the president of the
Shogi League, Tsukimitsu Seiichi, 9-dan.
He has taken the Meijin title 5 times
and has become an Eternal Meijin.
However, what's unfortunate is that he has
lost his eyesight to an illness in his 20s.
Nevertheless, he's still
one of the top players.
He's a living legend.
So... what can I do for you today?
I'd like you to take on a disciple.
What?
She's a granddaughter of a
business family that has
supported the shogi world for many years.
She's nine years old, in 4th grade.
W-Wait a second!
Why... Why is it me?!
Grade schoolers... don't you like them?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about!
I-I don't particularly like them!
I'm joking. It was a request.
What?
Please don't say things like that with such a
straight face. It's terrible for my heart.
The girl apparently said,
"If it's not someone above class A or a
title holder, I won't be anyone's disciple!"
Such a pompous request...
Do you mind meeting her just once, at least?
Think of it as saving face for me.
Thank you for coming!
I'm Yashajin Kouten, the head of this house.
N-Nice to meet you...
I've heard the name Yashajin somewhere...
My son is an amateur shogi player.
Perhaps you've seen his name somewhere.
This is my granddaughter, Ai.
Ai?
I will never call you "master".
You're simply a professional
teaching me classes.
There's no way I could stand calling someone
who took the title with luck a master.
Hey, Ai...
It's all right for me to be strict with her?
Please do so...
Then let's play.
D-Don't joke with me!
You think you can win while giving
me this much of a handicap?!
Stop yapping and come at me.
I'll destroy you!
How is it? It's getting fun isn't it?
N-Not yet!
Unlike her twisted personality,
she plays very honestly.
She must've been blessed with good
instructors who taught her all the basics.
However, she relies on
those basics too much.
She doesn't have the power to
push back when things go south.
She's the complete opposite from
Ai who shines in the end game.
I... I...
"I admit defeat"?
I'm not done yet!
I can still fight!
Her formation has gotten stronger!
She used my attacks to reform her defense!
She's even looking for a chance to counter!
This ability...
Receiving shogi...
When at disadvantage, she
shows amazing abilities.
A player with the special ability to
take advantage of opponents' attacks.
However, one must possess a
strong will that won't bend
no matter how terrible the situation is.
This girl... is strong!
You have guts, but you still
have a long way to go.
Shut up!
I hate you!
Hey, Ai!
Grandpa, you idiot!
I'm sorry. I may have gone too far.
No... that was necessary.
She's a poor girl.
Ever since both of her
parents died in an accident,
she's faced the shogi board alone
and won't let anyone get close to her.
Alone?
Yes. That's why when she
first asked for lessons,
I wanted a professional player
to guide my granddaughter.
Why shogi?
When she was with her parents,
there was always shogi.
To her, the happiest memories
she has involve shogi.
Kuzuryu-sensei, please guide her.
Please!!
But that shogi... those moves...
I've seen them somewhere.
I'm back.
Keika-san, thanks for watching... What?!
Idiot aunt!
Wait... what is this?
Um... girls' night?
No way girls' night is something like this!
And sis, weren't you supposed to
be in a title match in Shizuoka?
Against Tsukiyomizaka-san.
This...
[Women's Open Match]
Sora Ginko wipes out challenger!
Only uses 2 minutes of her allocated time.
Challenger, Tsukiyomizaka Ryo, admits
defeat before lunch break.
History's shortest match.
Snow White of Naniwa, too strong.
With this, Gin-sama's record against
female players is 48 wins 0 losses.
50 wins is almost within reach.
My angel got destroyed.
Ah...
Tsukiyomizaka-san's strategic play
was considered the best from the
first move as of two weeks ago.
But last week, this move was...
Yeah. Kansai's Promotional League said
"Nevermind, this works better if you go second."
I guess she didn't know about it.
That's just a terrible way to lose.
Tsukiyomizaka-san must be
going wild right now...
So the match ended so abruptly
and she's unsatisfied.
Shizuoka -> Hamamatsu -> Nagoya -> Gifu
Hashima -> Maibara -> Kyoto -> Shin Osaka
She wanted to let the pent up
frustration out by playing with me.
But I wasn't here, so she used
Ai as a punching bag...
Ginko-chan?!
Auntie?!
It must've been a shock to Ai-chan.
She still lost with a 4-piece handicap.
I'm going home.
Oh, Sis.
Yaichi.
Yes?
That thing's getting weaker.
Maybe winning at the workshop
made her relax too much.
This is when I decided to
teach Yashajin Ai's lessons.
I realized there are things I cannot give Ai.
And that's... a rival...
What do you plan on doing
at a place like this?
This neighborhood is called the "New World",
and in Osaka, it's the most
deep and angular place.
And it's also where shogi
prospered the most in Osaka.
A lot still remains here.
How is it? Can you play?
Hmph! They're too low level.
But since we came all the way here,
I'll at least play before I go home.
So predictable.
Then, let's go!
Cover charge
1h 300 yen, 2h 600 yen, 3h 800 yen, 4h 1000 yen
All day 1000 yen
Student discount 600 yen
New players welcome!
One child and two adults.
Here you go.
What do we do?
Go play with people who who
seem bored in the back.
Akira-san and I will be here watching.
Match with no handicap?
Take a seat.
The Ryuo's Work
Is Never Done!
Hey, Sensei.
Is that an old man? Or an old woman?
Seems like half and half.
Whoopies.
What?
What? Why is she surprised?
That's a Bishop Head Pawn.
It's a sideways rook ambush move.
At first, it often looks like a mistake.
Oh man, I did something dumb.
I guess I'll just have
to exchange the bishop.
I heard that she learned shogi through books
and the internet, after
her parents passed away.
Yes. Master and us guardians
don't know anything about shogi.
It's a wonder she got
this strong by herself.
But without experiencing real matches,
one cannot become stronger.
This is where it gets interesting.
W-Why? What happened?!
What? What did that person do?
It's a trap to deceive the opponent.
Is that against the rules?
If so, I'll go hunt down that panther...
No, no. It's not against the rules.
It's more like pretending to show your
opponent an opening, just to set up a trap.
It's a sly strategy.
I lost...
Five consecutive losses.
Well, that's normal for the first time.
You have an aptitude for shogi.
There's no more basics for me to teach you.
However, you can't learn tricks
during matches without an opponent.
Make sure you learn that here.
If you do, then no one will be
able to win against you.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Master!
Welcome back!
Kuzuryu-sensei! Thank you for
letting us use your place.
Oh right, today was a JS training group day.
Master!
Char has a request for you, Master.
Hm, what is it, Char-chan?
Can you make Char your disciple?
What?
Char-chan!
What are you saying!
Char-chan, you want to be my disciple?
Yes!
B-But doesn't Char-chan go to a class with
the same instructor as you, Ayano-chan?
Yes. But our master is the type to
leave kids to do whatever they want.
I-Is that right...
Even with Ai's talent and determination,
it's the reality that my
ability alone isn't enough.
I'm sorry. I can't make
Char-chan my disciple.
Char can't be your disciple?
Why? Why not?
Why is Ai okay, but not Char?
Char-chan...
If I just reject her, I might
leave a big scar in her heart...
That's one thing I must avoid!
Think, think harder, Kuzuryu Yaichi!
As a professional player, as a Ryuo,
a move that turns everything around...
Oh, right! There's this move!
I can't make you my disciple,
but you can be my bride!
Bride?
Yes, my bride.
Master's bride?
That's right.
Wow! Char likes being a
bride more than a disciple!
Right? Right?
A-Ai-chan...
Idiot master! You lolicon! Lolicon King!
Uh oh. Did I make it worse?
What are you saying? Making
a grade schooler your wife?
You pervert!
Calm down, Ai-chan!
That's like spitting while looking up!
Seems like Ai doesn't like the idea
of me taking on a new disciple.
I guess I'll keep quiet about the fact that
I'm giving lessons to someone else, for now.
She's reading the opponent's expression
and using that to make judgments.
She's the completely opposite of
Ai who only focuses on the board.
How's this?
Damn. I guess that's that.
Little girl, you're strong.
Thank you, I know.
How is it, that strength?
Her talent is undeniable.
But there's a lot of mental
training she needs to go through,
until no situation will shake her...
Well then, can someone play with me?
I-I'll be your opponent!
Why is it... Why is it
leopard print in pink?!
Perhaps it's in Osaka people's blood
to be flashier and flashier...
I'm too curious about that person's
gender. I can't focus on the shogi.
Well, this is training too!
You're pretty good, little girl.
To take this much attack from me,
who was called New World's Female Leopard!
I-It was a she!
Ai was so shaken by the
news, she self-destructed.
Like this, I go to shogi dojo on the
weekends and spend time with Ai otherwise.
Or so I thought that was
going to be the routine...
Recently, I've been able to
figure out people's habits.
Oh?
When Mio-chan is shaken, she says makes
sounds like "fuwaa" or like "yaaa."
Uwaaa... Yaa...
Yeah.
When Ayano-chan plans a surprise attack
during early stages of the match,
she takes off her glasses and makes
sure to not look at her opponent.
Ah, now that you've said it...
When master is hiding something, you
rub your hands against your pants.
What?
Master, what are you hiding from me?
I'm h-hiding?
Something from me, right?
No, no, no! Why would I do
that?! What is there to hide?!
Where are you working on Saturdays recently?
Um, the President asked me to be
this old man's coach in Kobe...
Staaaaare.
Oh no! I was rubbing my hands!
It must be a woman!
Mihane-chan thinks so too?
In dramas and mangas, it's always the
case that they have another woman.
You can't, Ai-chan!
What should I do?
If I can make do something for
Ai-chan for a change of pace...
By change of pace... you mean a shogi dojo?
Yeah! Let's try changing things up!
I've always wanted to
go to the dojo in Umeda!
I'm excited!
Excite!
This is so dumb.
If I'm playing against you,
we didn't have to come here.
People will show up eventually.
Also, don't call me "you". Call me "sensei".
I heard from grandfather...
that you also have another disciple.
Yeah. She's also the same age
as you. Are you curious?
N-Not really! It doesn't matter!
I really don't care, but...
So? Is she strong?
She's strong.
But you're probably better, since you know
how to navigate through the
early stages of the match.
So you learned shogi from your parents?
That's right.
Your shogi... I feel like I've seen it before.
It also feels like I know it very well.
Were your parents perhaps skilled players?
Or their match records were
in shogi magazines and...
Oh, I-I'm sorry!
You don't have to tell me anything,
if you don't want to! It's my fault.
That's not really the case...
My mother wasn't that strong, but
father was an amateur master.
I-I see.
He really was strong.
I'm sorry.
Hey...
Can you teach me how to play?
What? I'm teaching you right now.
Not that. I'm asking how to make beautiful
sounds when you play a move, idiot.
I said to call me "sensei"!
Fine, fine, idiot-sensei.
Hold it like this, then do this.
Like this?
So you hold it like this,
and then like this.
You're unexpectedly clumsy.
Don't call me "you."
Then what do I call you?
Just call me Ai...
Yay! It's pretty much empty!
Whoa!
Excuse me.
H-Hello...
Wait, what happened?
What? Isn't that...