Ryuo
Ryuo. That is the highest
title in the shogi world.
Currently, I am trying to take
the title of history's
youngest shogi player to
become Ryuo, as a 16-year-old.
One more move. Just one more
move and I'll become Ryuo.
The grand prize of 42 million yen, the
prestige, the promotion to 8th dan...
And my name will go down in history.
But the title of Ryuo comes
with a lot of pressure.
All professional players are
fighting for this title...
Proof that you're the
strongest: the title of Ryuo.
The pressure is so insane, I can't
even hold my piece properly.
If I don't go back soon,
I'll run out of time...
Um...
Here's some water.
Thank you.
And then... I became a Ryuo.
[Shitty Ryuo]Thread to fold cranes to wish
for Kuzuryu Yaichi's downfall 108 [history's weakest]
It's getting longer...
How about this site?
Shogi
Sora Ginko
Kugui Machi
Tsukiyomizaka Ryo
Shakando Rina
Sainokami Ika
Everyone's doing so well...
Kannabe Ayumu
History's strongest Meijin
God-like magic!!
I'm Kuzuryu Yaichi, 16-years-old.
I became a professional shogi
player in middle school.
Which means that I became a pro and didn't
continue onto high school and
I'm working hard in the shogi world.
It's good that I took the title of the Ryuo
with all the momentum and good luck, but...
It's been three months since then.
I am currently in the middle of a slump.
I went to the research group at the
shogi assembly hall again today,
but I can't seem to find a path to recovery.
I need to get myself together.
I need to become worthy of a Ryuo,
like that Meijin who's regarded
as history's strongest player.
I'm back!
As if... no one's home, anyway.
What?!
Welcome home, Master!
Um...
Game 1: A Disciple Storms In
Yes!
Hey... Why are you in my room?
Yes! Um, K-Kuzur-r-ryu Ya—
She bit her tongue!
It hurts...
A-Are you okay? That sounded painful.
You are K-K-Kuzu...-sensei right?!
She gave up!
As we promised, I came to be your disciple!
Disciple?
Yes!
You?
Promise? When did we make that?
Um... last year's Ryuo match...
Oh! That was you?
Yes! I am Hinatsuru Ai!
My father owns the inn that
was the Ryuo match venue.
Hinatsuru Ai...
Do you not remember me?
I'm sorry... I don't remember at all.
So I told you that I'd make you my disciple?
Oh, no... Um, not exactly.
You said, "If I become Ryuo,
I'll do anything you ask."
The promise was even worse than I thought!
And you want to be my disciple?
Yes!
I understand. I'll keep my promise.
Really?!
However, I'll have to
test your skills first.
How old are you?
I'm nine. I'm in third grade!
From what she told me, she was in my room
because she thought people would find
it suspicious if she stood outside.
She's thoughtful.
I'm amazed her parents gave her
permission, but that doesn't matter.
I don't plan on making her my
disciple in the first place.
My
glory
starts
tomorrow.
I'm still only 16, so I don't have
time to take care of other people.
I'll just fulfill my promise some other way,
and I'll send her back after one match.
Let's have a good match.
Yes, let's have a good match!
Please go first.
Yes.
My
glory
starts
tomorrow.
This is...
This position is a Double Wing Attack.
It's the strategy I like to use often.
I used it when I took the title of Ryuo.
I've been underestimated.
It'd be mean to let this continue
too long. I'll end it quickly.
This attack is a bit risky, but it's the end.
Here, then here.
Then there, and here.
And then this, then that...
Then this, then that...
Okay!
She went on the offense instead of defending!
Did she notice that my attack was forced?
A move that turns the table around.
In few moves, I'll be at a disadvantage.
If I'm not careful, it'll be checkmate.
How far ahead is she reading?!
She's seriously trying to defeat me.
At that moment, I got excited.
The excitement of being able to
fight against a strong player.
Come at me.
I admit defeat.
I haven't had a stimulating experience
like this since the Ryuo match...
Your shogi is really interesting.
Every move was so intense.
Thank you very much.
No, I need to thank you.
I haven't had fun like this in a while.
Do you use the Double Wing Attack often?
I wouldn't say often...
Um, it's the only thing I know.
What?!
I-I started playing shogi after I saw
how amazing your Ryuo match was!
I really want to be like you, so
I've been copying you, sensei!
Wait a second! So wait. You only
started playing shogi three months ago?
Oh, yes.
My grandpa loves shogi,
so I read the books he had at home.
I borrowed my friend's tablet at school
and played on shogi apps.
I can't believe it!
Despite being in a slump, I'm a Ryuo.
I hold the highest title.
To think, a girl who just started three months
ago managed to corner me in a match.
Um, Sensei.
Yeah?
M-My test... to become your disciple...
Oh, right.
I didn't really understand what happened,
so let's play another match.
Yes!
Then we continued playing
late into the night.
We were so absorbed
that we forgot to eat.
You made all this?
Yes! I'm sorry that it's a simple meal.
It tastes really good! You're amazing.
You solved them all? The 100 shogi problems?
Yes. My grandpa had this book in his library.
100 Shogi Problems
By all, do you mean... um... this one!
You solved this, too?
Yes. 4-6 Ryu, 5-4 Gyoku, 5-5 Ryu,
6-3 Gyoku, 5-3 Ryu, 7-4 Gyoku,
7-3 Ryu, 8-5 Gyoku...
You remember all of the moves?!
Yes. I can't look at the book
in class or while doing chores,
so I had to think in my head,
even though it was difficult.
611-move Tsumeshogi... Even professionals
have a hard time solving it.
And for her to solve it in her head...
This girl is insane.
Master, do you want seconds?
Talent. She definitely has the talent.
But for me to make her my disciple...
First of all, who knows
what Sis would do to me
if I took a girl in grade
school as my disciple.
Yes! Who is it?
Me.
What?
It's me.
What's up, Sis? What can I do for you?!
VS. We were supposed to have a
one-on-one match today, remember?
You're absolutely right!
Hurry up and open the
door. It's hot outside.
No, um... I'm a little busy right now!
Master, can you pass me the towel?
Hey, don't!
Did I just hear a girl's voice?
N-N-N-No, you didn't! No such thing!
Master, is there someone outside?
No! There's no one outside!
There's no one! There's really no one!
Yaichi! Open the door!
Master... you have a... female guest?
Whoa, she's scary!
Who is it?
Can you look me in
the eye and talk to me?
No way! You're butt naked right now!
Naked? There's a naked
girl in there right now?!
Wait...
Look at me!
This is checkmate.
The Ryuo's Work
Is Never Done!
So?
I've been telling you!
This is an unfortunate accident!
And?
This girl suddenly came here!
Wakura Hot Springs
On her own! From Ishikawa! By herself!
Osaka
And?
And? Are you listening to me?
Yaichi, bring over that
board and flip it over.
What?
Hurry up!
Yes, ma'am.
Like this?
This cavity is called the "Pool of Blood."
When a player gets executed for
misconduct during the match,
this keeps their blood
from getting on the floor.
Oh.
So don't worry. You can die right here.
Th-That's a joke... right?
There's a knife in the kitchen, right?
Please tell me you're joking!
Please stop!
What is this anteater-looking creature?
Who are you calling an anteater?!
You don't know me?
Even though you play shogi.
I don't know you!
This person here is Sora Ginko, a female
shogi player who has two titles.
I learned shogi with Sis, meaning
she's pretty much my sibling!
Sis?
My glory starts tomorrow.
We are both disciplines
of Kiyotaki Kosuke, 9th dan.
She's 14, so she's younger than me,
but she became his disciple first.
So that's why she's my senior disciple.
She's also an idol in the shogi industry,
known as "The Snow White of of Naniwa,"
Shogi World
and she holds the titles of the
Queen and the Empress' Seat...
Queen...
Yeah. The Queen, so you need to respect her.
I understand!
You're a SM person!
What's so funny?
I-I'm sorry— wai— stop!
Ow! Stop hitting me!
I knew it! There's no mistake.
You're mistaken, you idiot!
Please, just stop hitting Master!
Whatever, brat.
Indomitable
Could you just shut your mouth?
Stupid.
Huh? Did you say something, brat?
I'm not a brat! I have a proper
name, and it's Hinatsuru Ai!
Jeez.
We're going.
Where to?
Our master's house.
My glory starts tomorrow.
I see. So this is Ai-chan.
Actually, I received a call
from the Shogi Association
about a girl from the Hinatsuru
Inn who ran away home.
Ran away?
Her parents know that ever
since your Ryuo match,
Ai-chan has been hooked on shogi.
So they thought, maybe...
Ai-chan, why didn't you tell your parents?
Even if I did, they'd object...
But there's a lot of good teachers
in Ishikawa Prefecture, too.
No! I want to be Kuzuryu-sensei's disciple!
No one else will do!
Why?
Ow, ow, ow!
Why this?
Because he was cool!
You're weird.
Hey, Ginko. You...
During the Ryuo match, for the
first time, I saw shogi... A shogi player...
A challenger who was so serious and
fought until he was in pieces...
The way he was sitting, moving his pieces,
and even struggling on the floor...
Everything about it was cool!
That's why I wanted to play shogi!
I wanted to be like Master...
It's the first time I thought, "I want to be
like this person!" I couldn't help myself!
Both of you were like this at first, too.
That's right. Both Ginko and I just really
wanted to learn shogi, so we came to Master.
Master was really cool when he was playing.
He gripped his hand tight, so he
wouldn't make any unnecessary moves.
I even admired the wrinkles on his knees...
Yaichi, you should make
Ai-chan your disciple.
What?!
Master!
I'll contact her parents.
But, wait...
I understand. I'll submit her application to a
training group entrance exam as my disciple.
Master!
But only over spring break.
I guess it's disciple (temp) for now.
Disciple (Temp)
I finally have a grand-disciple.
Keika! We're celebrating tonight!
Make us some sekihan!
We're having okonomiyaki for dinner.
I see, okonomiyaki...
You must be Ai-chan.
I'm Kiyotaki Keika.
I'm this old man's daughter.
Yes! Nice to meet you. I'm Hinatsuru Ai!
I'm also learning, so I can become a
professional female player.
Let's work hard together.
Yes!
But with this, Ginko-chan
and I are aunties now.
Aunties?
The relationship within the
clan is the same as a family.
Master and disciple are the same as parent
and child, and disciples are like siblings.
Sis and Keiko-san are now your aunts.
Auntie?
Who are you calling "auntie"?!
What is it, Auntie?
Is this ever going to get better?
Shogi Association
First, we're going to join the
shogi training group that's held here.
Kansai Shogi Association
Then, if you do well in the ranks, you
can become a professional player.
Yes! In order for me to become like Master,
I need to become a professional player first!
Keychains
Wow! They're selling fans here!
Yeah. They print the signatures or favorite
quotes of famous players on them.
Is Master going to play in this room?
Today is a match for the imperial title.
It'll be broadcast on the internet as well.
Upper Tier Room
Imperial Match
Kuzuryu Yaichi    Kannabe Ayumu
What kind of person is your opponent?
Kannabe Ayumu, 6th dan.
He's from my study group—
That's just a disguise!
My true name is something else!
Knight
A shogi player who's actually a knight!
Shogi Player
The Silver Chevalier! God Cauldron, Ayumu.
Master! He's wearing a cape!
Wearing a cape to an
official shogi match...
Little girl! You must be something, if you've noticed how wonderful my cape is.
I don't mind letting you join
us, the Legion of Gate East!
Gate East?
You mean the shogi players
from the Kanto region.
Kansai        Shogi Association
Shogi Association        Kanto
The shogi league is split between
the Kanto and Kansai regions.
Little girl! If you're training as well,
I shall let you receive the
blessings of the eastern wind!
I-I am the disciple of Ryuo Kuzuryu!
I will not give in to the likes of you!
The life of the Dragon King
will come to an end today!
What are you?!
They're perfectly synced.
Hope you enjoy your short-lived
relationship with your master.
Hey, Ayumu.
I'm going to take her to the
dojo, so I'll see you later...
Fine. I'll be waiting!
Autograph!
Can you sign this?
Please!
Let's play together!
There're too many people. I can't get close!
Of course! He's history's youngest Ryuo!
Ryuo?
Yeah! Someone really, really strong!
Master! You're really popular!
I'm going to the match now, but
will you be okay by yourself?
Yes.
All right. Let's do our best, okay?
Yes! Best of luck, Master!
Shogi players are very unique.
Personality, age, birthplace...
They all vary.
But the one similarity is that none
of us can live without shogi.
I see that you didn't run away, Dragon King!
Of course I didn't. It's a match.
And now, a new talent is about
to enter the shogi world.
The story of Ryuo Kuzuryu Yaichi
and his disciple, Hinatsuru Ai,
begins like this.
Shogi Association
Let's have a good match!
The Ryuo's Work
Is Never Done!