[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-08-21 13:10:04
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: CN,楷体,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134

Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: JP,楷体,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,20,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.03,0:01:39.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}台本/时间 玩转づYoung 校对 逆時京介 翻译 x恶魔猎手　后期 Master·R \N 动漫先锋字幕组 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.03,0:01:39.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「台本役QQ287465050　台本について何かご意見がありましたら \N　遠慮なくご叱正ください　喜んで伺います」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.74,0:01:47.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,で　何なんだこれは
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.26,0:01:50.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,団子に決まっているだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.96,0:01:52.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなに買ったのかよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.70,0:01:54.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を言っている　お前が買うのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.85,0:01:55.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は？何で俺が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.99,0:01:58.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先日の失敗のお詫びに決まっている
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.27,0:01:58.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.92,0:02:00.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意味もなく砦に潜入させるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.89,0:02:04.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,折角見つけた勇者の遺物を使えこなせず置いてくるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.98,0:02:07.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これから毎日団子を買って貰うからな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.69,0:02:10.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置いてきたのはお前も一緒じゃねえか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.22,0:02:13.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仕方ねえだろう　何百年も眠ってた勇者の遺物を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.00,0:02:16.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう簡単に使えこなせるかっての！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.50,0:02:19.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それに　だからって何で俺が団子を…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.28,0:02:24.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい　買います　買わせて頂きます
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.53,0:02:25.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　よろしい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.58,0:02:26.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毎度あり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.84,0:02:28.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で俺がこんな目に
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.66,0:02:31.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クソ！これも全部シオンの所為だ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.59,0:02:34.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アイツが面倒くせえことばっか押しつけんから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.31,0:02:37.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ～今頃城でいいもん食って
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.53,0:02:40.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暢気に昼寝でもしてんだろうな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:55.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下　この度のこと　どのように責任を取るおつもりですか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.82,0:02:58.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのような物言い 陛下に対し失礼であるぞ！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.12,0:03:01.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいえ　言わせて頂きます
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.53,0:03:02.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下は甘いのです
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.93,0:03:06.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,属国のエスタブールの王や貴族に　我が国での地位を与え
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.87,0:03:08.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,領民の生活の保障まで
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:10.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのような態度が反乱を…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.63,0:03:11.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黙りなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.95,0:03:16.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふん　親玉のご登場か
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.65,0:03:18.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,申し訳ございません　陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.06,0:03:21.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし彼も国を思ってのこと
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.27,0:03:22.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かっている　気にするな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.81,0:03:27.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,して　この度の反乱　如何なさるおつもりでしょうか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.45,0:03:31.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迅速の対応をして頂けると期待しておりますが
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.27,0:03:36.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迅速の対応って 知らせが届いてからまだ二日ですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.19,0:03:39.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反乱軍の本拠地も　首謀者も分かっていないのに
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.85,0:03:41.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸糞悪い野郎だ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.42,0:03:43.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,対策はもう練ってある
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.85,0:03:44.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほう？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.80,0:03:47.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反乱の首謀者も調べはついている
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.28,0:03:51.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,エスタブールの嘗ての国王の一人娘　ノア·エン嬢だ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.84,0:03:55.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詳しいことは情報を集めてくれた　ミラン·フロワード大佐に
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.84,0:04:01.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情報によるとエスタブール側の兵の数は約五万
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.20,0:04:02.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五万？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.37,0:04:05.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはもはや反乱ではない　戦争ではないか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.62,0:04:08.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,エスタブールと隣接する領地の方々は
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.52,0:04:10.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戦闘に巻き込まれる恐れがあります
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.13,0:04:14.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫らくの間 この城へ避難して頂きたい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.06,0:04:18.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆様の領地は必ずお守り致します
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.24,0:04:19.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,領地を離れるだと
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.99,0:04:23.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴様ら如きが 我らの領地を踏み荒らすと言うのか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.27,0:04:25.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなこと　断じて許さんぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.30,0:04:28.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か見られて困るものでもおありになるのですか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.89,0:04:30.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そん　そんなものはないが…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.84,0:04:33.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勿論お留まり下さっても結構です
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.79,0:04:36.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,エスタブールの勢力は高々五万
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.28,0:04:38.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐れることはないでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.41,0:04:43.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 これより私が一軍を引き
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.53,0:04:47.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各領地の警護　並びに反乱鎮圧に参ります
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.31,0:04:50.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　今回のことはクラウ·クロム少将に任せる
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.15,0:04:54.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お任せ下さい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.67,0:04:57.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フロワードには情報の収集と伝達を頼む
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.33,0:04:59.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラウを補佐してやってくれ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.82,0:05:01.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな奴のサポートなんが
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.89,0:05:02.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命令だ　クラウ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.47,0:05:04.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フロワードもいいな
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.65,0:05:05.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.98,0:05:12.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下　どう言うことでしょうか
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.28,0:05:14.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この反乱　仕組んだのはお前だろ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.44,0:05:18.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意気の掛かった者に反乱を起こさせ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.84,0:05:21.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,エスタブールの反ローランド勢力を一掃する
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.92,0:05:25.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,序でに　戦争を口実に各領地に兵を送り
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.33,0:05:28.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反国王派の貴族たちの不正も探るか
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.39,0:05:31.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だとしたら　如何なさいますか？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.24,0:05:34.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何もしない　お前はお前の仕事をしろ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.54,0:05:35.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それだけだ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.69,0:05:46.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我が父上は　今だローランドか
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.58,0:05:48.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父上のことがお気になりますか
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方のお父上 我等が王は
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.11,0:05:55.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローランドから呈示された地位と安全とお引き換えに
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.45,0:05:57.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっさりと国をお売りになった
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.06,0:05:59.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かっている
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.60,0:06:02.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが　父が反乱の名士として立った方が
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.90,0:06:04.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民が嬉しかろうと思ってな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.03,0:06:09.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我々貴族　そして民も貴方を押したいと申し上げます
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.31,0:06:12.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等が新たの王　ノア·エン様を
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.69,0:06:15.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう言うことにして置こう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.31,0:06:17.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怖いのですか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.20,0:06:21.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怖いさ　この戦に勝てなかったらどうなる
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.38,0:06:24.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それにローランドはエスタブールの民にもよくしてくれている
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.03,0:06:27.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に戦う必要はあるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.83,0:06:30.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勿論です　由緒あるエスタブールをローランドの手から
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.90,0:06:33.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国などどうでもよい　それより民だ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.77,0:06:36.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これで本当に民が幸せになれるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.50,0:06:38.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,むやみに血を流すだけではないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.41,0:06:43.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は民が幸せに暮らせればそれでよいのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.85,0:06:46.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう教えたのはお前であろう　サラヴェル
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.65,0:06:49.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今はまだ我等の勢力が大きい
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.54,0:06:52.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だからローランドも無茶をしません
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.77,0:06:55.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　今後もそれが続く保証がありません
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.89,0:06:58.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローランドの貴族たちに関する悪い噂も聞きます
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.97,0:07:01.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に民のことを思うなら　今です
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.95,0:07:05.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前がそう言うなら　きっとそうなのだろうな
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.13,0:07:10.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方様のためなら　我等は死をも厭いません
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:16.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰もが笑って暮らせるような　誰もが幸せになれるような
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.11,0:07:18.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんな国が作りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.85,0:07:20.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来るかな　サラヴェル
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.96,0:07:22.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勿論です
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.50,0:07:40.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これより　ローランドとの戦闘を開始します
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.64,0:07:43.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,エスタブールの独立をこの手に取り戻すのです
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.51,0:07:50.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クロム少将より伝令　戦闘開始られました
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.65,0:08:11.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シュッス　敵の数は
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.25,0:08:13.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,およそ八千から九千かと
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.42,0:08:16.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フロワードの情報通りか　気に入らねえな
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.72,0:08:17.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.34,0:08:21.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何でもない　じゃまぁ　最小限の犠牲でここを治めるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.77,0:08:22.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.57,0:08:25.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全軍　進め！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.23,0:08:29.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローランドの犬ども
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.23,0:08:30.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何処から涌いて来やがった
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.79,0:08:33.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この混戦じゃでかい魔法は使えないぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.47,0:08:35.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退け…!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.17,0:08:38.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何処だ　指揮官は何処に居る
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.74,0:08:51.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメエが　この軍の指揮官か！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.09,0:08:53.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴様は
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.88,0:09:01.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメエらエスタブールの指揮官は　俺がぶっ飛ばしたぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.37,0:09:05.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ以上抵抗すれば皆殺しにする
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.32,0:09:08.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血に染まった　紅指のクラウ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.30,0:09:10.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アイツがローランドの紅指のクラウ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.08,0:09:14.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クソ　つまんねえ殺し合いしあがって
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.94,0:09:26.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又敗れただと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.75,0:09:29.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まるで我が軍の動きが全部読まれているようではないか
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.83,0:09:33.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから言ったのだ　無謀なことだと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.21,0:09:34.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今更何を言う
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.43,0:09:39.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紅指のクラウ　ローランドの指揮官は確かクラウ·クロムと言いましたね
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.08,0:09:40.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.61,0:09:45.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞くところによると　こちらの兵を極力殺さず
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.37,0:09:47.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降伏させているそうではないか
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.48,0:09:48.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.43,0:09:50.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それがローランドの戦い方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.81,0:09:54.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英雄王シオン·アスタールの意志ならば　やはりこの戦いは
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:58.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を仰います　それも敵の狙いに違いありません
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.86,0:10:01.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その通りです　エスタブールを取り込んだ後
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.75,0:10:04.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怒りや恨みを買わぬよう　戦いを進めているだけです
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.26,0:10:08.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未だ手はあります　弱気は禁物です　姫様
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.84,0:10:13.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クロム少将の軍　反乱軍の本拠地を包囲いたしました
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.16,0:10:43.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何いう事ですか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.53,0:10:46.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローランドは軍を撤退し　捕虜を解放せよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.01,0:10:49.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それらの望みが聞き届けられない場合は
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.09,0:10:52.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一国ごとにエスタブールの民の首を刎ねる
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.20,0:10:56.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同じ文面の物をローランド軍に送りました
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.94,0:11:00.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローランドの英雄王には民を見殺しにするなどできますまい
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.16,0:11:03.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何と言うこと　アナタは
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.64,0:11:04.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かっております
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.04,0:11:07.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　これは仕方の無いことなのです
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.71,0:11:10.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は貴方を　姫様を守りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.34,0:11:12.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の為に民を人質に取るのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.52,0:11:17.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民のことを思ってです　今我々が負ければどうなります
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.60,0:11:21.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敗戦国の民がどれほど虐げられ　辱めを受けるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.80,0:11:25.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民を人質に取ることは　民を虐げることにはならないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.71,0:11:29.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう止められないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.28,0:11:31.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,止められません
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.29,0:11:40.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか　私は担がれただけの傀儡の王
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.59,0:11:42.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結局　誰も救えないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.25,0:11:47.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひ　姫様　ローランドの兵が
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.07,0:11:51.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我が軍の兵がエスタブールの要塞を攻撃しています
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.44,0:11:52.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だと
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.64,0:12:00.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それが　我が部隊の兵が全て揃っておりまして
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.33,0:12:02.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は？じゃ何処の部隊だ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.40,0:12:04.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下が援軍を送って来られたでしょうか
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.47,0:12:07.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シオンは全て俺に任せると言った
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.93,0:12:09.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなことをするはずがない
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.08,0:12:10.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,では
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.88,0:12:13.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさか　アイツが
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.50,0:12:15.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんな馬鹿な
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.87,0:12:19.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紅指のクラウが人質を無視して攻撃して来るとは
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.78,0:12:24.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうする　民を人質に取ってこのまま破れれば　我らは死刑だぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.85,0:12:27.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいえ　未だ負けると決まった訳では
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.06,0:12:30.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人質を殺しましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.86,0:12:35.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なるほど　ローランドは我らが本気ではないと思っているのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.08,0:12:37.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人質を殺せば
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.22,0:12:38.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お止めなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.67,0:12:39.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.92,0:12:43.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆さんはよくやってくれました　でもここまでです
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.10,0:12:46.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人質を解放しましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.65,0:12:47.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ですが姫様
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.82,0:12:51.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私が手を尽くして見ます　私一人の命で
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.43,0:12:55.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いけません　姫様だけには死なせる訳には
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.54,0:12:58.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私も　私も姫様と一緒に
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.94,0:13:00.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私もだ　姫様
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.36,0:13:03.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆のその言葉だけで十分です
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.78,0:13:04.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姫様
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.32,0:13:07.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方がたは生きてください
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.68,0:13:12.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして　エスタブールの民が少しでも幸せに成れるように
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.28,0:13:14.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その為に　私は
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.64,0:13:17.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは困りましたね
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.04,0:13:21.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆様の国を思う心には痛く感動してしまいました
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.85,0:13:26.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　私としては　ノア·エン皇嗣様のお命だけでは
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.20,0:13:29.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この度の罪を償うには少々足りないかと
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.43,0:13:34.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう　エスタブールと言う国が無くなる悲劇の幕を飾るのは
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.23,0:13:37.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やはり悲劇が相応しいと思いませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.32,0:13:38.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アナタは
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.28,0:13:42.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私はローランド帝国軍大佐　ミラン·フロワードと申します
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.93,0:13:44.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしてここに
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.38,0:13:46.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外の兵たちが全滅したのか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.65,0:13:50.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいえ　いいえ　流石にこの城はそう簡単には落ちませんよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.77,0:13:54.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最も落ちたとしても　城の中にローランドの兵は入れませんけどね
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.19,0:13:56.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何せ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.32,0:14:00.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここで今から悲劇の最終幕が演じられるのですから
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.26,0:14:02.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇を　舞われ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.20,0:14:13.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なに？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.67,0:14:15.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姫様を
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.40,0:14:16.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.24,0:14:17.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　皆を置いては
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.43,0:14:27.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥へ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.15,0:14:35.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆　死んでしまった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.31,0:14:40.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国も　人も　全て無くなってしまった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.77,0:14:43.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいえ　未だ残っていますよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.41,0:14:45.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何が残っていると言うのですか
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.92,0:14:48.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方の命です
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.78,0:14:52.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追い詰められたエスタブールは暴走し
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.81,0:14:55.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あろうことか　人質を殺し始める
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.43,0:14:56.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,サラヴェル？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.61,0:15:00.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その暴走の指揮を取るのが　姫様　貴方です
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.86,0:15:02.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんな　では
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.98,0:15:06.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして　その暴走した姫君を殺し
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.31,0:15:10.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この戦いを終わらせた　エスタブールの貴族　サラヴェル·セールは
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.39,0:15:13.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国を救った英雄として　ローランドに迎えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.71,0:15:19.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我が軍の動きが筒抜けだったのも　人質を取ろうと言い出したのも
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.93,0:15:21.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全てはアナタの
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:24.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信じていたのに
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.69,0:15:28.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初は貴方を妻に迎え　この国を乗っ取るつもりでしたがね
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.93,0:15:35.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は　誰もが笑って暮らせる世界を創りたかっただけ　なのに
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.42,0:15:39.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綺麗言では世界は動かないのですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.82,0:15:41.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも　それでも…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.63,0:15:45.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可愛いな姫様は
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.95,0:15:47.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　これでお仕舞いです
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.58,0:16:06.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心して下さい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.24,0:16:12.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのような男が英雄に成れるほど　ローランドは英雄に困っておりません
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.19,0:16:14.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英雄だと
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.50,0:16:18.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これがローランドの英雄王　シオン·アスタールのすることか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.74,0:16:21.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我が王はこのような事は好みません
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.64,0:16:24.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今回のことは全て私の独断です
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.43,0:16:29.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,では　サラヴェルと結託し　我らを反乱に導いったのも
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.48,0:16:30.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええ　私です
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.87,0:16:36.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それを見抜かれ　私ではなくクロム少将に反乱鎮圧を任された
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.94,0:16:38.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我が王はそういう大方です
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.69,0:16:42.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　サラヴェルさんの仰る通り
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.65,0:16:45.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綺麗言では世界が動かないのも事実
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.16,0:16:49.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ノア·エン皇嗣は人質を殺したあげく　自決
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.73,0:16:52.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それが筋書きです
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.64,0:16:55.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アスタール王はそれを許すのか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.58,0:16:57.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バレなければ一番なのですが
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:17:02.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お許しになるではないでしょうか　それが王の器量とも…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.74,0:17:11.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　嬢ちゃん　怪我はねえか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.44,0:17:15.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメエが反乱の首謀者とはな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.65,0:17:17.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参りましたね　クロム少将
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.12,0:17:19.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさかこんなに早く来るとは
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.08,0:17:21.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,質問に答えろ！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.46,0:17:25.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クロム少将　では　この男が紅指クラウ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.34,0:17:27.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,返答次第じゃ…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.55,0:17:29.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私を殺す　ですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.96,0:17:32.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱりお前は　シオンには必要ねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.92,0:17:36.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方には　あの方の背負う物が見えていない
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.95,0:17:39.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方の方こそ　あの方に使える資格はない
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.92,0:17:42.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺がシオンの側に居るのに　資格なんかいられんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.13,0:17:48.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの方が歩む道の為にも　私はノア·エン様と人質を殺す
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.48,0:17:51.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もし貴方が邪魔をすると言うのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.69,0:17:53.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメエにできると思ってんのか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.23,0:17:55.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容易いこと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.02,0:17:59.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダメ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.06,0:18:04.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの力は　
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.63,0:18:11.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,エスタブールの民の為にも　今はこの男を失う訳には
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.63,0:18:13.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇を
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.52,0:18:14.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いけない
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.23,0:18:16.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フロワード
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.29,0:18:21.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フロワード大佐　エスタブールを完全に支配するのに
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.10,0:18:26.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人質を殺さねんばならないなら　私が説得します
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.52,0:18:30.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民や兵に　ローランドに従うように私が…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.30,0:18:32.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前　何を
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.98,0:18:36.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人質を殺してエスタブールの評判を落とすより
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.65,0:18:39.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのほうがよほど効果があると思いますが
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.44,0:18:44.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに　貴方はエスタブールの民に人気がありますからね
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.03,0:18:49.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　国を売った裏切り者と罵る者も出て来るかもしれませんよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.05,0:18:53.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,構いません　貴方が望むなら
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.27,0:18:55.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その後で私を殺して下さっても結構
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.79,0:18:59.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ですから　皆を殺すことだけは
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.40,0:19:01.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良いでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.37,0:19:07.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戦は終わりました　兵を引いてください　クロム少将
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.67,0:19:09.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待ちやがれ！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.01,0:19:14.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,って　おい　お前大丈夫か
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.84,0:19:17.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方と　貴方の王を信じます
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.71,0:19:19.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.73,0:19:27.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クロム少将　私は腰が抜けてしまいました
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.55,0:19:29.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立たせて貰えないだろうか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.31,0:19:31.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.00,0:19:36.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すまない
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.93,0:19:45.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方がたなら　エスタブールの民を　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.70,0:19:50.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又人が死んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.75,0:19:53.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又クラウに人を殺させてしまった
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.81,0:19:58.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かっていた　この戦争は必要と
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.74,0:20:02.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だからフロワードの罪を咎めなかった
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.66,0:20:06.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラウに指揮を任せたのは　少しでも救える命を増やしたかったから
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.06,0:20:10.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　それは自分への言い訳か
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.76,0:20:12.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シオン兄ちゃん泣くの？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.24,0:20:16.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絵本で読んだことあるけど　それで泣きそうな顔だよね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.69,0:20:18.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イリスでばそれ見るの初めて
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.03,0:20:21.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フェリス姉様は泣いたりしないし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.31,0:20:24.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ルシル兄様は泣く所か　いつも笑い顔で怖いし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.72,0:20:27.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに　ルシルは怖いね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.88,0:20:29.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　泣くの？ね　ね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.10,0:20:31.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣かないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.30,0:20:33.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひょっとしてイリス　邪魔しちゃった？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.32,0:20:34.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.15,0:20:39.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　次　次泣く時は絶対見せてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.50,0:20:42.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それより　ライナとフェリスからの報告があるんじゃないのかい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.03,0:20:44.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ　そうだった
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.43,0:20:45.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい　これ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.60,0:20:53.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは　犬がライナで　天使がフェリスかな
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.77,0:20:58.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　野獣君と勧善懲悪美少女天使フェリス姉様
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.03,0:21:00.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相変わらずだな
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.13,0:21:01.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.12,0:21:05.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのね　穴を掘ったら短剣見たいのが出て来て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.32,0:21:08.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だか分らないから投げたら　突然龍が生えたんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.70,0:21:11.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさか　勇者の遺物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.39,0:21:13.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当にあったのか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.23,0:21:16.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.28,0:21:18.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうした　ミラー
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.23,0:21:21.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これを
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.18,0:21:26.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.48,0:21:28.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情報を挙げてきたのは「彼」です
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.75,0:21:30.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「彼」のことはよくご存知でしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.43,0:21:37.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イリス　悪いがすぐライナたちの所に戻っては貰えないか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.62,0:21:45.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,んじゃライナ　今日の分頼んだぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.65,0:21:49.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,団子…！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.66,0:21:57.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シオンの…シオンの#￥%&（@！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.25,0:21:59.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あまり下品な言葉は禁止
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:34.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は？この間の勇者の遺物の再調査？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.61,0:23:36.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌だよ　そんな面倒くせえこと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.99,0:23:41.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうせ行った先でも何だかんだ面倒くせえことになってんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.28,0:23:44.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ったく　マジ面倒くせえ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,





Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.74,0:01:47.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧 这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.26,0:01:50.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显是丸子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.96,0:01:52.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买了这么多啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.70,0:01:54.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢 用你的钱买的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.85,0:01:55.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭什么用我的钱？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.99,0:01:58.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自然是作为前些日子你失败的赔礼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.27,0:01:58.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.92,0:02:00.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有意义的让我潜入要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.89,0:02:04.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易找到的勇者的遗物却放着不使用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.98,0:02:07.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今以后每天你都得给我买丸子 知道不
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.69,0:02:10.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放着不管的时候你不也在旁边吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.22,0:02:13.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法不是 沉睡了几百年的勇者的遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.00,0:02:16.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那么容易使用的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.50,0:02:19.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了 为什么我要给你买丸...子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.28,0:02:24.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我买 请让我给你买
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.53,0:02:25.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.58,0:02:26.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎下次光临
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.84,0:02:28.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我这么倒霉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.66,0:02:31.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！这全都是西昂干的好事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.59,0:02:34.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙把麻烦的事都推到我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.31,0:02:37.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 那家伙现在在城堡里吃着好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.53,0:02:40.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悠哉的睡着午觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:55.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 这段时间的事情 您准备怎么负责
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.82,0:02:58.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种口气说话 对陛下太无礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.12,0:03:01.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 让他说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.53,0:03:02.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下还是太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.93,0:03:06.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅赐予我们属国艾斯塔布鲁的王和贵族们在我们国家的地位
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.87,0:03:08.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给予他们百姓生活保障
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:10.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这种态度才导致了叛乱...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.63,0:03:11.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.95,0:03:16.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大登场了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.65,0:03:18.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉 陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.06,0:03:21.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他也是为国家着想
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.27,0:03:22.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂 不用在意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.81,0:03:27.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打断一下 对于这次的叛乱 您想如何处置呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.45,0:03:31.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望您能够迅速作出决策
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.27,0:03:36.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迅速的决策？ 得到消息也才两天而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.19,0:03:39.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叛乱局的大本营 以及主谋者也不清楚在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.85,0:03:41.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人生气的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.42,0:03:43.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对策已经有了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.85,0:03:44.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.80,0:03:47.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叛乱首领也已经查清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.28,0:03:51.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾斯塔布鲁过去的国王的独生女 娜亚·安小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.84,0:03:55.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,详细的事情就由收集情报的米兰·弗洛沃德大佐来解释
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.84,0:04:01.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据情报 艾斯塔布鲁有大约5万兵力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.20,0:04:02.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五万？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.37,0:04:05.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经不再是叛乱了 这不成战争了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.62,0:04:08.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与艾斯塔布鲁领土接壤的各位领主
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.52,0:04:10.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有可能将被卷入这场战争之中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.13,0:04:14.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你们能在短时间之内留在这座城堡中避难
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.06,0:04:18.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而各位的领地 我们一定会保护的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.24,0:04:19.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然叫我们离开领地
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.99,0:04:23.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是让我们允许你们任意践踏我们的领土吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.27,0:04:25.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情 绝不会被允许的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.30,0:04:28.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道有什么见不得人的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.89,0:04:30.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那样的东西当然没有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.84,0:04:33.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然你们留在领地也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.79,0:04:36.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾斯塔布鲁的兵力也不过才5万
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.28,0:04:38.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么好担心的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.41,0:04:43.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 现在我就去领一支军队
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.53,0:04:47.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去各个领地警卫 也镇压一下叛乱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.31,0:04:50.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 这次的事情就拜托给克劳·克罗姆少将了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.15,0:04:54.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.67,0:04:57.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗洛沃德你还是负责情报的收集和传递吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.33,0:04:59.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由你来辅佐克劳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.82,0:05:01.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要这家伙的辅助
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.89,0:05:02.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是命令 克劳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.47,0:05:04.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗洛沃德 没有问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.65,0:05:05.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.98,0:05:12.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.28,0:05:14.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场叛乱 是你设计的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.44,0:05:18.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你手下的人引起叛乱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.84,0:05:21.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将艾斯塔布鲁的反罗兰德者一网打尽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.92,0:05:25.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并以战争为借口 向各个领地里进兵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.33,0:05:28.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去探查反国王派的贵族的恶行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.39,0:05:31.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然是这样的话 又当如何呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.24,0:05:34.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么如何的 你做好自己的事情就行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.54,0:05:35.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.69,0:05:46.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲现在在罗兰德吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.58,0:05:48.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很在意您的父亲吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的父亲 也就是我们的国王
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.11,0:05:55.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了换取罗兰德的地位和安全
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.45,0:05:57.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然轻易的出卖了自己的国家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.06,0:05:59.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.60,0:06:02.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 如果父王是叛乱者的领袖的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.90,0:06:04.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,百姓们会更加高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.03,0:06:09.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们贵族 以及百姓都非常的仰仗您
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.31,0:06:12.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们新的王 娜亚·安陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.69,0:06:15.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事情就不要再说了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.31,0:06:17.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在害怕吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.20,0:06:21.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 这场仗没有打赢会怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.38,0:06:24.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且罗兰德对艾斯塔布鲁的子民很好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.03,0:06:27.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有战争的必要吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.83,0:06:30.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 要从罗兰德手中夺回历史悠久的艾斯塔布鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.90,0:06:33.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国家怎么样无所谓 重要的是百姓
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.77,0:06:36.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来人民真的会幸福吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.50,0:06:38.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只不过是无谓的流血啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.41,0:06:43.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我的人民过得很幸福就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.85,0:06:46.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样教我的不正是你吗？ 萨拉威尔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.65,0:06:49.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们的势力还算强大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.54,0:06:52.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以罗兰德才不敢轻举妄动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.77,0:06:55.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 今后这样的事情可不敢保证
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.89,0:06:58.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗兰德的贵族们的恶行也在四处流传
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.97,0:07:01.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真心为人民着想的话 现在是大好时机
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.95,0:07:05.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你都这么说了 一定是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.13,0:07:10.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了你 我们死也不惧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:16.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想建立一个谁都可以高兴的生活 谁都可以幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.11,0:07:18.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一个国家
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.85,0:07:20.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以做到吗？ 萨拉威尔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.96,0:07:22.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.50,0:07:40.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 正式与罗兰德开战！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.64,0:07:43.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺回艾斯塔布鲁的主权
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.51,0:07:50.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克罗姆少将的传令 战斗已经开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.65,0:08:11.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休斯 敌人的数量是？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.25,0:08:13.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概八九千人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.42,0:08:16.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如弗洛沃德情报所述啊 真是令人不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.72,0:08:17.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.34,0:08:21.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么 那么 以最少的牺牲来结束这里的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.77,0:08:22.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.57,0:08:25.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全军突击！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.23,0:08:29.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗兰德的走狗们！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.23,0:08:30.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哪里窜出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.79,0:08:33.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的乱战里大型魔法不能使用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.47,0:08:35.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪开闪开闪开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.17,0:08:38.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里 指挥官在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.74,0:08:51.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊 这支军队的指挥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.09,0:08:53.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.88,0:09:01.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们艾斯塔布鲁的指挥官 我已经改掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.37,0:09:05.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在抵抗的话就全部杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.32,0:09:08.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血染红了 红手指的克劳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.30,0:09:10.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是罗兰德的红指克劳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.08,0:09:14.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 无谓的厮杀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.94,0:09:26.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被打败啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.75,0:09:29.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直就像我军的行动被对方了如指掌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.83,0:09:33.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说过了 这是无谋的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.21,0:09:34.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今还说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.43,0:09:39.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红指克劳 听说罗兰德的指挥官好像是克劳·克罗姆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.08,0:09:40.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.61,0:09:45.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说他并不是全力杀我军兵士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.37,0:09:47.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是让他们投降
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.48,0:09:48.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.43,0:09:50.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果说那是罗兰德的战斗方式
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.81,0:09:54.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是英雄王西昂·阿斯塔尔的意志的话 果然这场战争...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:58.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在说什么呢 这些肯定是敌人的诡计
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.86,0:10:01.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 他们只是怕夺取艾斯塔布鲁之后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.75,0:10:04.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会招来更多的怨恨才这样做的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.26,0:10:08.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方法还是有的 不能示弱啊 公主
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.84,0:10:13.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克罗姆少将的军队 已经将叛军的大本营包围起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.16,0:10:43.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.53,0:10:46.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗兰德撤军 释放俘虏
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.01,0:10:49.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不听从以上命令的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.09,0:10:52.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将立即斩杀所有艾斯塔布鲁的国民
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.20,0:10:56.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相同内容的一封信我们发给了罗兰德军
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.94,0:11:00.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗兰德的英雄王是不会对人民见死不救的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.16,0:11:03.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然做出了这种事...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.64,0:11:04.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.04,0:11:07.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这是不得已而为之的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.71,0:11:10.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想 很想保护公主你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.34,0:11:12.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护我把全国百姓做人质吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.52,0:11:17.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为百姓着想 我们输了的话会变得怎么样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.60,0:11:21.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战败国的人民将受到多少虐待多少折磨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.80,0:11:25.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将百姓作为人质 就不会让他们受到虐待了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.71,0:11:29.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在已经不能阻止了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.28,0:11:31.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经无法阻止了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.29,0:11:40.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 我只是一个傀儡王
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.59,0:11:42.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果 谁也救不了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.25,0:11:47.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公...公主 罗兰德的军队
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.07,0:11:51.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们军队正在攻击艾斯塔布鲁的要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.44,0:11:52.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.64,0:12:00.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...我们军队的人都在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.33,0:12:02.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那是哪里来的部队？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.40,0:12:04.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陛下派援军过来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.47,0:12:07.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西昂将一切都托付给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.93,0:12:09.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会发生那种事情的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.08,0:12:10.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.88,0:12:13.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 是他？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.50,0:12:15.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.87,0:12:19.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红指克劳无视人质继续攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.78,0:12:24.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 以百姓作为人质也被攻破的话 我们都是死刑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.85,0:12:27.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 还没有分出胜负呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.06,0:12:30.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将人质杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.86,0:12:35.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 罗兰德认为我们不会真的下手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.08,0:12:37.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀掉人质的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.22,0:12:38.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.67,0:12:39.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.92,0:12:43.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都做得很好 但是到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.10,0:12:46.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将人质都放了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.65,0:12:47.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是公主殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.82,0:12:51.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会尽力去做的 以我一人的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.43,0:12:55.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 唯独不能让公主你死
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.54,0:12:58.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也 我也和公主一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.94,0:13:00.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 公主殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.36,0:13:03.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你们这些话就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.78,0:13:04.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.32,0:13:07.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都要活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.68,0:13:12.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 尽可能的让艾斯塔布鲁的国民过的幸福一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.28,0:13:14.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此...我...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.64,0:13:17.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会让我很苦恼的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.04,0:13:21.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位的爱国之心真是深深感动了我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.85,0:13:26.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 对我来说 如果光是娜亚·安皇室后裔的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.20,0:13:29.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不足以补偿你们所犯下的罪过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.43,0:13:34.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 用来陪衬所谓的艾斯塔布鲁这个国家消失的悲剧的戏幕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.23,0:13:37.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然也应该是相应的悲剧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.32,0:13:38.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.28,0:13:42.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是罗兰德帝国军大佐 米兰·弗洛沃德
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.93,0:13:44.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.38,0:13:46.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面的守军全都被打败了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.65,0:13:50.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 不是 这座城堡可没有那么容易被攻破
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.77,0:13:54.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被攻破了 我也不会让罗兰德兵进城的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.19,0:13:56.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.32,0:14:00.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场悲剧的最终幕将在这里展开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.26,0:14:02.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗 飞舞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.20,0:14:13.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.67,0:14:15.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护公主
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.40,0:14:16.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.24,0:14:17.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我不能对大家不管啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.43,0:14:27.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往里走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.15,0:14:35.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 都死了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.31,0:14:40.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国家 人们 都消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.77,0:14:43.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 还有幸存的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.41,0:14:45.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有幸存者这是真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.92,0:14:48.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你的性命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.78,0:14:52.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被逼入绝境的艾斯塔布鲁开始暴走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.81,0:14:55.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残杀人质
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.43,0:14:56.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨拉威尔？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.61,0:15:00.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那场暴走的指挥权所有者 公主 是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.86,0:15:02.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...那么...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.98,0:15:06.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 将暴走的公主杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.31,0:15:10.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终结这场战争的人是 艾斯塔布鲁的贵族 萨拉威尔·西路
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.39,0:15:13.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将会被作为拯救国家的英雄 被罗兰德欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.71,0:15:19.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泄露我军动向 提出以人质相要挟的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.93,0:15:21.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:24.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏我一直信任你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.69,0:15:28.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初我是想娶你为妻 借此来夺取这个国家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.93,0:15:35.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想 建立一个大家都能幸福生活的国度
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.42,0:15:39.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是说漂亮话的话世界可不会绕你转的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.82,0:15:41.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.63,0:15:45.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的公主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.95,0:15:47.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这样就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.58,0:16:06.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请安心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.24,0:16:12.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗兰德还不至于却英雄缺到让这样的男人成为英雄 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.19,0:16:14.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英雄吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.50,0:16:18.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是罗兰德英雄王西昂·阿斯塔尔的做法吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.74,0:16:21.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的国王不喜欢这样的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.64,0:16:24.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的所作所为都是我个人的独断
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.43,0:16:29.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 串通萨拉威尔引导我们叛乱的都是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.48,0:16:30.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 都是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.87,0:16:36.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看穿了这点 所以把镇压叛乱的事情交付给克罗姆少将而不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.94,0:16:38.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的王的大方之处
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.69,0:16:42.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 正如萨拉威尔所说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.65,0:16:45.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光会说漂亮话世界也不会就此改变这是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.16,0:16:49.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜亚·安小姐杀掉人质后自裁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.73,0:16:52.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是原本的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.64,0:16:55.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿斯塔尔王允许这么做了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.58,0:16:57.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有暴露的话最好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:17:02.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会原谅我的吧 那就是王的器量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.74,0:17:11.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 没有受伤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.44,0:17:15.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你才是叛乱的主谋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.65,0:17:17.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您来了 克罗姆少将
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.12,0:17:19.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟会来的这么快
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.08,0:17:21.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我的问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.46,0:17:25.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克罗姆少将 那么 这位红指克劳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.34,0:17:27.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据你的回答...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.55,0:17:29.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要杀了我 吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.96,0:17:32.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你对西昂来说 是不需要的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.92,0:17:36.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说 你根本看不到那位大人所背负的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.95,0:17:39.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是 根本就不配做那位大人的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.92,0:17:42.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在西昂的身边呆着 根本不需要什么资格
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.13,0:17:48.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了给那位大人开路 我要杀掉娜亚·安小姐和所有人质
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.48,0:17:51.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你还要阻挠的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.69,0:17:53.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为你能打败我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.23,0:17:55.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.02,0:17:59.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.06,0:18:04.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那股力量是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.63,0:18:11.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了艾斯塔布鲁的子民们 现在还不能失去这个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.63,0:18:13.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.52,0:18:14.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.23,0:18:16.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗洛沃德
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.29,0:18:21.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗洛沃德大佐 如果为了彻底支配艾斯塔布鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.10,0:18:26.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不得不是杀光人质的话 那就由我去说服他们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.52,0:18:30.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会向百姓和士兵说 让他们顺从罗兰德 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.30,0:18:32.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.98,0:18:36.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起杀人质来损害艾斯塔布鲁的名誉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.65,0:18:39.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做更有效果
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.44,0:18:44.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 因为你在艾斯塔布鲁人民心目中地位很高呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.03,0:18:49.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 可能会被说成是卖国贼的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.05,0:18:53.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系 你那么希望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.27,0:18:55.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后将我杀了也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.79,0:18:59.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何 绝对不可以伤害百姓
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.40,0:19:01.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.37,0:19:07.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争结束了 领兵去吧 克罗姆少将
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.67,0:19:09.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.01,0:19:14.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.84,0:19:17.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信 你 和你的王
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.71,0:19:19.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.73,0:19:27.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克罗姆少将 我有些脱力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.55,0:19:29.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能扶我站起来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.31,0:19:31.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.00,0:19:36.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.93,0:19:45.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是你们的话 一定可以 拯救艾斯塔布鲁的人民的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.70,0:19:50.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有人死了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.75,0:19:53.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有人被克劳杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.81,0:19:58.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂 这场战争是不打不可的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.74,0:20:02.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以也没有向弗洛沃德问罪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.66,0:20:06.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任命克劳为指挥 也是希望能更多的拯救生命
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.06,0:20:10.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这也只不过是自我慰藉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.76,0:20:12.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西昂哥会哭不？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.24,0:20:16.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,图书里面曾今看到过的 那是要哭了的表情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.69,0:20:18.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊莉丝还是第一次看到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.03,0:20:21.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲莉丝姐姐也不会哭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.31,0:20:24.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西尔哥哥别说哭了 整天一张笑脸可怕死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.72,0:20:27.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 路西尔很可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.88,0:20:29.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 会哭吗？ 诶诶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.10,0:20:31.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会哭的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.30,0:20:33.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 被伊莉丝打扰了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.32,0:20:34.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.15,0:20:39.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 下次 下次哭的时候一定要给我看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.50,0:20:42.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 莱纳和菲莉丝有没有报告发来？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.03,0:20:44.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.43,0:20:45.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.60,0:20:53.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是 狗是莱娜 天使是菲莉丝吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.77,0:20:58.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 野兽君和惩恶扬善美少女天使菲莉丝姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.03,0:21:00.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是一点没变呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.13,0:21:01.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.12,0:21:05.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊 挖洞的时候发现了一把短剑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.32,0:21:08.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道到底是什么就扔了 结果突然一条龙窜了出来 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.70,0:21:11.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 勇者的遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.39,0:21:13.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的存在吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.23,0:21:16.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.28,0:21:18.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 米拉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.23,0:21:21.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.18,0:21:26.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.48,0:21:28.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提交这份情报的是“他”
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.75,0:21:30.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“他”的话您应该非常清楚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.43,0:21:37.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊莉丝 不好意思能不能请你马上回到莱纳他们身边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.62,0:21:45.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么莱纳 今天的份就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.65,0:21:49.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丸子丸子丸子丸子丸子...!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.66,0:21:57.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西昂这个....西昂这个@%#$%&$(#!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.25,0:21:59.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下流的话是要“哔”的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:34.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？重新调查之前的勇者的遗物？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.61,0:23:36.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不呢 那么麻烦的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.99,0:23:41.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正去了以后肯定是各种麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.28,0:23:44.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 真的很麻烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,

