Won't you reconsider this
one more time?
Reconsider what?
The issue regarding Naruto!
It's too risky to allow Naruto
to take part in this mission.
If something were to happen...
Don't make me say it again!
Team Kakashi, with Naruto and Sakura,
will handle this mission.
I've explained my reasoning!
I understand that...
But...it's not really "Team Kakashi"
because he can't even go with them!
The situation is different from when
we dispatched them to the Hidden Sand!
That's true...
You'll probably get mad if I say this.
But I'll take care of that Jinchuriki.
In the previous mission,
the enemy was clearly after Naruto...
Wait! Hey!
We were able to prevent that since we had Kakashi Sensei with us, who knows Naruto very well...
Naruto!
But we won't have Kakashi Sensei
on this mission...
It's understandable that
Shizune would be concerned...
Don't worry, Sakura.
That point has been taken
under consideration...
I'll find two members to fill in the holes
left by Kakashi and Sasuke.
Make sure to tell Naruto as well!
Yes, ma'am...
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll.
Naruto! Just keep charging at him!
Ninja Art: Shadow Sewing!
Who the hell... are you...?
Lady Tsunade...
I'm on my way...
Tsunade...
I need to speak with you...
Let me see you for a moment.
Formation! New Team Kakashi
What did you want to talk about?
Since you two advisors are here,
this probably isn't going to be pleasant!
As it happens...
Shizune recently came to us
seeking our advice...
What do you want to talk about?
It's about Naruto Uzumaki.
From now on, do not assign missions
with a possibility of contact with
the Akatsuki to Naruto Uzumaki...
You know... the reason, don't you?
Yeah... I've been hearing about it
from Shizune.
From here on, make sure he works in a
four-man squad with more skilled Shinobi
and increase surveillance on him
as well as protection.
Furthermore, you should reduce the amount of
missions you assign him as much as possible,
and limit the scope of his activities.
Got it, Tsunade...?
If Shizune has asked for your advice...
then you should know what my answer will be.
Lady Tsunade...
No way!
Tsunade...
Naruto's not just an ordinary kid.
He's a Jinchuriki!
Under normal circumstances,
the logical thing to do
would be to keep him
in the village and under surveillance...
It may not sound like it,
but this is a compromise.
I agree that he should work
in a four-man squad.
But Naruto shouldn't have
so many restrictions placed on him!
Even if we keep Naruto in the village,
the Akatsuki will definitely come after him,
come after the Jinchuriki...
Even in the recent incident
in the Hidden Sand Village,
they went after Gaara, the Jinchuriki,
even though he was
in what was considered
the safest location in the village.
There's a strong possibility that
they'll take a similarly hard-line approach
in regards to Naruto as well.
If that happens, at the end of the day,
the Leaf Village will be in danger as well.
If Naruto stays on the move,
the enemy won't immediately be able
to figure out what he's doing.
First of all, Naruto does have talent...
He's a Shinobi who should be
a great asset to the Leaf Village.
That's a pathetic objection, Tsunade.
You call yourself the Hokage?
I'm trying to compromise too, you know!
Then can you ensure that, until then, Naruto
won't get taken out by the Akatsuki?!
And can you ensure that if the Akatsuki
take the Nine-Tails from Naruto,
it won't bring about bigger calamity
for the Leaf Village?!
As promised in that bet,
that unlucky necklace...will be mine.
That's enough!
Don't protect me anymore, Naruto!
I told you...That kind of stubbornness
will get you killed!
If you die, you'll have nothing...
No dreams or anything!
That's enough! Move! Run!
It'll be okay...
Until...
Until I become the Hokage,
there's no way will I die!
Here's a spell that makes
dreams come true.
Naruto...won't be beaten!
I believe that...
If... that judgment turns out
to be mistaken...
what will you do?
If perchance, the Hidden Leaf Village and the
Land of Fire become endangered by my decision...
then as the Fifth Hokage,
I will protect them with my life!
Very well... If you're willing to go that far,
do as you like.
However...
In exchange for that,
you will use the Shinobi we select
as the additional members
of the four-man squad.
Fine.
Danzo... Come on in!
You're...
Long time no see...
Princess Tsunade.
To think you'd show up...
I see... So the new team members
will be from The Foundation, huh...?
You're sure weak.
Are you sure you have any
"balls" with that kind of skill?
Wha--?! You little!
I asked...
who the hell you are!
We'll be seeing
each other again...Naruto.
Hold it!
Who was that...?
Choji! I thought you'd be here!
For crying out loud!
Asuma Sensei's angry and
wants you to get a move on!
Sorry, Ino...
We got attacked by some weirdo...
Some weirdo...?
By weirdo, do you mean...
Isn't that Naruto?!
No... when I said weirdo,
I didn't mean Naruto...
Naruto! Long time no see!
- Don't bother, Choji.
- How have you been!
This atmosphere's such a pain...
- Hey, you've gotta tell me your stories!
So you will be arranging
the two additional team members?
No...
Just one member...
So you also weren't expecting
the team leader, Kakashi...
to be out of action, huh...?
Since Kakashi Hatake is
recuperating right now,
an additional member will be required
on Team Kakashi's next mission.
And we don't have much time
until the mission.
This should be left up to you,
Lady Tsunade...
Kakashi's withdrawal is unexpected
for me as well...
I was just at the point of wondering
what should be done...
Then you should select
someone very skilled
from the Anbu Black Ops under
your direct control to lead the team.
Yes! That would be good.
You've no objections, right, Tsunade?
Leave the selection to me.
Is that okay with you...?
How about it, Danzo...?
Then, I'll do it as I please...
L-Lady Tsunade...!
Geez, I don't like this!
I-I'm very sorry...
But I had absolutely no intention
of betraying you...
I'm not talking about you!
What...?
I'm talking about that man.
I'd also thought of having someone
from the Anbu Black Ops
under my direct control replace Kakashi.
I have someone specific in mind...
But...I never thought they'd
suggest that from their end.
I totally thought they were going to force
one of their own subordinates on me...
Does this mean one person
is enough for the surveillance of Naruto?
Or...are they after something else?
Uh...Umm...Lady Tsunade...?
Of course, I've got tons of things
I want to say to you !
Yikes!
That said, the formation of Team Kakashi
is a more immediate concern.
You're going to work really hard!
Oh, y-yes, ma'am!
That was fast...
I heard it was a matter of urgency...
You know why you're here, right?
I have a general idea.
I want you to take Kakashi's place.
It's an honor to be able to work
in Kakashi Senpai's stead...
This isn't an Anbu Black Ops mission.
It will be a regular mission.
Therefore, take off that mask
and I will give you a codename.
During this mission,
you'll be known as "Yamato."
I understand...
An additional member... a new recruit from
the Anbu Black Ops Training Division
will be dispatched to Team Kakashi.
From the...Foundation?
However...
What is it?
Keep a close watch on his actions.
What...do you mean?
Danzo recommended this new recruit.
The man called Danzo...
used to be in the Taka faction that
opposed the Third Hokage...
He formed the Anbu Black Ops
Training Division
as a detached unit within
the Anbu Black Ops and
took the position of chief.
I'm sure you've at least heard
of his name, right?
The Foundation has since been
disbanded and he has fallen from power.
But I still can't figure out
what he's thinking...
Perhaps you're worrying too much...?
Never mind...
Meet up with the team immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Sakura!
This is the spot...
where we're supposed to meet, right?
Yeah... No doubt about it.
Nobody's here yet, considering...
Did Granny Tsunade really arrange
new members for us?
It'll be okay. We just got here
a little too early, that's all.
We've still got a little bit before
the meeting time.
I hope they don't turn out to have the habit
of showing up late like Kakashi Sensei...
Hi...
Hey! It's you!
You're the guy who was up
on the roof earlier...
Umm...as of now I will be...
taking Kakashi's place in
Team Kakashi and...
This is going to be a nasty mission.