I knew you'd be here.
I'd expect no less from
the Anbu Black Ops...
under the direct command
of the Hokage.
To think I wouldn't be able
to deceive you with that corpse...
Now tell us everything.
What's this about?
Bonds
You jerk!
Why did you betray us?!
You shouldn't make too much
of a commotion here.
Things will get troublesome,
you see.
- You jerk!
- Naruto!
Here...take this.
It's yours, isn't it?
Thank you.
It was an order
from Danzo, right?
Danzo has teamed up
with Orochimaru...
and is attempting
to do something...
You were chosen
to be the go-between...
for Danzo and Orochimaru.
What're they planning...?
With Orochimaru, he's planning to...
once again destroy the Leaf Village...
Isn't that right?
No, that's not--
I can tell right away that
your smile is a lie!
And I can tell right away that
what you're saying is a lie!
Now that you have found me...
my mission is considered
a failure.
I can't handle all of
you guys by myself...
And...if you know that much...
then there's no point
in hiding anything.
You're exactly right.
We're going to crush
the current Leaf Village.
Say what...?!
The real mission I was given was
to gain the favor of Orochimaru...
and create an opportunity for
a collaboration...
in order to crush the Leaf Village.
Do you know
what you're saying?!
- To do such a thing--
- That's not all.
I also have the duty
of secretly sending...
information about Orochimaru
to Lord Danzo...
In other words, I have also been
entrusted with a mission as a spy.
Keep going.
Own up to everything
you're hiding.
So basically what
you're saying is...
while proposing the collaboration
with Orochimaru...
you're trying to outflank him?
You've been given such
a dangerous mission...
Orochimaru will definitely betray us...
once the Leaf Village
has been crushed.
It's to make sure we've always
got the advantage.
I get it...
Danzo wants to make
the Leaf Village his own, huh?
You made preparations
for that all by yourself...
The information I wrote
in black ink
transforms into small animals...
and carries the information out
while protecting itself, you see.
This ability of mine
was valued highly...
and so I was selected
for this mission.
Many people will die, once again...
if things become turbulent
in the Leaf Village!
Do you even know why
you're doing this?!
No idea...
They're my orders, so...
Sai, you...
Let me tell you
one more thing...
Sai is the name I was given
just for this mission...
I'm nobody.
I'm a tool for Lord Danzo.
I don't exist.
So no matter what you say
to me, it's pointless.
Then...
Then why...
do you hold on to
that picture book with such care?!
The two kids on the cover...
are you and
your older brother, right?
You're holding on to
that picture book with such care...
because it's the only thing
that proves your existence, isn't it?
You haven't been able to discard
your emotions as completely as you say.
Even Shinobi can't completely
discard their emotions.
As proof of that...
when I handed
the picture book to you earlier...
You said thanks and took it.
You were relieved to get back...
the picture book that can prove
your existence.
Why does having this picture book
prove my own existence?
The reason why you don't want
to part with that book...
is that you can't forsake yourself
as a younger brother...
Do you know why?
It's because your bonds with
your older brother...
were that important to you!
You don't want to erase the bonds
you have with your older brother...
Bonds...
Sorry, but we had a look
inside the picture book.
Only the picture in
the center-facing pages is unfinished.
Sai... I also know that you're
from The Foundation.
And I also know that
you received special training...
from Danzo in order
to suppress your emotions.
Special training...?
It's the same as the evil practice...
once conducted in the Village Hidden
in the Mist a.k.a. Blood Mist Village,
in order to take away emotions.
The Blood Mist Village ...
The Hidden Mist...?
That's where Zabuza's from!
Then...
A long time ago...
in the Village Hidden in the Mist
a.k.a. Blood Mist Village,
there was an extremely difficult obstacle
in order to become Ninja.
You even know about
that graduation exam...?
That graduation exam?
What's that graduation exam?
Fellow students kill each other.
Fellow comrades who all ate
from the same bowl...
make teams of two
and fight each other...
until one of them dies.
Comrades who until that point
would help each other,
talk about their dreams
and compete with each other...
Looking at the flow
of the picture book,
it appears you're
defeating enemies...
and taking away
their weapons and armor...
On the facing pages at the center...
you will end up fighting
your older brother...
You killed your older brother...
No!
I was planning on
giving this to him.
But when I was just about finished
with the picture book, he...
He...
died from sickness.
What do you mean...you don't feel
anything or have any emotions?
I mean just what I said.
Even so...
If you have a brother,
you should be able to imagine...
what it would be like
to lose him, right?
Yeah, well...you could say that...
My brother's dead, after all.
Then all the more...
I wonder if I should've
looked like that.
What're you trying to say?
Well... I didn't know what kind
of look to make
when my brother died...
In The Foundation, there were
many children of broken families...
brought about by battle.
He was one of those children.
I became close with him,
like a brother.
We weren't related by blood...
But he often said nice things
about my drawings.
In this picture book...
what I wanted to show him
most of all...
was what were supposed to be the final
pictures on the facing pages.
But after he died...
I couldn't remember
what I was going to draw.
Unfortunately Sai...
I'll be having my clone
stand guard over you here.
All right!
Now it's back to square one...
We're going to save Sasuke!
I wouldn't bother.
I...
met Sasuke.
Sasuke always has Orochimaru
with him.
That is to say, you'll have to fight
Orochimaru once again.
You'll end up being
chopped up into pieces...
and turned into a test subject
if you pursue reckssly.
And...
And what?!
Sasuke said he doesn't care
about you...
Sakura said you think of Sasuke like
a brother.
And yet...
For a guy like that, why...?
Why are you trying
to get him back...
going so far as to oppose
Orochimaru and put your life at risk?
Why is that?
When nobody's ordering you to do so?
I used to really hate Sasuke.
Even though, like me,
he didn't have a family...
he was elite and
I was always at the bottom.
But it was actually fun
being with him.
He...
He's the person
who acknowledged me...
more than anyone else.
Sasuke...
is my friend.
It's a special bond
I was finally able to make.
A bond.
Even so...
Even so, with Orochimaru
as your opponent...
It doesn't matter
who the opponent is!
If my arms get torn off,
I'll kick him down.
If my legs get torn off,
I'll bite him down.
If my head gets torn off,
I'll stare him down.
If my eyes get torn out,
I'll curse him in my grave!
Even if I get chopped up
into pieces...
I'll take Sasuke back
from Orochimaru!