I tried coming alone to our usual park.
It's a feeling I've never felt.
Like a child, frightened by the sound of the wind
I ran back along the path home.
The sky outside the window is too vast. Where are you now?
Please, may this reach you...
Dear Lord, if you ever grant wishes,
grant my wish right now, please!
I want to hear your voice, I miss you! I want to see you now!
Why must you already be looking toward tomorrow?
Don't just brush it off, saying the time has slipped by.
Once more...
I love you, and yet it's been too late since long ago.
Even if I give up, it can't be like the past.
Don't just decide so simply there's no way, no choice.
Smile once more.
Kogorr!
The mysterious plant-like creatures
that appeared at the White House have
shown their monstrous true form!
Washington has issued an
emergency evacuation order.
And the well-being of the
President and his staff
who were in the White House before it
was swallowed up is currently unknown.
The Skrugg have reappeared,
but I'm sure that Heroman...
I mean, I'm sure that both
of them will do something!
It's the brat...
You again?
That's my line!
You can try again, but
it'll turn out the same!
We'll stop you... as many times as it takes!
Impossible.
You fools can no longer stop me.
Because this Earth is already well on
its way towards being annihilated...
Heroman!
Will you attack?
Then I will make you realize just how
much more powerful I am than that time!
We've entered the airspace
of the bombing target!
Code entered.
Safeties disengaged.
Can we really win with this?
Keep it together.
That kid's down there fighting
his heart out, you know?
We will accomplish our mission.
Yeah...
Prepare to drop the storm gathering bombs!
Bombs away!
Hey, what's with that?
What's the point of bombing the sky?
Did you forget?
I told you, remember?
They're making the energy that we're
going to use to recharge Heroman.
That?
Those bombs have a special compound in them.
This compound makes all the water vapor in
the air gather together almost explosively!
Pretty soon the entire sky will
be covered with storm clouds.
Lightning?
Exactly!
We'll get those clouds to produce lightning,
and have it strike Heroman directly!
If it works, he should be able to have plenty of
energy to recover, just like the time he ran out.
But wait...
Is it possible to direct where
lighting strikes like that?
I overlook NOTHING!
Generally speaking, lighting tries
to avoid traveling through air.
That's why it zig-zags as it falls
and strikes the tallest buildings.
We'll make use of that tendency!
I've installed special equipment on the MR-1
that can create an artificial
vacuum in the vicinity of Heroman.
If I do that, as it tries to avoid the air,
the lighting will strike toward the
invisible vacuum that acts like a lightning rod,
and Heroman's charging up will be complete!
So that's why we've got to hurry and
get this thing near Heroman, then?
Yes...
As soon as possible.
You are such a fool.
Thinking you could oppose
me, as weak as you are.
You're too late.
There is no one that can stop me now.
If I make one false step, I'm done for.
That's...
Those are... the spheres!
The spheres are heading toward Kogorr!
The spheres...
The spheres are turning into a liquid,
and being absorbed by Kogorr!
Mr. Hughes... What in the world is going on?
It's probably...
Well, our common wisdom is
useless against the Skrugg.
The spheres melted?
Those spheres, that humanity
couldn't even scratch?!
Just like that?
Watch where yer drivin', baldy!
Hey, Professor!
Look ahead!
Watch out!
Ahead?
Phew...
That was close...
What in the world...
I told you already.
I will devour this world.
Everything I consume will
become my sustenance.
And they are no exception!
Lord Kogorr, what are you...
Hey, wait...
He's eating his ally?
Everything will become my food!
This isn't good...
Let's move a bit farther away!
We can't!
This is a crucial moment!
Is this the time to worry about that?
If we're shot down, that's it!
But...
Don't worry.
We'll keep filming.
We should just get some altitude, and then...
Understood!
Guess that's for the best!
At this rate...
That's...
Will!
Heroman!
Heroman...
Is everyone okay?
Yeah...
Somehow...
Thank goodness.
Don't be so relieved.
What're we supposed to do now?
We fell pretty far...
How are the preparations?
We can go any time.
Okay, head out.
Yes, sir.
Why are you heading to the scene now?
I can give orders more quickly observing
the situation on the ground myself.
I can't do that from the cargo plane.
Then why not use a helicopter?
The enemy has complete
control of the airspace.
There's a great chance that we'd
be shot down if we got too close.
In the end, Mr. Denton's
plan seemed to be the best.
I'm sorry about getting you involved
in something this dangerous.
I-I don't really mind.
I know.
But they're fighting in an
even more dangerous situation.
I couldn't just sit there doing nothing.
Will!
Will, answer me!
Are you okay?
I didn't ask for your help.
Get away from here, Will.
We'll handle this.
Not a chance!
Will?
I have no reason to follow your orders.
I...
I came here for my own fight!
Will...
Don't misunderstand me!
I'm not your ally or anything!
But...
Even so, we have the same goal.
Ironic, isn't it?
This weapon caused Heroman so much
trouble, and now it's going to help him?
Hate to say it, but we
really owe Dr. Minami one.
That's the way!
Nice and slow!
Slowly!
Hurry! It's about to break!
No!
It'll be even more dangerous
to pull up too quickly!
So take it slow!
But hurry!
Make up your damn mind!
Hurry!
Slowly!
...says them.
Don't worry.
This speed will do, according
to my calculations.
Professor!
Let's do this thing!
Excellent.
No, don't look at me.
That's just the amazing
potential the MR-1 possesses.
With it, we're going to save
Joey and Heroman, for sure!
Do you understand?
Our target is the crystal on Kogorr's chest!
I realized it after my body became like this.
That's the weak point for all the Skrugg!
If we can destroy that
crystal, we can end it all!
Heroman.
Will.
Let's go!
You bastards...
You're mine!
Look at that!
What's going on?
Go back! On the double!
Get the shot!
Somehow...
Somehow I have to get up there...
Then how about this?
Heroman!
What?!
You impudent little...
Take this!
That's not all!
Heroman!
Go!
Fool.
I've already predicted your every move!
Oh, I wonder about that.
Heroman...
Augment!
What?
Finish him, Joey!
Heroman...
Blast!
I don't think so!
All right!
Too bad.
That's not where my weak point is!
Heroman!!!
I want to get to know you better,
to go at each other with our true feelings.
Your tears and smile are both here.
No matter how hard it is, I won't be scared any more.
With both of us, we can go anywhere.
Since you're the one who taught me that I'm not alone.
Every time I mutter the words "I was born to meet you"
my unease disappears, and my heart burns stronger.
Thank you. We'll go on together with a sign only we understand.
Carve out this irreplaceable time!
I can't move away from here.
Because I live feeling the same heartbeat.
I want to protect you to the very last,
to protect the promise built up.
Thank you. We'll go on together with a sign only we understand.
We are carving out this irreplaceable time!
On the next Heroman:
Heroman!
It can't be!
Answer me!
Say something!
I'm begging you!
Kogorr continues to evolve
to his complete form,
and Heroman has fallen silent
after being attacked.
While the countdown to Earth's destruction
begins, Joey makes his decision.
The final battle heads toward its climax.
Next time on Heroman #26: Faith.
Heroman!