They're both smiling...
Yeah... He smiled for real for
the first time when he drew that.
Smiled from the bottom of his heart.
Wh-What's this...?!
Reunion
It was in Sai's bag...
This is an assassination list
that has...
an Anbu Black Ops member's
own targets recorded...
It's called a Bingo Book.
An assassination list...?
What are these "X" marks?
In all likelihood,
they're marks indicating targets
that have already been eliminated.
Why does Sai have such a thing?
Look at this...
Th-This is...!
Sasuke...
Why does Sai...!
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll.
There's no "X" mark on this yet...
I get it...
So that's what this is about?
What do you mean?!
Sai...
His mission wasn't to be a go-between
for Orochimaru and Danzo.
Sai's true classified mission...
was to assassinate Sasuke.
That could never be!
After all, he said earlier that
he was going to save Sasuke...
And he really smiled from
the bottom of his heart...
This is what I wanted
to show him.
The picture of our dreams...
Unlike before, he's now...
What if that was all...
an act in order
to forestall you, Naruto?
I'm a tool for Lord Danzo.
I don't exist.
So no matter what you say to me,
it's pointless...
The owner of this Bingo Book...
could indeed be capable
of something like that.
Look at this...
This man in the book
next to Sasuke...
He's a Jonin from
the Hidden Mist...
and the man who expressed
a hard-line stance against the Leaf.
Sai...defeated him, huh...?
He couldn't have been
an easy opponent to defeat...
The fact that he eliminated him
means that in all likelihood,
he must have resorted
to every possible means.
An act in order
to forestall someone...
was probably all in
a day's work for him.
A smile is used
to carry out a goal...
You tricked me with
your fake smile earlier.
So that's how you use
a fake smile, huh...?
I'll remember that.
How can you grin like that
after getting punched?!
A smile is the best way
to get through a tough situation.
Even if it's a fake smile.
Surprisingly enough,
everyone gets fooled...
It said that in a book...
It's quite clear by looking
at each of the people listed...
in this Bingo Book...
Sai was assigned to the disposal
of people dangerous to the Leaf...
And Sasuke is also
one such dangerous person.
Danzo's goal...
was to bury Orochimaru's new flesh...
to bury Sasuke...
In order to do that,
Sai attempted
to approach Orochimaru...
He didn't betray the Leaf.
It was for the sake of the Leaf.
That's exactly what one from
a hard-line military faction would think up.
There's no point in going on
about that here...
It doesn't matter
what Sai was ordered to do...
or what that Danzo guy's
thinking about.
Meeting up with Sai
as quickly as possible...
and saving Sasuke
is what's important!
It's indeed as Naruto says.
I felt Sai's Chakra earlier.
We need to go quickly.
Right! Got it!
If Sai is after Sasuke...
then I'll stop him,
no matter what!
Who's there?
You found me out, huh...?
But...I've already made
the first move.
What is your objective?
Lord Danzo's objective is
to bury you...
I'm going to...
Sai!
...take you back to the Leaf!
Although at the beginning,
I came here with the intention
of killing you...
He's the person who acknowledged me
more than anyone else.
Naruto...thinks of Sasuke
like a brother.
I'll do whatever it takes
to save him.
I'll even team up with you.
Even if I get chopped up
into pieces,
I'll take Sasuke back
from Orochimaru!
Sasuke is my friend.
It's a special bond
I was finally able to make...
I want to protect
his bond with you,
the one he's desperately trying to
draw closer to.
Bond...
You interrupted my sleep
for something like that...?
What was that?!
It's Sai's Chakra.
That way, right?
What was that...?
Sasuke, huh...?
That kid wakes up in
a bad mood, you see...
Impressive...
To think he'd break free
from my Jutsu by force...
I found him!
Sakura!
You!
What're you really after?!
How many times do you have
to betray us until you're satisfied...?
Sakura, huh?
That voice...
Sa...su...ke...
Sasuke...
Naruto, huh...?
So even you were here, huh?
Then is Kakashi also with you?
Sorry, it's not Kakashi...
I'm his substitute.
Team Kakashi will now be taking you
back to the Leaf.
Team Kakashi, huh?
Sai! I knew it!
So he's my replacement, huh...?
Some soft one has once again
joined up.
He said he wanted to protect
the bond...
between Naruto and me, but...
Sai... I thought your mission
was to kill Sasuke.
My classified mission was indeed
the assassination of Sasuke...
But I've had enough of orders...
I now want to act on
my own beliefs.
I think Naruto will get me
to remember...
my past emotions.
I kind of get the feeling...
it's something
very important to me.
I don't know you very well.
But there must be some kind
of reason why Naruto and Sakura...
have pursued you so desperately.
They don't want to sever
their bonds with you...
They're giving it their all
to secure those bonds.
I still don't understand it
all that clearly...
But Sasuke...
you should understand.
Yeah... I did understand.
That's why I severed the bonds.
Knock it off!
That's just what I want!
Why?
I haven't narrowed the gap at all
since back then.
What's up with this difference?
You're weak.
You're weak...
because you don't have enough...
hatred.
I have different bonds...
Bonds of hatred...
with my older brother.