Rikka Park Meeting Center - Hotel Elnath
Le Wolfe Black Academy
Student Council President: Dirk Eberweine
Allekant Academy
Student Council President: Shuma Sakon
Jie Long 7th Academy
Student Council President: Fan Shinlu
Garrardworth Academy
Student Council President: Ernest Fairclough
Welcome, Ms. Enfield.
As always, you're right on time.
Seidoukan Academy
Student Council President: Claudia Enfield
Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm happy to see you all looking so well.
All right, since we're all here,
why don't we get started?
Oh, but...
Oh, she's in the middle of
her European tour.
How fitting for a world-famous diva!
Seems like there's a lot on her plate.
Not that it makes any difference whether
she's around or not, a little brat like that!
I'd appreciate it if you could refrain from
insulting reps from other schools,
Overlord of the Double Swords.
How many times has that bitch
from Queenvale been absent now?
I just told you not to talk like that.
Interesting.
Want to take me on, Lord Holy Knight?
Look at your little kiddie toy.
I see you're as tight
as ever, little punks.
But you'd better stop that
childish horseplay now.
Otherwise, I'll start itching
to join the fray myself.
I suppose there's no defying
the princess's mediation efforts.
By the way, Claudia...
What is it?
I'm hearing rumors that Seidoukan and Allekant
agreed to co-develop a new type of Lux.
So what's up with that?
Oh, my, news does travel fast.
It's true that we'll be sending
our engineers to Allekant.
You vixen!
Secret deals between schools are
prohibited under the Stella Charter.
In the first place, the technological difference between
Seidoukan and Allekant is like night and day.
Yes, it's like saying, "Please help yourselves
to as much of our technology as you like."
Are you sure you're
okay with that, Allekant?
Uh, actually, all I did was
give the go-ahead.
So I don't know any of the details.
There seems to be some
kind of misunderstanding.
This isn't a secret deal,
but rather an official collaboration between
Seidoukan Academy and Allekant Academy.
The details will be made public eventually.
So you're saying this deal
was made on equal terms?
Of course.
In return for the use of
Allekant's facilities,
we will be assuming 70% of
the R&D fees, after all.
Right, speaking of Seidoukan,
they had some internal strife the other day,
and had to mobilize the Shadow Stars.
Now, could that have
anything to do with...
Whatever are you talking about?
You scheming bitch!
All right, I think that's
enough of this topic.
Then let's wait for
the official announcement.
All right, once again,
about today's agenda...
Uh, excuse me...
Actually, uh...
I know this is sudden,
but there's something I'd like to
add to today's discussion.
What? Now you're joining the fray?
Aha, what could that be?
Uh, what I'd like to propose to you all
is the handling of artificial intelligence
in Asterisk, as well as during the Festas.
Lightning Blade Speed
If I don't hurry,
Julis is going to kill me!
Are you all right?
Yes... I'm fine.
Uh... Sorry about that.
I wasn't paying attention.
N-No, I'm the one
who should be apologizing.
I think there's something
stuck in your hair.
Where? Where?
Okay, hold still.
Um... Thank you very much.
Uh...
Kirin!
What are you up to over there?!
Y-Yes, sir! I'm sorry!
S-See you later!
Uh... right.
Julis?
Burst into bloom...
LIVINGSTON DAISY
Livingston Daisy!
Go!
Now that was a nonchalantly
ridiculous stunt.
But how do you plan
to evade my next attack?
Then how about something like this?
Come out... Gloriosa!
GLORIOSA
Amagiri Shinmei Style, Second Sword!
Ten Linked Thistles!
TEN LINKED THISTLES
I thought I had you today for sure.
No, to tell you the truth,
that last one was a close call.
You've got a whole
arsenal of moves, huh?
M-Mmm. I suppose so.
So how are you feeling physically?
Yeah, well, I think I'm
good for up to 3 minutes.
I see.
Assuming you can go
full blast for that long,
I'm sure we can find a way
to handle anyone at my level.
But there can't be that many
students more powerful than you.
I'm happy for that
vote of confidence from you,
but there must be more than
you can count on both hands and feet.
That many?
Garrardworth's student council president is such
an able swordsman, he's known as the Holy Knight.
His counterpart at Jie Long is said
to be a beast of epic proportions.
Although neither of them are
old enough to take part in the Festas.
Oh, right, there's another famous
contestant that I've heard of.
The one who became the second person
in history to win Lindbels Festas last year.
I think it was Le Wolfe's...
Elenshquigall Ophélia.
Oh, yeah, that's the one!
Julis?
Oh... Sorry.
Now, then. Despite all that,
we do have one thing in our favor.
And that's the fact that your
skills aren't yet well-known.
The fact that you're wielding
the Ser Veresta may be public knowledge,
but knowing this sword's power
still won't do anyone any good.
It would be even more ideal
if you could use it without unsealing it.
Yeah...
But unless I'm at full power, this thing
won't acknowledge me as its wielder.
At any rate, we only have one month
left before the Phoenix Festa.
Don't go tipping your hand
in any useless duels!
Roger that.
No fair!
Riessfeld, you're totally
monopolizing Ayato.
I know you've been shutting yourself
into a room alone with Ayato after school,
indulging in unspeakable acts...
I've got you dead to rights!
Don't slander me!
We've been training for
the Phoenix Festa, that's all!
Lester. I see you're out of the hospital.
Well, yeah.
So what brings you here today?
And with Saya, of all people?
I just picked up this
little squirt on the way.
Who are you calling a little squirt?!
Well, but I do owe you
big time. Thanks.
Well, uh, about that incident with Silas...
There's no denying that you saved me.
So... you know...
A-Anyway, you did me a solid! That's it!
Uh, sure!
Oh, so you're all here!
Ah, so this is the Seidoukan
training room, eh?
Wow, it's gorgeous!
Don't get too carried away, Ernesta.
Allow me to introduce you all.
This is Camilla Pareto of
Allekant Academy.
And this is Ernesta Kuhne.
Of Allekant?
Seidoukan and Allekant are about to embark
on a joint venture, developing a new type of Lux.
And so they're here today
to sign the contract.
Hello.
So that's what this is about?
What are you talking about?
In return for not charging Allekant
with the Silas incident,
they must have secured their
technological collaboration.
My, what are you talking about?
Well, whatever. But...
Why did you bring those two here?
Right, because...
Oh, yes, because I said
I wanted to see for myself!
Honestly, I just had to
see him with my own two eyes!
The young swordsman who shredded
every one of my little puppets!
Heh, heh!
You wretch!
Step away from Ayato this minute!
Hmm, hmm... I see, I see...
Yes! Not bad at all!
I think I like you!
Uh, look...
But things won't work out
so well for you next time.
What did you just...
What do you think you're doing?!
Thieving cat.
Must be destroyed!
So scary! So scary!
It was just a little greeting, that's all!
I'm so sorry.
What you just saw was
Ernesta's true nature.
I apologize on her behalf.
Now this is quite unique.
Three Manadites,
forcefully linked together.
It's a design concept that
I haven't seen in ages.
Correct. How did you know?
Because that's what I specialize in.
Still, you can't really call it practical.
This was dismissed over ten years ago
as a half-baked technology.
You're forced to deploy
the Météo Arts non-stop
to boost Lux output by pouring
Prana into the Manadites.
The Météo Arts, huh?
Therefore, an interval is
needed between each attack.
But it doesn't look like
that flaw's been rectified.
That's true.
Even so, I won't let you get away
with insulting my father's gun.
I demand that you take that back!
Oh, so are you Dr. Sasamiya's
daughter, then?
What if I am?
Then I can't retract my
statement, all the more.
Because of Dr. Sasamiya's
renegade tendencies,
he was cast out of Allekant,
as well as our faction, Ferrovius.
As the leader of the latter, I cannot
acknowledge his perverse notions.
Now, then, my guests.
Why don't we get back to business?
Good idea. Pardon me.
Hold up. I insist that
you retract your statement!
Well, but Camilla can be
stubborn, you know?
Well, if you're really determined,
your only hope would be to force her.
You mean I should duel her?
Please, no way would she
accept a challenge!
But see, we'll be taking part in
the upcoming Phoenix Festa, you know?
Come on, Ernesta.
Coming!
All right, see you later, guys!
Ayato...
What's up?
I'm going to fight in the Phoenix Festa,
too. I've made up my mind.
But it's a tag team
tournament, you know.
Who are you gonna team up with?
With you, of course.
Don't be ridiculous!
This guy is my partner!
No monopolies.
I'm the one who asked him first!
Ouch ouch ouch! Come on, you two!
Great. Just great.
Oh, boy, now that was a rare
sight, seeing you like that.
You know, baiting that
blue-haired girl and all...
I wasn't really baiting her.
That was just my frank opinion.
Anyway, what do you think of him?
I have to say I'd like
just a little more data.
Our prez did a good job,
helping us prepare for the Festa.
Now the only thing
we have to worry about is him.
Are you planning
another one of your stunts?
Well, you know me, I'll do anything!
In order to realize my dream, that is...
Allekant is divided into two groups.
The research class that develops Luxes,
and the practical skills class
that fights with them in the Festas.
And the research class is
the one with more clout.
Yeah?
Not only that, but the research
class itself has its cliques.
FERROVIUS
TENORIO      PYGMALION
METHUSELAH       SONNET
ALLEKANT RESEARCH CLASS
And they're always fighting over R&D facilities
and the most promising students.
And right now, Ferrovius has
the most clout of all.
FERROVIUS
I see.
I already told you, that's
not your concern, Kirin!
B-But, Uncle...
I don't recall ever giving you
permission to talk back, either!
That's enough!
Who the hell are you?
I don't know what this is about, but
I don't approve of raising a hand to a girl.
I was only disciplining her as her uncle.
Outsiders should
stay out of family matters!
Uncle?
I'm Koichiro Toudou.
Kirin Toudou here is my niece.
Now you know, so
get out of my way. Anyway...
You Genestella kids are pretty much immune
to anything of this level, aren't you?
That doesn't mean
that we don't feel pain.
What's your name?
Ayato Amagiri.
Amagiri...
A rank-and-filer who isn't even
listed in the Named Cults, eh?
Fine!
If you have a problem with
my way of doing things,
then tell me what you want me to do.
I'm telling you that
I'll comply. Just speak up.
Don't ever get violent with her again.
Can you promise me that?
Sure, I can do that.
Only if you win a duel, that is.
Duel?
Your opponent is... her.
Uncle! I...
Kirin!
You're not actually
defying me, are you?!
No... Of course not.
Fine, then.
If you defeat that Ser Veresta,
it'll pad your resume further.
I'm so sorry.
I... I, Kirin Toudou...
challenge you,
Amagiri-senpai, to a duel.
N-No, wait, why should
I have to fight you?
Please, Senpai. If you decline,
then that'll be the end of it.
And if I do, what'll happen to you?
What's going to happen to you?
I...
I don't care what happens to me.
Because there's nothing
I can do about it.
In that case, I don't think I can decline.
You're very kind, Amagiri-senpai.
Then I have no choice.
I can't afford to lose this duel, either.
I accept your challenge.
Kirin, don't parry that Ogre Lux of his!
He'll slice right through your sword!
Here I come!
Amagiri-senpai, you're very powerful.
You surprised me.
Well, I could say the same of you.
I told him not to get into
any meaningless duels!
That idiot!
The pressure's on Ayato?
Well, well, if it isn't Her Highness.
Yabuki?
Hey, isn't this a spectacle?
That Amagiri's totally been
hiding his true skills from us!
But it doesn't look good for him.
Well, of course not.
He's up against the notorious
Lightning Blade Speed, right?
Still, looks like Amagiri's still not
going all-out with the Ser Veresta.
Toudou's been dodging every blow
without once receiving an attack.
So he can actually read
the defense and offense patterns?
Never mind that! How long
has this duel been going on?!
Maybe 4, 5 minutes, I guess?
Amazing... I never thought
it would be like this.
Dammit, I'm out of time...
You can read her sword skills.
Wait till the last second
to dodge and come out swinging!
He's panicking? But why?
I'll dodge this one, too!
End of duel!
Winner, Kirin Toudou!
The ones that are used to fighting
elsewhere always end up doing that!
It's over, huh? Let's go.
Yes, sir!
Um... I'm really sorry!
Hey...
We're getting out of here right now.
You don't have all that
much time before your limit's up.
Uh, right.
You have some explaining to do later.
What possible reason could you have
for dueling the student
who's ranked #1 at our school?
That girl's...
our...
Rank #1?
Ayato... Oh, to think
that my Ayato actually lost!
You have to hand it to Seidoukan's
Rank #1, Ms. Kirin Toudou!
Apparently, she's not called
Lightning Blade Speed for nothing.
Episode 6 - The True Face of the Girl
Oh, but I haven't quite
gone down in defeat myself.