Turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy,
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is when you get it or lose it
Turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Kuchiyose no Jutsu!
This time, let there be a toad...
What is a toad?!
How do I tell if something is a toad?!
Life or death?!
Mastering the move is life threatening!
Life or Death?! Mastering the move is life threatening!
Hey!
Expect something from me, damn it!
Fell again?
It is understandable, though.
He trained continuously for three weeks straight on guts alone.
Hokage-sama.
Anko?
I am sorry.
I...
You regret coming back alive from the Forest of Death?
It is not important.
You and Orochimaru are not related anymore.
There are no ninja in Konoha that can fight him equally.
Even I...
...cannot.
If the Fourth was alive right now...
Don't say that.
He saved this village and died already.
And that happened 13 years ago.
He is not here anymore.
We must do something with our own powers.
Yes!
I am going to get some fresh air.
Do not blame yourself.
Hey! Wake up!
What?
You have zero talent.
Ero-sennin!
You trained for three weeks, and you're still at this level.
It might be useless for you to continue.
That's not true! I'm working hard, even if it doesn't seem like it!
I know that.
But, if you want to master the Kuchiyose no Jutsu,
you need to train harder... as if your life depended on it.
That's what I'm doing!
I mold chakra everyday as if my life depended on it!
If you have time to complain, why don't you tell me a tip or two on how to do it!
A tip?
The secret is to...
What? You're going to tell me?
Put your life on the line.
Life?
I'm not kidding here, will you still do it?
Of course!
I always put my life on the line!
I see.
Then follow me.
What are we going to do here?
Don't tell me that you're going to peek again.
That might be nice but, for today, we're going to bathe.
We need to cleanse our bodies first.
He's acting weird...
This is a nice bath.
Very nice.
Paradise.
Hey, Ero-sennin.
Toad hermit.
I don't care.
What do taking a bath and the Kuchiyose no Jutsu have to do with each other?
Hey.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What now?
Hey, Naruto.
Do you have something you want to eat?
Time to eat!
It's good!
If the training consists of this, I can do it every day.
Eat up.
Since this is your last...
What?
Anyway, eat up. Just keep eating.
Eat until you have no regrets.
I'm not sure what the point is, but I just have to eat, right?
Okay.
Another, please! Miso ramen.
All right!
Another!
Miso barbecue pork.
All right!
I'm full.
Thanks, Ero-sennin.
What?!
Thank you.
It's completely empty...
Hey, are you full now?
That was cruel, Ero-sennin!
I thought you were going to treat me!
Idiot. When did I say I would treat you.
You call yourself an adult?! Damn it!
By the way, Naruto, do you have a girl you like?
What?
I'm asking if you have a woman you love.
Well, there might be one that I might like...
She might be Sakura-chan...
So you have one?
Actually, it is Sakura-chan.
Okay.
Go hug that girl right now, then.
What??!
Is that part of the training?
Something like that.
All right! Then I'll go right away.
But if I do that, Sakura-chan might...
No! This is training.
If I don't do it, I can't become stronger!
But if I do that, Sakura-chan might not talk to me for a while.
No! I have to do this to master the Kuchiyose no Jutsu!
But Sakura-chan might...
No! But...
Just go!
What do you want?
Well, um...
I'm not going to lend you any money.
I'm pretty stingy, you know.
Well, that's not it...
If I ask her to let me hug her for training, she'll punch me for sure.
If there's nothing to do, I'm leaving.
Wait!
This is my chance!
Sakura-chan, I'm sorry!
What was that for?!
All right, damn it!
O-Ouch...
That is part of one's springtime of life, as well.
Hey.
Is a toad really going to come out by doing these things?
Yes, I am positive of it.
Really?
Did you do everything you wanted to?
You have nothing else to do?
What are you...
Extracting great chakra when it is needed and using it...
Mastering control of that is indeed hard.
And it is true that his body is too small a container to accept the chakra of the Kyuubi.
Naruto's body most likely tries to avoid stress by rejecting the Kyuubi's chakra.
If danger and intense emotions are the keys to call upon the Kyuubi's chakra...
I'll have to make him learn how to use those keys with his body.
Don't take it personally, Fourth.
Huh?
Where am I?
Stand up!
What?
The training ends here.
Wait, I didn't learn anything!
Naruto!
Go die now.
Die?
Try to extract the powerful chakra withing you from the fear of death.
And experience that with your body, and grasp the trick to do it.
If you don't want to die, do something on your own!
Now...
Let's see if the power given to you was really meant to protect you...
This will be interesting.
I have to grab onto one of these...
Or I'll die!
Now!
That's not possible.
The rock surfaces here are slippery because of the waterfall.
On top of that, at the speed you're falling, you cannot cling onto a rock with your current chakra control abilities.
Naruto, all you can do now is to rely on the Kyuubi's chakra.
Open the key.
From your side, now.
At this rate... At this rate...
I'm going to die!
I'm going to die...
Today, we're going to have history class outside.
As you know, these faces on this rock represent the former Hokages.
Starting form the left, the First...
The Second...
The Third...
And the Fourth...
The face looks way different from the current old geezer.
Especially the hairline.
Iruka-sensei!
Who's the Fifth?
One hasn't been decided on yet...
But I might become it!
You mix in jokes from time to time to have a fun class, eh, Iruka?
H-Hokage-sama!
It's the Third!
Geezer!
Why did you come here?
I felt like looking at the faces on the rock, as well.
You came at a good time.
Please, come here.
Sure.
He is the third person himself on that rock.
The Third Hokage.
The Third has been said to be the strongest amongst the Hokages,
and was a genius who was known as The Professor.
What?
Iruka.
Do no speak in past tense.
I am sorry.
Are you really strong?
Doesn't seem like it.
That's true.
Hey!
To receive the name of Hokage means that you are the strongest person in this village!
Okay! I'll become the Fifth Hokage, then!
It'll mean that I'm strong and cool, right?
You can't with your current grades.
Looks like I can expect something out of you.
Unlike me, you are all very young.
And someone here might receive the title of Hokage one day.
You live only once.
You do not have to go the hard way.
You can live how you want, and die as you want.
But...
Do not forget to protect those important to you, no matter what path you choose.
Those important to you?
Those you accept, believe, and love from your heart.
Do you have people like that?
Yes.
Dad and mom.
And, although I hate him a little, my older brother.
Also, my dog Gonta.
I would say, my friends.
Me, too!
Then Hokage-sama, do you have people like that, too?
Yes, of course.
Really? Who? Who?
My grandson there, Konohamaru, and...
Everyone in this village.
Just like how they were to you.
This feeling...
It's that chakra.
What's this...?
He's huge...
What is it?
Brat, come closer.
I want to devour you, but this gate will not open.
It is a detestable seal.
You're...
Kyuubi.
I see... So the red chakra was his.
You came to me this time.
Why did you come here?
Hey, you dumb fox!
Since you're staying in my body, give me your chakra as rent!
You're saying that if you die, I'm going to die as well?
You have guts, blackmailing me like that.
Very well.
It's a reward for coming all the way here. I'll give it to you!
This is the feeling.
Kuchiyose no Jutsu!
Well done.
Where the hell am I?!
One! First, Tyson jumps and slamdunks
Two! He kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "l love you"
Three! Masala masters Yoga but hates curry
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter. Ole!
All over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Fight! Fight! Fight!
One! Bodimahattaya-san devotes his time for digging black ships
Two! Peking Duck, Action Scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
Three! Popo loves to polish his Coteka
Four! Japanese people, now lend me you hand!
All over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Fight! Fight! Fight!