[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,MS UI Gothic,90,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,5,0,1,2,2,1,10,10,10,0
//
Style: Rubi,MS UI Gothic,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,1,10,10,10,0
//

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.93,0:00:56.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}北見との勝負に挑んだカイジは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.93,0:00:56.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}土壇場で生き残る\N
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.23,0:01:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そして星３つを奪取\N
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.23,0:01:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}さらに敗れた北見たちの内輪もめ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:06.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}それを見たカイジは彼らの持つ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:06.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}30枚のパーの買い占めに動く\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.32,0:01:17.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}１人100万で足りるはずだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.32,0:01:17.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}はい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.22,0:01:19.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}場が煮詰まった終局\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.59,0:01:23.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}グーとパー２種類のカードを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.59,0:01:23.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}30枚買い占めていれば\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.46,0:01:27.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}電光掲示板の残りのカードは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.46,0:01:27.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}こうなる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.30,0:01:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}この場合 実際にフロア内で\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.30,0:01:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}動いているカードは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジたちだけが唯一 真実の\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}情報を手にすることができる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.97,0:01:40.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}さらにカードが減っていくと\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.34,0:01:43.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}より決定的な情報を\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.34,0:01:43.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}得ることができる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.81,0:01:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}例えばグーが買い占めた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.81,0:01:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードだけになれば\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.75,0:01:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}残りはパーとチョキ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.75,0:01:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}チョキで必勝できる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:56.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}同様にパーが消えてゼロになれば\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.39,0:02:00.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}残りはグーとチョキ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.39,0:02:00.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}これもグーで必勝\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.26,0:02:03.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}引き分けはあっても\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.26,0:02:03.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}負けることはない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.06,0:02:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}これがカイジの生き残り戦略\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.60,0:02:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}グー パー ダブル買い占め\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.60,0:02:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そして…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.91,0:02:14.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}パー20枚を手に入れる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.61,0:02:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}びっくりした　拍子抜けするほど\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.61,0:02:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あっさりっすよ カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.88,0:02:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}じゃあ俺は 今や裸の王様となった\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.88,0:02:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}小悪党との交渉といくか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.29,0:02:34.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何の用だ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.29,0:02:34.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ちょっと邪魔するぜ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.86,0:02:37.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}何なんだよ　隣になんか座るな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.77,0:02:41.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}向こうへ行け\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.77,0:02:41.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}おいおい 北見\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.27,0:02:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺はお前を救いに来たメシア\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.27,0:02:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}救世主なんだぜ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.91,0:02:49.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.91,0:02:49.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ウソじゃない　見な\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.71,0:02:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あ あいつら… 何で俺を置いて\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.12,0:02:59.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}100万で\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.12,0:02:59.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あっさり転んでくれたよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.49,0:03:03.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カネをもらってあがれるんだから\N
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.49,0:03:03.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}悪くねえ話だと思ったんだろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.89,0:03:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}まあ 無理もない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.89,0:03:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}お前らは元々 信頼関係なんかない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.60,0:03:12.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}100パーセント\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.60,0:03:12.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}利害だけの仲だからな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.13,0:03:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}明らかな利が他に生じれば\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.13,0:03:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}人の心はそっちへ流れる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.44,0:03:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}その機会を\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.44,0:03:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺が与えてやったのさ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.28,0:03:25.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}どうする 北見\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.28,0:03:25.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}パートナーを失ったお前は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}残りのカードを引き分けで\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}処理するわけにはいかなくなった\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.25,0:03:33.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}その手に大量に抱えている\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.25,0:03:33.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}10以上あるパーで\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.19,0:03:36.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}運否天賦 10戦以上\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.19,0:03:36.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}戦わざるをえない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.16,0:03:39.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}売れってことか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.16,0:03:39.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}連中と同じように\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.06,0:03:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}はした金で手持ちのパーを…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.06,0:03:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}おいおい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.80,0:03:48.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何 寝ぼけてんだよ　お前は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.80,0:03:48.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あの２人とは状況が違う\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.07,0:03:51.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺にカネを払い\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.07,0:03:51.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}引き取ってもらうんだよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.47,0:03:54.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}冗談じゃない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.47,0:03:54.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}奴らがいなくたって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.18,0:03:57.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}星足らずでカードが欲しい奴らが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.18,0:03:57.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}まだたくさんいる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.55,0:03:59.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そいつらに\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.55,0:03:59.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}いくらでも譲渡できるさ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.98,0:04:03.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残念だがそれは無理だ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.39,0:04:07.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺がそうはさせない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.39,0:04:07.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}お前のカードがほとんどパーだと\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.22,0:04:09.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺が公言して回る\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.16,0:04:13.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}この終盤 パーだと知れた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.16,0:04:13.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードを誰がもらう？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.03,0:04:16.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}貴様 ふざけるな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.06,0:04:18.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そんなことしたら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.06,0:04:18.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺だって言ってやる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.83,0:04:21.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}お前らだって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.83,0:04:21.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ほとんどグーじゃねえか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.74,0:04:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}分かってねえな 北見\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:29.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺たちは引き分けで処理できる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:29.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードを譲る必要なんかない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.14,0:04:34.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}それに他のカードも何枚かある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.14,0:04:34.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}問題は勝負だけさ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.55,0:04:39.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}しかし お前は残りのカードが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.55,0:04:39.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}パーと知られたら致命傷\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.49,0:04:44.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}しょせん２戦目はごまかせても\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.49,0:04:44.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そのあとが厳しい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.33,0:04:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}10枚以上あるパーの現実は重い\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.16,0:04:51.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}それで星３つ維持できたら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.16,0:04:51.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}まさに奇跡\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.70,0:04:54.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そうは思わねえか？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.17,0:04:59.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}200で手を打ってやる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.17,0:04:59.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}奴らの買収に使った額だ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.78,0:05:06.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}こうして\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.78,0:05:06.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}グー パー頂上決戦は決着\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.38,0:05:08.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.38,0:05:08.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}パー買い占め派のカードを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.88,0:05:13.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}すべて もらい受けた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.88,0:05:13.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}その数 30枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.22,0:05:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}これでカイジらのカードは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.16,0:05:22.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}グー30 チョキ５ パー34\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.16,0:05:22.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}計69枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.06,0:05:27.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}この時 電光掲示板の示す\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.06,0:05:27.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードの総数は135\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.30,0:05:30.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジらは全体の\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.30,0:05:30.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}50パーセントを超えるカードを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.84,0:05:37.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}買い占めたことになる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.84,0:05:37.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}まさに圧倒的占拠率\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.15,0:05:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}打つべき手は打った\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.15,0:05:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あとは祈るだけだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.48,0:05:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺たちにとって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.48,0:05:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}理想的状況が出現することをな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.25,0:05:48.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}動き出すまで まだ時間がある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.86,0:05:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}それまでは別々\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.86,0:05:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}固まらないほうがいい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.36,0:05:54.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}必要以上に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.36,0:05:54.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}怪しまれたくないからな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.86,0:05:56.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}はい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.24,0:06:03.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}あと30分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.24,0:06:03.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}それで すべてが決する\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.97,0:06:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}イカサマだ！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.97,0:06:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}今 確かに聞こえたんだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.68,0:06:09.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}この中から合図を送る音が\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.61,0:06:13.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}言いがかりはよせ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.61,0:06:13.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星を… 星を返せ！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.28,0:06:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}うるせえ！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.92,0:06:19.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}返せったら！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.33,0:06:29.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あの男は確か…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.26,0:06:33.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}任せとけ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.26,0:06:33.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺の言うとおりにすればいい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.13,0:06:35.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}言うなら必勝法\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.67,0:06:39.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}あの時の男\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.67,0:06:39.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ってことは ひょっとすると\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.37,0:06:43.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}今 騒いでいたイカサマ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.37,0:06:43.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}本当にあったかもしれない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.95,0:06:46.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}もし落ちる先が\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.95,0:06:46.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あの鏡の裏側にある部屋で\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.85,0:06:50.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あの鏡がマジックミラーだったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.52,0:06:55.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}星１つのおっさんを説得して\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.52,0:06:55.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}別室に送り込んで合図をもらう\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.82,0:06:59.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}その見返りとして\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.82,0:06:59.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}最後の星売買の時に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.09,0:07:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}星３つを与え 落ちてくれた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.09,0:07:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}おっさんを救い上げる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.60,0:07:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}あり得ないことじゃない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.60,0:07:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}奴がリピーターなら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.80,0:07:11.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}やるやんか カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.54,0:07:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}船井！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.54,0:07:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}この男 船井\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.41,0:07:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}限定ジャンケンのしょっぱな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.41,0:07:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジをまんまと だまし\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.68,0:07:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星２つを奪取\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.08,0:07:24.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}現在 この窮地にカイジを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.08,0:07:24.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}追い込むきっかけとなった張本人\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.39,0:07:29.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}何の用だ 船井\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.99,0:07:33.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}ま そうツンツンせんと\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.99,0:07:33.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}見てみ 奴らを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.33,0:07:39.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}ああいう どっちつかずの\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.33,0:07:39.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}連中が出てくると\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.23,0:07:42.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}いよいよ終盤 最終局面\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.64,0:07:46.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}奴ら 星１つ２つで\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.64,0:07:46.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードなしって連中や\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.98,0:07:50.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}さっき黒服たちが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.98,0:07:50.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}連中に言うて回ったんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.61,0:07:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}このゲームの終了時に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.61,0:07:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星の売買タイムがある言うてな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.28,0:07:58.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}となったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.28,0:07:58.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}命をかけて勝負するより\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.29,0:08:02.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カネで星を買うほうを選ぶ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.29,0:08:02.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ここまで場が煮詰まると\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.66,0:08:05.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}新たにカードを仕入れても\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.66,0:08:05.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}勝負はしとうない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.69,0:08:10.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}買うたカードの情報が\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.69,0:08:10.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}第三者に流れたら終わりやからな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.97,0:08:16.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}せやけど実はこの状況こそ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.97,0:08:16.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}船側にとって好都合 思うツボ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.57,0:08:19.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そもそも売買で\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.57,0:08:19.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星を３つにするっちゅうことは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.47,0:08:21.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}最初に船から借りたカネを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.54,0:08:24.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}その星に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.54,0:08:24.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}注ぎ込むっちゅうことやから\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.41,0:08:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}当然 新たな借金を生む\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.08,0:08:32.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}シャバの借金がチャラになっても\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.08,0:08:32.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}借金苦の状況は変わらへん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.29,0:08:37.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジさん　あんた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.29,0:08:37.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}買い占めてるやろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.86,0:08:41.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何をバカな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.86,0:08:41.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}いいや 隠さんでもええ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.13,0:08:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そのこと自体 俺はどうでもええ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.13,0:08:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺はただカードが欲しいだけや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.50,0:08:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}終盤からマークしとる獲物が\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.50,0:08:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}数人おる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.44,0:08:53.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}最後の１枚 何を持ってるかも\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.44,0:08:53.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}分かっとる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.91,0:08:57.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}それに勝つカードをカイジさんが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.91,0:08:57.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}回してくれればええ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.35,0:09:02.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そうすれば４勝 いや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.35,0:09:02.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あと５勝はいける\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.62,0:09:05.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}星は前渡しや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.62,0:09:05.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}え？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.59,0:09:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}他の２人に見つからんように\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.59,0:09:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}さっさとポケットにしまっとき\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.96,0:09:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}この星でカイジさんは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.96,0:09:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}100パーセント救われる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.33,0:09:18.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}ええか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.33,0:09:18.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジさんがやろうとしとる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.13,0:09:21.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}最後に星を拾う戦略は絶対やない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.94,0:09:24.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}相手が勝負してくれんかったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.94,0:09:24.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}それまでや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.51,0:09:27.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}それより今 確実な道がここにある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.28,0:09:29.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}この星や\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.21,0:09:31.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}しかし安藤や古畑はどうなる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.78,0:09:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}切りゃええんとちゃうの\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.78,0:09:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そういうクズは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.75,0:09:38.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}バカなことを言うな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.75,0:09:38.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}またまた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.62,0:09:42.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そういう善人ぶった\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.62,0:09:42.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}芝居はやめろや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.19,0:09:45.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}第一 カイジさんは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.19,0:09:45.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}１千万 借りたんやから\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.13,0:09:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}いくらなんでもまだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.13,0:09:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}500や600 持っとるやろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.96,0:09:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}最後の売買で カイジさんだけ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.96,0:09:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}救われるっちゅうことやないの\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.30,0:09:56.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}つまり最終的にはカイジさんは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.17,0:10:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}連中を\N
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.17,0:10:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}見捨てるつもりっちゅうことや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.04,0:10:03.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}気取るのはやめようや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.04,0:10:03.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}今 カイジさんが欲してるのは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.91,0:10:07.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}これ　星や　なあ？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.32,0:10:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}よせ！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.22,0:10:16.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}拾うな！俺の星や\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.22,0:10:16.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺の星やぞ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.89,0:10:20.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}クソッ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.96,0:10:25.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}せっかく垂れた救いの糸を\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.96,0:10:25.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}自ら切るんか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.47,0:10:29.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}救えぬ偽善者\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.47,0:10:29.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}せいぜい後悔せえや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.85,0:10:51.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}どうしたんすか？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.85,0:10:51.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}何か もめてたけど\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:53.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}何でもねえ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.83,0:11:00.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}安藤　古畑\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.73,0:11:04.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}裏切るなよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.73,0:11:04.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}はあ？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.67,0:11:07.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}初戦に勝って\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.67,0:11:07.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星３つになったからって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.51,0:11:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}勝手にカードを売ったり\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.51,0:11:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}おいしそうなこと吹きかける奴に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.04,0:11:13.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}フラフラついていったり\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.04,0:11:13.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そんなことはするなよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.95,0:11:16.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}するわけないっすよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.95,0:11:16.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そうっすよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.45,0:11:26.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}200万ずつ渡しておく\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.66,0:11:30.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}これで俺だけ星を勝って\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.66,0:11:30.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}上へってわけにはいかなくなった\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.66,0:11:34.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}つまり これで条件は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.66,0:11:34.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}みんな一緒ってわけだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.27,0:11:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}いいんすか？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.20,0:11:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}今は互いに\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.20,0:11:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}半端な気持ちは命取りになる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.84,0:11:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺はお前らを信じる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.84,0:11:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}お前らも俺を信じろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.28,0:11:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カ カイジさん…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.48,0:11:51.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}こんな所で朽ちてたまるか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.48,0:11:51.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あと星３つ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.42,0:11:54.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺たちは必ずたどり着く\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.42,0:11:54.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}たどり着いてみせる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.56,0:12:02.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}最初 103名で始まった\N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.56,0:12:02.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}この限定ジャンケン\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.93,0:12:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}44人は無事 ２階へ上がり\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.93,0:12:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}18人は別室行き\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.20,0:12:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}今現在フロアにいるのは41名\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.24,0:12:16.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}このうち22名は勝負後の\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.24,0:12:16.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星売買に望みを託す者たち\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.31,0:12:21.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}残るは16人　この16人から\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.31,0:12:21.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星を奪うしかない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.71,0:12:23.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星を奪うしか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.62,0:12:28.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.62,0:12:28.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}分かってる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.49,0:12:36.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジたちに風\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.49,0:12:36.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}救いの風が吹き始めていた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.03,0:12:38.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}電光掲示板はこうだが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.03,0:12:38.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}実際は…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.70,0:12:43.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.70,0:12:48.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}残り３枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.70,0:12:48.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}パーが残り３枚になったら動く\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.44,0:12:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}いいな？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.44,0:12:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}はい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.94,0:12:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}実際フロアにあるパーは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.94,0:12:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}今 ５枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.85,0:13:02.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そしてパーは４枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.13,0:13:13.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}チャンス到来　残り23分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.13,0:13:13.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}フロアにあるパーは３枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.97,0:13:18.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}行こう　決着の時が来た\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.97,0:13:18.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.17,0:13:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}大丈夫 勝てる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.17,0:13:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}流れも利も 今 俺たちにある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.68,0:13:29.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}負けるもんか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.68,0:13:29.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}だが しかし\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.61,0:13:34.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}フロアは想像を超えた異常事態\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.61,0:13:34.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}閉塞状況に入っていた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.95,0:13:38.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}打つ手なし　疑念疑惑の終着駅\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.13,0:13:45.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}戦えば勝てる　だが…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.70,0:13:47.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}それができない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.63,0:13:50.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}待ってくれ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.30,0:13:53.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}戦えない 相手にもされない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.07,0:13:55.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}それは安藤 古畑も変わらない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.97,0:14:00.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}みんな身を固くして固持\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.71,0:14:02.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カ カイジさん！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.65,0:14:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}と この時 場は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.65,0:14:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジらを拒否するように\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.62,0:14:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}急速に閉塞 こう着化\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.25,0:14:13.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何か 全然みんな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.25,0:14:13.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}勝負してくれないんすよ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.79,0:14:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺も\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.79,0:14:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}買い占めがバレたんすかね\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.30,0:14:19.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そんなんじゃねえ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.17,0:14:28.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.17,0:14:28.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}恐らく 不信感\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.24,0:14:32.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}え？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.24,0:14:32.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ぬぐえない疑念 疑惑\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.11,0:14:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}人を疑う心がここにきて\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.11,0:14:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}みんなの動きを止めたんだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}勝負できないのは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺たちだけじゃねえ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.12,0:14:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}他の連中も成り立ってねえ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.76,0:14:46.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ここに至るまでの過程で\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.69,0:14:50.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}だましたり だまされたりするのを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.69,0:14:50.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}目の当たりにしてきたからな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.06,0:14:53.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}声をかけてくる奴なんて\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.06,0:14:53.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}信用できねえのさ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.77,0:14:58.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}途中でカードを購入した連中は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.77,0:14:58.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}もう疑心暗鬼\N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.10,0:15:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}その情報が売られ売られて\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.04,0:15:02.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}目の前の敵に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.04,0:15:02.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}流れてるかもしれないからな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.87,0:15:06.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}それに購入していない奴でも\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.87,0:15:06.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}直前の戦いを３戦ほど\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.78,0:15:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}チェックされてるかもしれないと\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.78,0:15:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}考えると これはこれで戦えない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.68,0:15:14.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ここは待つしかない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.52,0:15:17.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}連中だってカードを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.52,0:15:17.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残したままじゃ終われない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.69,0:15:20.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}いつかは戦わなきゃならない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.19,0:15:22.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}その決断の時を\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.19,0:15:22.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}はあ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.40,0:15:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残り19分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.97,0:15:33.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残り18分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.77,0:15:38.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}クソ…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.71,0:15:41.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残り17分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.65,0:15:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジさん！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.48,0:15:47.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}待つしかない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.82,0:15:50.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残り16分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.42,0:15:54.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}もう限界っす！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.42,0:15:54.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}行きましょう カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.03,0:15:57.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}よせ　行ったからって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.03,0:15:57.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}誰も勝負してくれないぞ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.03,0:15:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}しかし ただこうしていても\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.76,0:16:01.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}待つんだ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.76,0:16:01.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}でも…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.83,0:16:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}今 動いたらアウト\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.00,0:16:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}自殺行為だってことが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.00,0:16:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}分からないのか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.04,0:16:09.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ええ加減にしようや　みんな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.74,0:16:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}こんなんしてても らちが明かんで\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.48,0:16:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}みんな聞け　提案がある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:20.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:20.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}船井…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.95,0:16:24.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}自分のカードが相手に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.95,0:16:24.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}知られてるかもという疑念で\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.59,0:16:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}互いに けん制しあって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.59,0:16:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}動かれへんっちゅうのは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.96,0:16:31.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}まるでアホみたいや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.96,0:16:31.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}誰のプラスにもならへん　だから\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}１度ゼロに戻すんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}みんなのカードを１度集め\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.70,0:16:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}シャッフルして配り直すんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.44,0:16:40.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何！？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.44,0:16:40.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.81,0:16:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そしたら自分のカードが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.81,0:16:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}知られてても関係ない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.68,0:16:50.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}また最初と同じ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.68,0:16:50.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}まっさらな状態に戻るんやから\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.55,0:16:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}疑念の雲は一気に晴れる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.55,0:16:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ちゃうか？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.29,0:16:59.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カ カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.52,0:17:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}こいつ 何を言い出すかと思ったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.52,0:17:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}とんでもないことを\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.40,0:17:07.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}もしそんなことになったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.40,0:17:07.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺たちの買い占めが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.97,0:17:10.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}白日の下にさらされる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.80,0:17:13.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}チョキ殺しの戦略は破綻する\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.47,0:17:17.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}どや　名案やろ？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.47,0:17:17.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ふざけるな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.18,0:17:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}みんな試行錯誤の末 現在の\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.18,0:17:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}この状況にたどり着いたんだぞ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.08,0:17:25.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}高田とかいうたっけ？あんた\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.35,0:17:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}あんた３人を標的にしとったやろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.35,0:17:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}誰とは言わんけど\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.69,0:17:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}あんたは その連中が持ってる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.69,0:17:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードが何かを知っとる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.16,0:17:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}分かるんや　お互い１枚の\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.16,0:17:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードに命を懸けとるからな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.80,0:17:43.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}せやけど 場が煮詰まった今\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.80,0:17:43.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}そんなことには構ってられへん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.63,0:17:47.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}みんなもよく聞け\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.63,0:17:47.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あの時計がゼロを示して\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.10,0:17:50.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}終了のブザーが鳴った時\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.10,0:17:50.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カード１枚でも持っとったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.81,0:17:54.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}即 別室行きや　しかし\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.18,0:17:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カードさえ使い切っとったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.18,0:17:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}生き残りの可能性はある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.48,0:18:02.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}ゲーム終了後 星の売買タイム\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.48,0:18:02.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}っちゅう救済措置がある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.35,0:18:05.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}あそこにいる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.35,0:18:05.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}星３つに至らん連中は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.26,0:18:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}その売買待ち\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.26,0:18:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あんたは今 星が３つ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.16,0:18:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}仮に２つに減らしても\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.16,0:18:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}まだ生き残る可能性がある\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.80,0:18:18.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}だが このままカードを残したら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.80,0:18:18.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}100パーセント終わり\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.07,0:18:20.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}すべてを失う\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.57,0:18:25.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}と ひとごとみたいに言うたが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.88,0:18:29.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺もあんたと同様\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.88,0:18:29.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}機会を待っとったんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.08,0:18:31.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何を持っとるか知っとる奴が\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.08,0:18:31.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}何人かおる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.98,0:18:34.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}例えば そこのグラサンがグー\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.39,0:18:37.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}キャップのメガネがチョキ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.39,0:18:37.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}その横の長髪がパー\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.09,0:18:44.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}な 何を言う\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.09,0:18:44.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}アホもたいがいにせえ！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.63,0:18:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}お前らにカードを売った男は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.63,0:18:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードと情報を売り\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.33,0:18:51.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そのカネで星を仕入れる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.33,0:18:51.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}リピーターや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.27,0:18:54.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}せやから お前らに何を売ったか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.27,0:18:54.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}っちゅう情報も\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.14,0:18:58.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}また他の奴らに\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.14,0:18:58.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}売り飛ばしとるんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.01,0:19:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}ここにいる半数は\N
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.01,0:19:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}それを買っとるやないか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.88,0:19:02.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}いい加減 気づけや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.81,0:19:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}そうやって 手をこまねいとって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.81,0:19:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}何が解決するんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.32,0:19:09.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}俺と おどれらのカードが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.32,0:19:09.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}混ざり合ったら\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.09,0:19:11.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}もう誰が何を持ってるか\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.09,0:19:11.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}分からんようになる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.92,0:19:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}１度ゼロに戻すんや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.92,0:19:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}だから来い！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.30,0:19:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}この３人が口火\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.30,0:19:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}あとは なだれ現象\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.30,0:19:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}高田も後に続き７人が船井に同調\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.50,0:19:29.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.41,0:19:32.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジたちは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.41,0:19:32.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}戦う相手を次々に失い\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.31,0:19:36.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}打つ手なし　またしても戦略破綻\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.81,0:19:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}クソッ　船井め！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.48,0:19:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}飲まされる ２度目の煮え湯\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.72,0:19:47.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}13 14 15 16…\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.53,0:19:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}変じゃねえか　８人集まって\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.53,0:19:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カード16枚ってのは\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.40,0:19:56.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}電光掲示板には まだ90枚\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.40,0:19:56.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カードがあることになってる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.97,0:20:00.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}向こうにいる誰かが\N
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.97,0:20:00.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}こっそり買い占めとるんやろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.81,0:20:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}まあ いい\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.81,0:20:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}うちらは うちらだけで進めようや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.68,0:20:09.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カードシャッフルの意向を\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.68,0:20:09.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}理解した者だけで作った\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.98,0:20:13.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}会員制のクラブみたいなものと\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.98,0:20:13.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}考えればええ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.42,0:20:16.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}勝負は会員の中だけでやる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.32,0:20:19.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}部外者は締め出そうや 徹底的に\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.82,0:20:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カ カイジさん\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.20,0:20:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}入れてください 俺も\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.20,0:20:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺も\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.00,0:20:33.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}これで10人\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.00,0:20:33.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}一部の頑固者を除き ほぼ全員\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.87,0:20:37.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}じゃあ結ぶで\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.87,0:20:37.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}会員だけで勝負をして\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.74,0:20:42.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}他の者との戦いを禁ずる紳士協定\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.18,0:20:44.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}カ カイジさん！\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.99,0:20:51.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}待て\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.82,0:20:54.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}何や\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.82,0:20:54.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}俺たちも加わる\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.66,0:21:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}随分 遅い決断やな\N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.66,0:21:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}ま ええやろ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.20,0:21:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}来る者は拒まずや\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.20,0:21:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}入りや カイジ\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.64,0:21:09.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジ 苦渋の決断\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.64,0:21:09.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}飲まざるをえない\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.14,0:21:12.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}すべてをゼロにするシャッフル\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.18,0:21:16.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,898)}カイジはそこに\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.18,0:21:16.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}どんな活路を見出せるのか？\N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.35,0:21:19.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}残り時間 あと14分\N
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.23,0:22:46.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,1018)}次回 ｢喝破｣\N
