[Script Info]
;   Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.9
;   http://www.aegisub.org/

Title:诸神字幕
Original Script:诸神字幕组
Original Timing:Maize
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: JP,有澤行書,52,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,0,0,2,128
Style: JP_OP,有澤行書,53,&H00CEF3D6,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,7,15,0,5,128
Style: JP_ED,有澤行書,53,&H005B5D5F,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E0E7EE,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,9,0,15,30,128
Style: CN_OP,汉仪行楷简,57,&H00CEF3D6,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,7,15,15,20,134
Style: CN_ED,汉仪行楷简,57,&H004A4D52,&H000000FF,&H00F9F9FB,&H00FEFEFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,3,0,15,30,134
Style: CN,汉仪行楷简,65,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,0,0,60,134
Style: disclaimer,方正楷体_GBK,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,方正楷体_GBK,53,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,90,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.00,0:10:51.36,disclaimer,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(200,200)}本字幕由诸神字幕组制作，仅供学习交流之用\N更多中日双语动漫，请登录www.kamigami.org
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.00,0:10:51.36,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}---诸神字幕组---\N日听：辰  翻译：有明の月  校对：喵  小爱\N时间轴：Maize   压制：娜夏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.05,0:01:35.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこだ どこへ行った
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.19,0:01:40.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やつは あの女は
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.74,0:01:47.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこだ どこへ行った
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.26,0:01:51.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの女は どこへ行った
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.79,0:01:55.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.84,0:01:58.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バイトなら 海だろ 海の家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.60,0:02:00.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おお 海か
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.03,0:02:01.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか出会いとかあったりして
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.94,0:02:03.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ある ある 絶対
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.06,0:02:08.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ 夏目 何やってんだ お前
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.83,0:02:10.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何って
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:16.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんでもない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.71,0:02:20.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんでもないって 泥だらけじゃないかよ 大丈夫か
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.12,0:02:21.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.53,0:02:25.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,な 近くに神社はないか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.59,0:02:29.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神社なら その藪を抜けたところに確か
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.83,0:02:30.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.76,0:02:34.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 夏目 何だあいつ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.15,0:02:36.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何急いでんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.27,0:02:44.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ 今の
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.27,0:02:46.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すんげえ風
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.36,0:02:50.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あいつ変わってるよな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.58,0:02:54.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,転入してきてからちゃんと喋ったこと殆どないもんな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.67,0:02:57.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか話かけづらいっていうかさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.01,0:03:00.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何やってんだ か
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.85,0:03:03.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれが見えないなんて 羨ましいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.82,0:03:06.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待て
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.89,0:03:12.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小さな頃から 時々変なものを見た
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.36,0:03:16.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは恐らく妖怪と言われるものの類
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.32,0:03:19.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,元々いい気はしなかったが
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.27,0:03:20.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここに引越してきてから
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.91,0:03:23.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やたらと絡んでくるやつがいて困っている
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.61,0:03:26.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そういう時は 神社にでも逃げ込んでしまえば
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.26,0:03:31.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕まえた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.93,0:03:36.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっと捕まえたぞ レイコ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.78,0:03:38.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコ？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.25,0:03:41.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ 返せ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.50,0:03:44.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ さあ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.88,0:03:46.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待て まあ待て
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.88,0:03:49.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前の名前が呼ばれては厄介だ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.27,0:03:52.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名前を呼ばれないよう舌を抜いてしまおう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.21,0:03:54.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌を
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:03:58.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,い いてえ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.49,0:04:02.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}痛い 痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.67,0:04:03.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばか 逃げたぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.93,0:04:07.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}痛い 痛いよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.21,0:04:07.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おのれ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.24,0:04:12.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして いつも
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.05,0:04:15.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見たくて見てる訳じゃないのに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.33,0:04:18.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あら 貴志君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.14,0:04:21.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お皿は三枚でいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.88,0:04:26.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,え でもそこにいるお客さんの分
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.01,0:04:31.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの子 また今日変なこと言ったのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.42,0:04:32.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気を引きたいんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.84,0:04:34.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂しいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.04,0:04:37.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうなのかしら なんだか気味が悪いわ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.83,0:04:41.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほら あそこだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.80,0:04:42.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.60,0:04:45.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なにもいないわよ 貴志君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.11,0:04:47.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いるよ よく見てよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.96,0:04:49.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほら あそこだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.52,0:04:51.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あそこだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.74,0:04:53.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こっち見てるじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.74,0:04:58.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いるってば いるんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.26,0:05:03.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御免ね 見えないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.54,0:05:10.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっててて…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.27,0:05:16.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ まさか？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.48,0:05:19.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 破れた
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.48,0:05:22.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我を封じし結界が破れたぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.79,0:05:26.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結界？ やばい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.64,0:05:31.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駄目だ どうしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.43,0:06:02.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人のくせいに私を見て動じないとは 生意気な
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.86,0:06:12.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か言え
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.29,0:06:15.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慣れているんでね
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.72,0:06:18.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふん ふてぶてしいやつめ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.71,0:06:23.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おや お前 夏目レイコじゃないか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.56,0:06:28.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕まえたぞ レイコ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.77,0:06:30.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.18,0:06:33.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだ 違うのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.80,0:06:35.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目レイコは祖母の名だ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.14,0:06:39.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母？ なんだお前はレイコの孫か
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.12,0:06:43.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なるほど よく見れば男だ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.30,0:06:45.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よく見なくても男だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.40,0:06:47.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人間と違ってな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.26,0:06:50.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我々は性別などはさほど頓着せんのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.82,0:06:52.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母知ってるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.43,0:06:55.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あぁ この近くに住んでいてな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.46,0:06:58.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはそれは美しい人間だった
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.94,0:07:03.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そしてお前えのように妖ものを見ることができた
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.67,0:07:06.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが周りの人間が見えない
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.82,0:07:09.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰もレイコのことが理解できなかった
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.72,0:07:13.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコはいつも一人だった
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.35,0:07:16.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつもいつも一人だった
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.15,0:07:21.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.06,0:07:30.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこで レイコは妖ものを相手にし始めた
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.96,0:07:33.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳を知っているかい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.36,0:07:35.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.01,0:07:38.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ そういえば 祖母の…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.95,0:07:51.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消えた
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.49,0:07:59.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あら お帰り 貴志君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.33,0:08:02.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子さん ただいま
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.04,0:08:05.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたの 顔が青いわよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.49,0:08:07.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこか悪いの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.79,0:08:10.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ いえ 大丈夫です
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.51,0:08:13.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ 制服どろどろじゃないの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.13,0:08:14.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何があったの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.44,0:08:17.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや これは転んだだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:21.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,転んだ？ どこで？ 怪我はないの？ 痛い所は？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.78,0:08:23.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん 大丈夫です
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:25.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すいません 心配掛けちゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.57,0:08:27.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当大丈夫ですから
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.55,0:08:30.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それならいいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.47,0:08:34.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何があったら遠慮しないで言ってよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.37,0:08:36.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい ありがとうございます
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.35,0:08:40.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わんぱくも結構だけど 程程にね
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.51,0:08:41.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.32,0:08:52.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪に追いかけられたなんて塔子さんには言えないからな
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.97,0:08:55.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気味の悪い思いはさせたくない
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.11,0:09:06.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両親を早くに無くした俺は 親戚の家を転々としてきた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.41,0:09:08.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血の繋がっていない
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.51,0:09:15.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも俺と関わりを持ってしまった人々の間で 俺は暮らしてきた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:19.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この家のお世話になり始めたのは先月
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.44,0:09:24.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここはかつて俺の祖母も暮らした土地だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.39,0:09:28.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亡くなった祖母も俺と同じように
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.02,0:09:32.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他の人には見えないものを見てしまう力を持っていて
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.94,0:09:36.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのせいで 周りから疎まれていたという
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.01,0:09:44.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もらった遺品の中に確か…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.14,0:09:48.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これか 招き猫が言ってたの
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.43,0:09:52.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんなんだ これ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.52,0:09:55.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それを渡せ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.35,0:10:00.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは お前の持つべきものではない
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.52,0:10:05.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳を 寄越せ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.00,0:10:14.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴志君 今の音は 何
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.38,0:10:17.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すいません なんでもないでーす
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.15,0:10:23.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう ちょっとお買い物行ってくるから お留守番お願いね
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:25.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい 行ってらっしゃい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.50,0:10:34.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抜けん 早く 私を出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.51,0:10:36.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳も出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.00,0:10:39.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いやいや でもまず私先をに出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.96,0:10:41.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その後に 友人帳も
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.57,0:10:44.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しばらくほっとくか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.24,0:10:53.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それ食ったら帰れよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.20,0:10:56.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前ここの居候か
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.58,0:10:58.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うるさいな ニャンコのくせいに
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.13,0:11:01.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニャンコとはなんだ 失敬な
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.38,0:11:04.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この招き猫は本来の私の姿ではない
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.90,0:11:08.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来の私は それはそれは優美な姿なのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.13,0:11:11.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ ニャンコじゃないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.46,0:11:13.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから そう言ってるだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.26,0:11:17.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニャン ニャン
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.10,0:11:20.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニャンコじゃないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.18,0:11:21.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ち…違うわ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.52,0:11:23.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体がこの形に慣れてしまっただけだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.06,0:11:26.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ何でもいいから 早く食って帰ってくれ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.24,0:11:28.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面倒は御免だから
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.97,0:11:30.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや 帰らん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.25,0:11:34.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前が友人帳を持っていることが分かったからな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.88,0:11:37.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結界を破ってもらった恩義もある
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.96,0:11:40.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これからはお前の用心棒をしてやるから
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.48,0:11:42.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生とでも呼ぶんだな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.45,0:11:48.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用心棒って？ そんなに危険なものなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.51,0:11:50.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだ 何もしらんのか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.98,0:11:52.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳にはな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.34,0:11:57.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目レイコが負かした妖もの達の名前が書いてあるのだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.98,0:12:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名前？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.44,0:12:05.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコは出会う妖ものたちに次々と勝負を挑んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.22,0:12:10.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれながらにして強力な妖力を持つレイコは全戦全勝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.05,0:12:12.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして負けたものには
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.25,0:12:15.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子分となる証しとして紙に名を書かせた
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.31,0:12:20.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それをつづりにしたものが友人帳なのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.84,0:12:23.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪の名前だったのか
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.58,0:12:27.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その契約書を持つものに名を呼ばれると
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.30,0:12:30.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆らうことはできないと言われている
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.17,0:12:33.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つまり 友人帳を手に入れると
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.54,0:12:38.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名を連ねた妖ものたちを統べることをできてしまうのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.19,0:12:41.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,な 危険だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.75,0:12:46.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,種 ついてるぞ 口の横
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.38,0:12:52.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なるほどね それでニャンコ先生はこれを欲しがった訳だ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.39,0:12:54.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばか ぞんざいに扱うな
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.59,0:12:58.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文字が傷つくと名を持ちものも傷つくと言われているのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.67,0:13:00.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ そうなんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.54,0:13:02.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ ってことは
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.61,0:13:05.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニャンコ先生もこれに載ってるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.21,0:13:06.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,載っ取ろうわ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.14,0:13:09.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それだけデリケートな代物だといっておるのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.54,0:13:10.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.20,0:13:14.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だその目は 私がレイコごときに負けるものか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.67,0:13:16.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも封印されてたじゃないか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.65,0:13:22.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ…あれ にはなあ また色々と深い訳があって
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.50,0:13:24.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや そんなことよりもだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.22,0:13:29.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前が考えているより 友人帳の力は遥かに大きい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.73,0:13:33.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だからこそ そこに名をつられたあやかし者達は
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.26,0:13:36.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必死に夏目レイコを探しているのだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.03,0:13:40.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前 危ないぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.94,0:13:43.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御免下さい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.98,0:13:45.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめん下さい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.50,0:13:52.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すいません 家のものは今留守でして
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.53,0:13:58.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やはり 帰ってきたね レイコ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.46,0:14:05.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡せ 友人帳を
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.49,0:14:08.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめん下さい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.55,0:14:11.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,返せ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.06,0:14:17.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん？ ああ やれやれ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.91,0:14:25.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニャンコ先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.25,0:14:27.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこへ行く気だ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.78,0:14:28.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どこへって
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.27,0:14:30.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その物陰に隠れろ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.36,0:14:41.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まいったな
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.54,0:14:44.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人の手におえるものではないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.33,0:14:46.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さ よく分かったろう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.59,0:14:49.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから 私に送り
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.57,0:14:50.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駄目だ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.53,0:14:52.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,な…何故だ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.30,0:14:55.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人間のくせに妖ものの上に立つつもりか
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.91,0:14:57.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんな訳ないだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.10,0:14:59.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ なんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.08,0:15:02.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前にとってそう使う以外何の意味がある
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.79,0:15:04.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生には関係ないだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.59,0:15:17.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脈あるまでと思ってやったが 友人帳を寄越せ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.27,0:15:22.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だ…駄目だ 先生こそ変なことに使う気だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.78,0:15:25.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当たり前だ そんな面白そうなもの
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.21,0:15:27.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんてやつだ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.70,0:15:31.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早く渡せ さもないと 潰してしまうぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.15,0:15:39.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは 友人帳はな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.54,0:15:43.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺にとって祖母の大事な遺品なんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.15,0:15:49.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに 祖母は人とうまく付き合えなかったらしい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.57,0:15:52.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覚えている人も殆どいないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.70,0:15:55.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼女は若くして亡くなったから
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.13,0:16:00.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから 唯一血縁の俺ぐらいは繋がりを持っていてやりたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.76,0:16:03.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人事とは思えないしな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.09,0:16:09.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,な 先生 返したいんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:10.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたらいいのかな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.25,0:16:12.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,返す？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.67,0:16:16.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名前だよ 妖怪達に返してやりたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.38,0:16:18.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あほ やめろ もったいない
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.74,0:16:21.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それに中には凶暴なやつも多い
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.03,0:16:24.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命がいくつあっても足りんぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.93,0:16:28.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平気だよ 俺には先生がついてるじゃないか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.67,0:16:29.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.59,0:16:32.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコさんがやり残したことを俺がやりたいんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.86,0:16:36.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もし俺が途中で命を落としたら
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.31,0:16:37.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳は譲る
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.15,0:16:41.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力を貸してくれよ 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.56,0:16:45.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 お前が消える時
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.62,0:16:48.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に友人帳をもらっていいんだな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.39,0:16:49.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ いいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.54,0:16:54.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よかろう 見届けよう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.23,0:16:58.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.03,0:17:08.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おのれ レイコ 舌を抜いてくれるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.21,0:17:10.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前は？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.57,0:17:12.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帳が欲しいのか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.67,0:17:17.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふん 友人帳さえあれば この辺りの主になれる
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.25,0:17:20.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前もそうなんだろう 斑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.01,0:17:22.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一緒にするな 低級めが
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.89,0:17:24.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おのれ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:30.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まずは相手の姿をイメージしつつ 開き 念じろ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.74,0:17:33.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我を護りしものよ その名を示せ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.26,0:17:49.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うせろ そして二度と我が前に姿を現すな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.09,0:17:55.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次に必要なのは
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.41,0:18:00.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコの唾液と息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.66,0:18:02.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血縁のお前ならやれる
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.13,0:18:04.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,契約書を破ってくわえ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.45,0:18:09.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両の手を強く打ち合わせ 集中し
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.38,0:18:12.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふっと息を吐く
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.34,0:18:23.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂しい 寂しい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.67,0:18:27.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おなかがすいた
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.99,0:18:36.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ わしの饅頭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.11,0:18:41.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんまり美味しくないわよ これ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.07,0:18:43.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人間のくせに何をする 意地汚い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.86,0:18:47.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美味しいお饅頭が食べたかったら 七辻屋のがお勧めよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:49.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七辻？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.29,0:18:52.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうね あたしと勝負してあなたが勝てたら
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.76,0:18:54.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ご馳走してあげましょうか
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.77,0:18:57.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前 私が見えるんだな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.91,0:18:59.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええ 見えるわよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.65,0:19:01.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐ろしくはないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.49,0:19:04.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全然 だって私は強いもの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.53,0:19:06.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ いくわよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.02,0:19:11.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.70,0:19:13.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい 私の勝ち
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.63,0:19:17.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不意打ちじゃないか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.04,0:19:18.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝ちは勝ちよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.81,0:19:21.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし これであなたは私の子分よ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.99,0:19:23.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子分？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.53,0:19:27.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.56,0:19:29.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その頬の傷はどうした
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.83,0:19:32.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 石をぶつけられてね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.43,0:19:35.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は気味が悪いんですって
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.77,0:19:39.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へー あなた 綺麗な名前なのね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.03,0:19:41.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子分になったんだら
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.84,0:19:44.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この名前を呼んだら飛んできてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.80,0:19:46.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前の名前は
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:47.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.58,0:19:50.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.22,0:19:51.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ まったねー
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.07,0:20:03.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコ…レイコ…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.78,0:20:13.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコ…レイコ…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.61,0:20:19.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 今日も呼ばないのかい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.11,0:20:22.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂しい 前よりずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.26,0:20:27.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,返せ 名前を返せ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.82,0:20:32.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どんなに待っても 呼んでくれないくらいなら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.73,0:20:40.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしがき
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.77,0:20:44.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコ もういいのかい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.05,0:20:47.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一人でも平気かい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.28,0:20:51.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母はきっと 一人じゃなかったよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.01,0:21:01.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう ひしがき 心優しい祖母の友人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.87,0:21:16.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レイコには会えたかい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.96,0:21:18.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.92,0:21:20.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひどいやつだったろう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.32,0:21:24.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やれるかい 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.06,0:21:27.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺はやりたい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.66,0:21:31.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.97,0:21:38.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪のことは 相変わらず 好きにはなれない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:40.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.76,0:21:46.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 あそこの饅頭うまいんだってさ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.38,0:21:47.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何 GOGO
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.84,0:21:49.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こら 暴れるな
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.72,0:21:53.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良くも悪くも 出会いの一つ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.76,0:21:58.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ でもニャンコって甘いもの食べてもいいのか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.43,0:22:00.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから ニャンコじゃないと言ってるだろうか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.98,0:22:04.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饅頭ください
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.20,0:23:50.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.51,0:23:37.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の名は？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.47,0:23:39.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は露神
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.09,0:23:41.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい ばあさんがお前の祠拝んでるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.88,0:23:44.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私はあの人をずっと見てきた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.26,0:23:46.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声を聞いてきた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.30,0:23:50.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 私の声が聞こえたらな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.05,0:01:35.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪 去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.19,0:01:40.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙 那个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.74,0:01:47.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪 去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.26,0:01:51.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女人 去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.79,0:01:55.54,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1B2D4A&\4c&H9EDBA5&}猫{\c&H005606&\4c&H6CB0A2&}与{\c&H1B2D4A&\4c&H9EDBA5&}友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.84,0:01:58.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工的话 当然是去海边 海之家呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.60,0:02:00.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢噢 海啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.03,0:02:01.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定还有命运的邂逅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.94,0:02:03.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的 有的 绝对的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.06,0:02:08.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 夏目 你在干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.83,0:02:10.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:16.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.71,0:02:20.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说没什么 身上都是泥啊 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.12,0:02:21.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.53,0:02:25.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 附近有神社吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.59,0:02:29.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神社的话 我记得穿过这草丛后有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.83,0:02:30.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.76,0:02:34.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 那家伙怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.15,0:02:36.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么急匆匆的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.27,0:02:44.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.27,0:02:46.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强的风
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.36,0:02:50.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙真奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.58,0:02:54.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从转学以来就没怎么见他说话过
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.67,0:02:57.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很难搭上话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.01,0:03:00.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问我在干什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.85,0:03:03.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真羡慕他们看不到那些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.82,0:03:06.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我站住
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.89,0:03:12.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候开始 我就不时地看见奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.36,0:03:16.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概就是人们所说的妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.32,0:03:19.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就对妖怪没什么好感
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.27,0:03:20.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从搬到这里之后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.91,0:03:23.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缠着我不放的家伙更多了 实在让我头疼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.61,0:03:26.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候 只要逃到神社里…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.26,0:03:31.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.93,0:03:36.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于抓到你了 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.78,0:03:38.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.25,0:03:41.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.50,0:03:44.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 快
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.88,0:03:46.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 嘛 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.88,0:03:49.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字被叫到的话就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.27,0:03:52.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为防万一先把他舌头给拔了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.21,0:03:54.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把舌头…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:03:58.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼…疼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.49,0:04:02.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}疼 疼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.67,0:04:03.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 让他逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.93,0:04:07.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}疼 好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.21,0:04:07.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.24,0:04:12.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 一直以来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.05,0:04:15.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我想去看见这些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.33,0:04:18.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.14,0:04:21.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盘子只要三个就够了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.88,0:04:26.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 但是那边的客人的份呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.01,0:04:31.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子 今天又说了奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.42,0:04:32.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是想引起大家的注意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.84,0:04:34.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太寂寞了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.04,0:04:37.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗 真令人害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.83,0:04:41.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 那边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.80,0:04:42.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.60,0:04:45.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有啊 贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.11,0:04:47.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊 看清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.96,0:04:49.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 就在那里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.52,0:04:51.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.74,0:04:53.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是正看着我们这边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.74,0:04:58.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有啊 有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.26,0:05:03.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 我们看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.54,0:05:10.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.27,0:05:16.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.48,0:05:19.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 被打破了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.48,0:05:22.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印我的结界终于被打破了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.79,0:05:26.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结界？不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.64,0:05:31.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接不上 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.43,0:06:02.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类 看到我竟然还面不改色 真是狂妄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.86,0:06:12.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快说点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.29,0:06:15.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.72,0:06:18.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 目中无人的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.71,0:06:23.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀 你不是夏目铃子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.56,0:06:28.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到你了 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.77,0:06:30.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.18,0:06:33.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 弄错了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.80,0:06:35.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目铃子是我祖母的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.14,0:06:39.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母？ 原来你是铃子的孙子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.12,0:06:43.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 仔细一看的确是男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.30,0:06:45.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仔细看也是男孩子好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.40,0:06:47.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和人类不同
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.26,0:06:50.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不那么在乎性别
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.82,0:06:52.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识我祖母吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.43,0:06:55.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 她就住在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.46,0:06:58.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可真是个美人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.94,0:07:03.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也和你一样能够看见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.67,0:07:06.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是身边的人却看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.82,0:07:09.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人能理解铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.72,0:07:13.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子总是孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.35,0:07:16.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直一直 都是孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.15,0:07:21.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤单一人…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.06,0:07:30.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 铃子开始和妖怪打交道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.96,0:07:33.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.36,0:07:35.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.01,0:07:38.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 说起来 祖母的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.95,0:07:51.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.49,0:07:59.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 你回来啦 贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.33,0:08:02.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨 我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.04,0:08:05.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 脸色不太好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.49,0:08:07.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有哪里不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.79,0:08:10.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.51,0:08:13.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 校服弄得脏兮兮的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.13,0:08:14.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.44,0:08:17.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 摔了一跤而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:21.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摔跤了？ 在哪里？ 有受伤吗？ 有哪里疼吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.78,0:08:23.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:25.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 让您担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.57,0:08:27.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.55,0:08:30.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.47,0:08:34.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事的话别客气 要跟我说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.37,0:08:36.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.35,0:08:40.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淘气没什么不好 但要注意分寸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.51,0:08:41.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.32,0:08:52.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被妖怪追的事不能跟塔子阿姨说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.97,0:08:55.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让她们感到害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.11,0:09:06.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双亲早逝的我一直辗转于亲戚家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.41,0:09:08.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说没有血缘关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.51,0:09:15.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我在跟我有点关系的人们的家中住了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:19.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是从上个月开始住在这个家里的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.44,0:09:24.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里也是我祖母曾经生活过的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.39,0:09:28.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经去世的祖母也和我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.02,0:09:32.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有着能够看见他人无法看见的东西的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.94,0:09:36.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 被周围的人所疏远
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.01,0:09:44.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下来的遗物当中我记得有…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.14,0:09:48.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个吗 招财猫说的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.43,0:09:52.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 这些
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.52,0:09:55.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它给我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.35,0:10:00.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是你该有的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.52,0:10:05.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.00,0:10:14.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君 刚刚那是什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.38,0:10:17.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.15,0:10:23.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 我去买点东西 拜托你看家了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:25.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 路上小心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.50,0:10:34.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔不出来了 快点 把我弄出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.51,0:10:36.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐也交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.00,0:10:39.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 还是先把我弄出来再说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.96,0:10:41.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再把友人帐给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.57,0:10:44.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂且别管它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.24,0:10:53.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完这个就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.20,0:10:56.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你寄住在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.58,0:10:58.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真罗嗦 区区一只猫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.13,0:11:01.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么猫啊 真是无礼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.38,0:11:04.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个招财猫不是我的真身
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.90,0:11:08.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的真身那是多么的优美
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.13,0:11:11.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你不是猫咯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.46,0:11:13.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.26,0:11:17.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.10,0:11:20.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还不是猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.18,0:11:21.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才…才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.52,0:11:23.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为身体习惯了这种形态
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.06,0:11:26.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎样都好 快点吃完回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.24,0:11:28.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.97,0:11:30.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.25,0:11:34.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经知道你手中有友人帐了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.88,0:11:37.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你打破了结界也算对我有恩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.96,0:11:40.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后就由我来做你的保镖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.48,0:11:42.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就叫我老师吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.45,0:11:48.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保镖？这东西有这么危险吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.51,0:11:50.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 你什么都不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.98,0:11:52.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐上面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.34,0:11:57.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写着夏目铃子打败的妖怪们的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.98,0:12:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.44,0:12:05.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子一个接一个地挑战了她所遇到的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.22,0:12:10.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而天生拥有强大妖力的铃子百战百胜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.05,0:12:12.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 她让输掉的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.25,0:12:15.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在纸上写下名字 作为成为手下的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.31,0:12:20.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这些纸装订在一起就成了友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.84,0:12:23.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪的名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.58,0:12:27.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说 若是妖怪被手持这本契约书的人呼唤名字的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.30,0:12:30.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是无法违抗的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.17,0:12:33.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 只要把友人帐弄到手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.54,0:12:38.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能统领上面所写的一系列的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.19,0:12:41.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 很危险吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.75,0:12:46.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西瓜子 黏在嘴边了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.38,0:12:52.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 难怪猫咪老师想要得到它
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.39,0:12:54.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 别那么粗鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.59,0:12:58.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说若是文字受损的话 会伤害到那个妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.67,0:13:00.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.54,0:13:02.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 这样说来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.61,0:13:05.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师的名字也在上面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.21,0:13:06.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在个鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.14,0:13:09.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说那些小妖
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.54,0:13:10.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.20,0:13:14.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛用这种眼光看我 我怎么会输给铃子那种货色
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.67,0:13:16.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不是被封印了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.65,0:13:22.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那是… 还有很多深层的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.50,0:13:24.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 先不说那个了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.22,0:13:29.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的力量远比你想象的要强大
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.73,0:13:33.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因为如此 在上面写下名字的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.26,0:13:36.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才拼命寻找夏目铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.03,0:13:40.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 会很危险哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.94,0:13:43.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.98,0:13:45.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.50,0:13:52.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 家人暂时不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.53,0:13:58.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然回来了 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.46,0:14:05.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.49,0:14:08.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.55,0:14:11.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.06,0:14:17.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 啊 哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.91,0:14:25.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.25,0:14:27.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.78,0:14:28.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还问我去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.27,0:14:30.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲到那里的隐蔽处
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.36,0:14:41.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.54,0:14:44.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是人类能解决得了的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.33,0:14:46.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下清楚了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.59,0:14:49.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 把友人帐就给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.57,0:14:50.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.53,0:14:52.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.30,0:14:55.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道区区人类还妄想统率妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.91,0:14:57.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.10,0:14:59.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.08,0:15:02.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说除了这么用之外还有什么意义
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.79,0:15:04.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟老师你没关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.59,0:15:17.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来还以为有可能说服你的 把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.27,0:15:22.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不行 老师你才是想用在坏事上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.78,0:15:25.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话 这么有趣的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.21,0:15:27.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.70,0:15:31.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点交出来 否则我就压扁你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.15,0:15:39.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.54,0:15:43.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说是祖母留下的重要的遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.15,0:15:49.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 祖母不擅长和人打交道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.57,0:15:52.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几乎没有人记得她
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.70,0:15:55.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她年纪轻轻就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.13,0:16:00.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 唯一和她有血缘关系的我想留住这份联系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.76,0:16:03.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟别人无关
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.09,0:16:09.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 老师 我想还给它们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:10.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.25,0:16:12.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给它们？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.67,0:16:16.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是名字 我想还给妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.38,0:16:18.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 住手 那样多可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.74,0:16:21.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且在那之中 有很多凶狠的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.03,0:16:24.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任你有几条命都不够
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.93,0:16:28.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 我不是有老师在嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.67,0:16:29.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.59,0:16:32.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子未完成的事 我想继续完成
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.86,0:16:36.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是我中途丢了性命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.31,0:16:37.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把友人帐让给你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.15,0:16:41.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助我一臂之力吧 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.56,0:16:45.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你消失的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.62,0:16:48.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的可以拿走友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.39,0:16:49.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 可以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.54,0:16:54.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我会保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.23,0:16:58.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.03,0:17:08.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 铃子 我要把你的舌头拔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.21,0:17:10.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.57,0:17:12.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.67,0:17:17.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 只要拿到了友人帐 就能成为这一带的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.25,0:17:20.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也是这样想的吗 斑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.01,0:17:22.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我和你相提并论 低级的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.89,0:17:24.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:30.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先想象对方的相貌 然后翻开友人帐 念出咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.74,0:17:33.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾者 显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.26,0:17:49.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚 别再出现在我面前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.09,0:17:55.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来需要的是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.41,0:18:00.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子的唾液和气息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.66,0:18:02.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有血缘关系的你可以做到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.13,0:18:04.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撕下契约书 含在嘴里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.45,0:18:09.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两手用力拍掌 集中精神
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.38,0:18:12.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞬间吐气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.34,0:18:23.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寂寞 好寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.67,0:18:27.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.99,0:18:36.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我的馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.11,0:18:41.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怎么好吃啊 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.07,0:18:43.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类 你在做什么 这么贪吃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.86,0:18:47.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想吃美味的馒头的话 我推荐七辻屋的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:49.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七辻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.29,0:18:52.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 若是你能赢了我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.76,0:18:54.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就请你吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.77,0:18:57.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能够看见我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.91,0:18:59.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 能看见哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.65,0:19:01.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不害怕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.49,0:19:04.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不 因为我很强嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.53,0:19:06.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.02,0:19:11.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.70,0:19:13.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 是我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.63,0:19:17.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这不是偷袭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.04,0:19:18.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了就是赢了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.81,0:19:21.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这样你就是我的手下了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.99,0:19:23.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手下？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.53,0:19:27.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.56,0:19:29.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸颊的伤是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.83,0:19:32.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是被石头砸的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.43,0:19:35.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人说我很可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.77,0:19:39.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 你的名字挺好听的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.03,0:19:41.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你成了我的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.84,0:19:44.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是我呼唤你的名字 你就要飞奔过来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.80,0:19:46.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:47.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.58,0:19:50.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.22,0:19:51.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 再见咯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.07,0:20:03.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.78,0:20:13.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.61,0:20:19.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 今天也不叫我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.11,0:20:22.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寂寞 比以前更加寂寞了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.26,0:20:27.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我 把名字还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.82,0:20:32.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然不管我怎么等 你都不叫我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.73,0:20:40.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱垣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.77,0:20:44.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 已经不要紧了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.05,0:20:47.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人也不要紧了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.28,0:20:51.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母一定 不是独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.01,0:21:01.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 菱垣 心地善良的祖母的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.87,0:21:16.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到铃子了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.96,0:21:18.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.92,0:21:20.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个过分的家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.32,0:21:24.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做到吗 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.06,0:21:27.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去做
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.66,0:21:31.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.97,0:21:38.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于妖怪 我还是无法喜欢它们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:40.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.76,0:21:46.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师 听说那边的馒头很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.38,0:21:47.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 GOGO
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.84,0:21:49.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别乱跑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.72,0:21:53.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论好坏 都是一种邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.76,0:21:58.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 但是猫咪吃甜食好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.43,0:22:00.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说了我不是猫了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.98,0:22:04.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请来份馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.20,0:23:50.53,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(500,800)\c&H0A2035&\4c&H8AA092&}露神之祠
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.51,0:23:37.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.47,0:23:39.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫露神
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.09,0:23:41.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 老奶奶在你的祠堂参拜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.88,0:23:44.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在注视着她
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.26,0:23:46.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直听着她的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.30,0:23:50.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 要是她能听到我的声音就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.05,0:01:30.81,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(870,942)\fn方正楷体_GBK\b1}{\fad(250,0)}{\c&HCEF3D6&}「诸神字幕组」　夏目委员会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.42,0:00:13.13,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}またそんな顔して {\c&HBFC3F4&}唇{\c&HCEF3D6&}噛み締めて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.43,0:00:19.50,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}弱さを{\c&HBFC3F4&}隠{\c&HCEF3D6&}してるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.23,0:00:28.90,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}その瞳の奥 うずくまる{\c&HBFC3F4&}君{\c&HCEF3D6&}が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.21,0:00:35.10,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}本当の{\c&HBFC3F4&}心{\c&HCEF3D6&}なら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.65,0:00:40.52,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}思って 泣いて {\c&HBFC3F4&}一人で{\c&HCEF3D6&} 不安で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.70,0:00:44.29,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}なんで {\c&HBFC3F4&}痛いの{\c&HCEF3D6&} 持ってんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.48,0:00:50.34,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}僕に {\c&HBFC3F4&}そっと{\c&HCEF3D6&} 預けてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.26,0:00:56.49,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}{\c&HBFC3F4&}直ぐ{\c&HCEF3D6&}じゃ無理と思うのならば
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.74,0:00:59.90,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}少し{\c&HBFC3F4&}ずつ{\c&HCEF3D6&}でいい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.45,0:01:04.05,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}翼の無い{\c&HBFC3F4&}僕等{\c&HCEF3D6&}はきっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.41,0:01:07.97,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}{\c&HBFC3F4&}飛{\c&HCEF3D6&}べないと 決め付けてるだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.19,0:01:15.60,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}声の限り君を呼ぶよ {\c&HBFC3F4&}迷わない{\c&HCEF3D6&}ように
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.12,0:01:22.93,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}フワリ心舞い{\c&HBFC3F4&}上{\c&HCEF3D6&}がれ あの風に乗せて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.21,0:01:27.06,JP_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(150,150)}{\c&HBFC3F4&}一斉{\c&HCEF3D6&}の声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.11,0:22:12.54,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}色づく 西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.09,0:22:19.97,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}差し込む一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.15,0:22:26.16,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.62,0:22:33.41,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}気付く夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.15,0:22:41.49,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ひしめく光が照らす
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.76,0:22:48.71,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想いに耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.02,0:22:57.95,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}聴こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.29,0:23:05.79,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.05,0:23:12.76,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.05,0:23:20.11,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.40,0:23:25.88,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.42,0:00:13.13,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}你又摆出这副表情 紧咬{\c&HBFC3F4&}着{\c&HCEF3D6&}双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.43,0:00:19.50,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}隐瞒着{\c&HBFC3F4&}自己{\c&HCEF3D6&}的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.23,0:00:28.90,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}即使如果那才是蹲在{\c&HBFC3F4&}瞳眸{\c&HCEF3D6&}深处的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.21,0:00:35.10,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}你的{\c&HBFC3F4&}真心{\c&HCEF3D6&}的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.65,0:00:40.52,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}思念与哭泣 {\c&HBFC3F4&}明明{\c&HCEF3D6&}你感到不安
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.70,0:00:44.29,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}为何{\c&HBFC3F4&}还要{\c&HCEF3D6&}独自承受这痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.48,0:00:50.34,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}悄悄{\c&HBFC3F4&}把它{\c&HCEF3D6&}交付给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.26,0:00:56.49,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}若你认为不能{\c&HBFC3F4&}马上{\c&HCEF3D6&}做到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.74,0:00:59.90,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}{\c&HBFC3F4&}慢慢{\c&HCEF3D6&}来也不急
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.45,0:01:04.05,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}没有翅膀的我们一{\c&HBFC3F4&}定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.41,0:01:07.97,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}只是{\c&HBFC3F4&}随便{\c&HCEF3D6&}被认为不能飞而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.19,0:01:15.60,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}我会尽我所能呼叫{\c&HBFC3F4&}你{\c&HCEF3D6&} 为了不迷失你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.12,0:01:22.93,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}心轻飘飘地飞扬起来 {\c&HBFC3F4&}乘载{\c&HCEF3D6&}那阵微风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.21,0:01:27.06,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(150,150)}{\c&HBFC3F4&}一齐{\c&HCEF3D6&}之声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.11,0:22:12.54,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}渐黄的西空
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.09,0:22:19.97,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}射入一缕阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.15,0:22:26.16,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}傍晚骤雨过后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.62,0:22:33.41,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}传来夏日气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.15,0:22:41.49,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}照着熙攘的阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.76,0:22:48.71,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}沉醉于回忆中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.02,0:22:57.95,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}友人面容浮现脑海
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.29,0:23:05.79,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夏日晚空 芬芳洋溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.05,0:23:12.76,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}鲜明生动的逝去时光
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.05,0:23:20.11,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}坦诚相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.40,0:23:25.88,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}那个夏日的回忆啊


