Kabuto, I'll tell you
about this kid later...
More importantly...
Why don't you call over
the three little mice behind you?
So he's seen through
everything, huh...?
There's the signal!
You again, huh...?
I've seen that face often...
And it looks like
the Nine-Tails kid is here, too...
Maybe I'll play with
you guys a little.
Let's see who's become stronger...
you or Sasuke.
Give Sasuke...
back...!
"Give him back" is not the correct
way of saying it, Naruto...
Your reasoning is off...
Sasuke came to us
because he wanted to.
For a man, you're too obsessed...
about the past.
You need to resign yourself.
Shut up, four-eyes!
You don't even know
how Naruto feels...
Stop acting so cold
about everything!
If you want to know about Sasuke,
try forcing it out of me...
If you can, that is...
The Nine-Tails Unleashed
Naruto...
What is this?!
What is that?
I see...
So it appeared just as I thought...
Judging from the shape
of the Chakra,
the number of tails will probably
continue to grow...and eventually...
there will be nine.
That's about the size of it...
Master Jiraiya, how many tails
have you seen?
I've come close...
to dying twice...
The first time, I broke
six ribs and both arms,
and several of my
internal organs ruptured...
It was when I tried to peek into
the women's bath at a hot spring
and you pounded me good, Tsunade...
The other time was...
during Naruto's training
when I saw the fourth tail
of the Nine-Tails Chakra.
His anger became the trigger
and the number of Fox Spirit tails
he grew increased.
He maintained consciousness up
until the third Fox Spirit tail.
But by the fourth tail,
he had lost all rationality and was
controlled by destructive impulses.
He was just like a small version
of the Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit.
Even with the
Fourth Hokage's seal
it can go that far?
Yes.
I don't know the details,
but I can say this for certain:
The Fourth Hokage's Sealing Jutsu
might very well...
be weakening.
The Fourth Hokage's Sealing Jutsu...?
I can't believe it...
There's more...
It may appear that when Naruto
is in the Nine-Tails state,
he's being protected by
the Nine-Tail's Cloak...
But in actuality, his body was
continuing to suffer damage
from the Nine Tail's Cloak itself.
After the fourth tail formed,
his body, wrapped in the Nine-Tail's
Cloak, grew bloodied,
and he thrashed about
despite suffering serious injuries.
After the Nine-Tail's Cloak
dissipated,
his wounded body
was healed by the Nine-Tails Chakra
inside his body.
But if he continues to get hurt
and then heal at that
speed over and over...
Naruto's body will break down
and his life span will shorten.
That's why we need you...
Yamato!
You, who has inherited the cells
of the First Hokage.
Now you're the only one...
who can control
the Jinchuriki Host.
Fortunately for us,
Naruto happens to be wearing
the First Hokage's necklace...
We're counting on you...
Naruto... you've grown considerably
as a Jinchuriki Host.
The power of the Nine-Tails
is rapidly getting stronger...
The striking feature of
the "Jinchuriki Host" is
how it utilizes unbelievable power
by resonating with the "Tailed Beast."
Naruto...
You're starting to become more like
a Jinchuriki Host, aren't you...
Naruto?
I get it...
So that's why you were chosen to
keep watch over him, huh?
So my experiment turned out
to be somewhat useful...
Experiment...?
The Leaf should be thanking me
a little more for this...
Don't you agree...
my adorable little test subject...?
Test subject?
Who the heck is this person?
It happened...
a long time ago when I was
still in the Hidden Leaf Village...
I wanted the power of
the First Hokage,
the only one among all Shinobi
who could use the Wood Style Ninjutsu
and control Tailed Beasts at will.
I once conducted an experiment
where I took some DNA information...
from the remains of the First Hokage
and implanted genetic components...
from that DNA into
the cells of sixty children.
But their bodies
violently rejected it,
and they died while
kicking and struggling...
Around the time when
I was about to give up,
I ended up being tracked by
another one of my experiments
and had to leave the village...
leaving my laboratory just as it was.
I thought all the test
subjects had died...
but I never thought one of them
would still be alive.
I get it...
Four-Pillar Prison Jutsu!
Th-This is...the secret Jutsu that only
the First Hokage could use.
The Wood Style Ninjutsu!
How come Captain Yamato can use
the Wood Style Ninjutsu?
So that's why he can use
the Wood Style
that only the First Hokage
could use...
So that's the story...
I see...
So it looks like we'll now
be able to obtain
a sample from a product
of old research.
More important than that...
I'd like to test out how strong
my Sasuke has become...
by having him
fight against Naruto.
He doesn't...
He doesn't belong to you...!
Don't talk about Sasuke...
in front of me...
like he belongs to you!
That's...
What's...that Chakra?!
The air stings...
Interesting...
No doubt about it.
It's the Nine-Tail's Cloak...
Three tails have formed...
Th-That's...the power of
the Jinchuriki Host...
I can feel it in my bones...
This...
This terrifying Chakra...
is not the kind that
can be controlled!
This is...Naruto Uzumaki's...
the Nine-Tail's power, huh?