The Earth was at its greatest crisis in history!
A large fleet of the Space Empire Zangyack tries to control the entire universe...
...by causing as much destruction as possible and plunging people into the depths of fear!
However, on Earth, there were warriors who stand against this mighty evil!
With love! Dreams! And peace!
These are the 34 Super Sentai that have continued to protect people's smiles!
Note: At the time, there were 34 Sentai teams. As of April 15, 2024, there were 48.
This battle is known as the "The Great Legend War".
Everyone, gather the power of all the Super Sentai and protect the Earth!
Fire!
Just like that, the Earth's future was secured!
However, the warriors of Super Sentai lost their fighting power and became legends.
Since then, time have passed...
HEEEEY!
I felt it! I felt it!
What's wrong, Navi?
It's Earth! And the greatest treasure in the universe!
Seriously?
What a beautiful planet.
I am sure that they live comfortably!
Just the reaction I'd expect from you, Ahim.
I think it looks like a big jewel!
That's always the first thing on your mind, Luka.
Does that even matter?
Our loot is on that planet.
The greatest treasure in the entire universe i-
You're trying to look cool! Even though you're secretly excited, Joe!
But is it really on a backwater planet?
It's a treasure with the same value as everything in the universe, right?
I'm sure of it.
Yup.
Oh, geez! Doc!
Okay, okay...
The Zangyack Space Fleet!?
Oh, crap! They found us!
What do we do, Marvelous? If they get involved, we'll be dead.
Then we'll get involved.
Really, that's it?!
That's what pirates do, right?
In search of adventure and glory, the young will sail across the ocean of space!
While rebelling against the Space Empire Zangyack...
...these brave fellows take pride in their pirate reputation.
And they are...
Kaizoku Sentai
Gokaiger
Forward! Hoist the flag of courage...
susume! yuuki no hata kakage
...and sail through the seven seas
nanatsu no umi wo kake-nukero
Whether it's sink or swim, the invincible wind...
ichi ka bachi ka muteki na kaze
...will lead you
kimi wo michibiku
Aim for the place that’s not on the map
mezase chizu ni nai basho wo
It's not a mirage
MABOROSHI nanka jya nainda
The only thing that’s yours...
tatta hitotsu jibun dake no
...is the treasure that everyone is searching for
takaramono dare mo sagashiteru
I wanna make sure everyone is not the same
tashikametai ze minna onaji jya nai kara
So, I gotta do whatever the hell I gotta do
yaritai koto wo yatte yare
My life is on the line!
If I want it, I gotta grab it with this hand!
inochigake da ze! hoshikerya sono te de tsukame!
Let's Go! Let's Gokaiger!
Go, go! Let’s go! Let’s take the helm
Go Go! Let's Go! Let's kaji wo tore
The sea stretches out before you...
kimi no mae ni hirogaru umi
...so let's take a road that has no path!
michinaki michi wo yukou!
Let's go! Let's Gokaiger!
Go, go! Let’s go! Let's! In the midst of the storm...
Go Go! Let's Go! Let's arashinnaka
Your hard-working “daredevil” ways will...
ganbaru kimi no “gamushara” ga ima
...change this world
kono sekai wo kaeru ze
Big dreams are infinite!
dekkai yume wa mugendai!
Kaizoku Sentai Gokaiger!
Subbed and Adapted by: TV-Sentai
Original Translators: takenoko, Magenta
Research: RangerWiki, TV-Nhion
Special Thanks, TV-Nihon, Over-Time,  Rampage Subs
Original Writer: Naruhisa Arakawa
Original Director: Shojiro Nakazawa
Very Special Thanks: Silverfoil
This is a fansub. This is not to be sold for retail.
Episode 1
The Space Pirates Appear
Prepare the artillery.
Those are the pirates with bounties on their heads?
We'll crush them and get our money's worth!
Shoot 'em down!
Port side Galleon Cannon, fire!
Hard to starboard!
Screwy pests!
Playtime's over!
Fire! Fire!
How's that?
Not good enough.
What!?
Alright!
We're going straight to Earth!
Indeed!
I really hope they have the treasure
Oh, it's there.
I want to eat some pasta!
What is that?
Sorry for the intrusion, Earthlings.
We're the Kaizoku Sentai Gokaiger.
The name's Captain Marvelous.
This planet has the greatest treasure in the universe, right?
So hurry up and tell us where we can find it.
You better not hide it from us!
You mustn't do that, Luka-san...
Good day to you all.
Now then...that commoner over there!
Yes, you.
Yes?
Do you happen to know anything about it?
I don't know anything.
Not even a little rumor?
I'm sorry, but I don't think anyone on Earth knows about this.
Right?
Oh, my...
So far, what he said was wrong.
See!? How many times have I told you guys!
What are we going to do, Marvelous
We grab a bite.
Jeez...
But we don't have any money on this planet! What are we going to do now?
Luka.
Gimme your ring.
Barizorg! Insarn! Are you prepared to take over the Earth?
Yes, boss.
We have a ruthless commander of action on standby to the likes of you, Walz Gil-sama.
I developed and gave them the most powerful weapons.
I wanted to see you pleased...
There's no need to hold back!
Let them realize the full power of the Space Empire Zangyack!
Right.
Yes, sir.
Your Highness, it appears that the advance team has been attacked by those pirates.
What?! Those pathetic wretches. They're the boot of our army!
Barizorg!
Erase the existence of the advance team from the data!
Yes, boss.
Shall we make a plan for dealing with these pirates?
We don't need a plan.
Those insignificant pirates are nothing more than flies to our empire.
Your Highness!
If you underestimate them, you'll be blindsided.
You dare defy me, Damaras!?
I am Walz Gil, the son of the Zangyack Emperor!
Of course not. Now give your orders, Your Highness.
Proceed to Earth! Full speed ahead!
T-This is amazing!
I'll buy it for ¥10,000,000!
If that's what it is.
Aw, geez...
This is only for rent!
I want it back, with interest!
I don't think he'll give it back to you...
Is that so?
He's sort of a sloppy guy.
It's a pretty good planet...
...so they must have pretty good eats.
Well, let's take this opportunity to go to a gorgeous restaurant!
Sign: Beef Curry, Chicken Curry, Dry Curry, Deluxe Safari Curry
Why did we go here?
'Cause it smells great.
And I heard that curry's good.
I get that, but...
Living the life of a commoner...
Isn't it a great experience?
Well, it may be a little unusual for you, Ahim...
So, how do we find the greatest treasure in the universe?
Don't be in a hurry. If we don't eat, we can't think straight.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
This is our Deluxe Safari Curry!
It looks delicious! Let us eat.
Down the hatch it goes!
My money! My precious money!
Yo.
What about my curry?
Out of the qusetion! No matter what you think!
Really...?
More importantly, look at that!
What is that giant thing?!
The Gigant Horse, the flagship of Zangyack Space Fleet!
They were the advance troops that we had just killed!
So?
The fact that they're here means they're serious about conquering this planet.
Geez, go do that somewhere else!
What should we do? This is no time to be treasure hunting!
Let's go back to the Gokai Galleon for now.
Walz Gil-sama! Please enjoy the methods of me, Force Commander Shikabanen
It's gonna be okay!
There's no use running!
What's the matter?
You're not getting away!
Let the children go!
Aren't we going?
I don't wanna to say it...
...but there may not be a future for this planet.
And... it'll become part of the empire's territory.
Just like what happened to our hometown...
Nice face! It's thrills me!
Show me more fear!
I don't like it.
Thanks for the sweet face.
Who's there!?
So, you're the wanted pirates.
What in the heck are you doing here?
Who knows?
I guess you're on some boring treasure hunt.
I'll let you off the hook, so get out of my way.
Shut it, ya dummy!
D-dummy!?
It's you who'll disappear.
I have no interest in listening to what you have to say.
Me too. I hate guys like you!
Are you idiots insane!?
We are the Space Empire Zangyack!
Do you know what will happen if you turn against us?
We know.
However, if we don't like something, we'll kick your butt.
That's what it means to be a pirate.
Gokai Change!
Gokaiger!
GokaiRed!
GokaiBlue!
GokaiYellow!
GokaiGreen!
GokaiPink!
Kaizoku Sentai Gokaiger!
Let's go out with a bang!
Gormin, get 'em!
It can't be...the 35th Super Sentai!?
Move!
Doc!
Ahim!
Duly noted!
I'm not done yet!
Jeez! It's getting crowded.
Give them "that".
"That"...
That, it is!
A splendid idea!
Gokai Change!
GoRanger!
Teacher, what's that?
The first Super Sentai formed on Earth.
Himitsu Sentai GoRanger, right!?
But how!?
GoRanger Hurricane! Approaching!
Goranger Hurricane: Gomi-Sensousha!
(Garbage Truck)
Doctor-san!
Got it!
Luka!
Joe!
Marvelous!
End Ball!
Jeez, they're persistent!
Gokai Change!
Shinkenger!
MagiRanger!
Gii Magika
Thatt was an interesting spectacle, but I'm getting sick of it.
See ya!
Kill him.
Right.
Final Wave!
Well, we did it.
We have completely turned the Empire into an enemy.
I guess so.
What shall we do?
This is bad, Marvelous! We have to leave Earth as soon as possible!
What is it?
Thank you!
Thank you so much for saving us!
What are you saying?
We are space pirates. We're just here for a treasure hunt.
Then why did you fight against them!?
Because...
Because of the curry rice.
Our food was ruined, and we were pissed off.
It's what it is.
Therefore, there is no reason for you to thank us.
Super Sentai!
Fly! Cross over the endless time
tobidase! eien no toki wo koe
The strongest warriors are on parade!
saikyou senshi on parade
All five assembled are the GoRangers
gonin sorotte goranger
JAKQ were trump themed cyborgs
jakka trump cyborg
Battle Fever's worldwide dance
battle fever sekai no dance
From the Planet Denji, Denjiman
denjisei kara denjiman
1 + 2 + Sun Vulcan
ichi tasu ni tasu sun vulcan
Goggle Five doing rhythmic gymnastics
goggle five de shintaisou
Explode! Explode! Dynaman
bakuhatsu bakuhatsu dynaman
The bio-particles of Bioman
bio-ryushi no bioman
Changeman were legendary beasts
changeman wa densetsu-jyuu
Flash, a cosmic supernova
flash uchuu no choshinsei
It's a glowing aura, Maskman
hikaru aura da maskman
Friends, why did you... Liveman
tomoyo doshite!? liveman
I want to sing it! I want to remember it!
utaitai zettai obetemiitai
Super Sentai let's go!
Shine the brightest...
ichiban kagayaku
...and find the treasure! Let's go pirates!
otakara sagase let's go pirates!
There's more, it's not enough!
motto mada mada
I want to see it all one step at a time
mitemitainda ippo mae he!
The exciting Kaizoku Sentai
uuu waku waku kaizoku sentai
(Go Let's Go!) Gokaiger!
Next time on Episode 2...
Try looking for someone dressed in black!
You've got no intention of protecting the Earth, do you!?
Nope.
The Worth of This Planet
Episode 2
We're just looking for something.