Come on!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
I'm going to complete missions today too!
Let's go!
Enter the new chapter!
It's the Chuunin exam.
Enter the new chapter, It's the Chuunin exam.
Oh.
Good morning, Sakura-chan.
Oh, not again!
These two...
They've been sort of strange since
we got back from the Land of Waves.
Ugh, it's almost uncomfortable.
Hurry up and get here Kakashi Sensei!
Damn it!
Hello everybody. Good morning.
I got lost today, so.
You're late!
Hey, hey...
Kakashi Sensei!
We the 7th squad have only been doing easy missions, right?
Aren't there more exciting missions where I can be more active,
where I can use my way of the Ninja and my soul, you know?
Ah, yes yes yes yes...
I basically understand what you're trying to say.
Damn it!
He's always making me indebted to him and making himself look good during our missions.
I'm not going to lose to you.
This guy...
Today...
Really, you're a guy that needs help all the time.
That's what I'd like to say!
Hey Naruto, what are you doing? We have a mission.
Okay!
You're noisy!
I'm not gonna lose to Sasuke.
Hey, you.
Oh, Miss.
I've gotten rid of all the weeds.
What's wrong?
Those aren't weeds.
Those are herbs I've been cultivating!
Ouch!
Somebody... help...!
No way! Free fall!
You idiot.
Hey.
Trap field
Do not enter
Don't go over there.
Hey, please stop!
That idiot.
Ah, that's because he stubbornly chose that big dog.
Hey, hey. Wait, wait a minute.
That's the trap field over there.
This is what you get for being reckless.
You're a guy that needs help all the time.
Sasuke!
If you act up again I'll finish you!
Teamwork hasn't been good lately.
That's right, that's right!
You're the one that disrupts our teamwork, Sasuke!
You're always attracting attention!
That's you, idiot.
If you don't want to owe me anything.
Become stronger than me.
It seems like they're getting along worse than before.
Damn it, this pisses me off.
There are plenty of guys out there who are stronger than I am.
Always making me go on this stupid missions.
Well then...
Perhaps we should disperse.
I have to to submit a report about this mission.
Then, I'm going home.
Hey, Sasuke-kun, wait for me!
Hey, how about...
Why don't you and...
Why don't we work on improving our teamwork together?
You're just like Naruto.
JUST LIKE NARUTO.
If you have time to spend on me, why don't you practice a Jutsu.
To be honest, your abilities are less than Naruto's.
LESS THAN NARUTO.
Less than Naruto! Less than Naruto!
That's right.
It's always that way for me during every mission.
I'll never be able to really do anything at all.
Sakura-chan! Just let Sasuke be, let's train together.
Sensei disappeared.
Was he being thoughtful?
Is that supposed to be a rock?
There's no such thing as a perfectly square rock with perfect holes!
It's totally obvious!
Just what you'd expect from the man I respect.
You're my rival, aren't you.
Hey, that's too much gunpowder.
With an adult sexiness.
I'm Moegi of the senior class at Kunoichi Preschool.
I love factoring.
Udon.
The most genius Ninja in the village, Konohamaru!
The three of us together are
the Konohamaru Corps!
Here we are!
I knew it was Konohamaru and friends.
Why are you all wearing goggles?
We copied the old you.
Oh?
What's with the oh? Your reactions have been pretty cold these days.
So, did you want something?
See? Cold.
So, leader. Do you have some free time now?
Nope.
I have to train.
What?! You said you'd play Ninja with us today!
Oh...? Is that right?
Geez... If I played with these guys they would make me hang out all day.
Why would a Ninja play Ninja?
W-What is it?
So, abilities less than this guy, huh?
Staring at me like at embarrasses me.
Hey, who is this girl?
She's been staring at him with eyes like she's gonna kill him.
You've been busier than I thought.
Huh?
Is she your...?
This?
You kids are pretty sharp.
No way!
Naruto!
What are you doing?!
oh, no... Leader!
His pulse, his pulse is!
You ugly girl! Ugly!
Are you okay, Konohamaru-kun?
Ouch.
Damn that big foreheaded ugly girl, is she really a girl?
That hurt.
Eh?
So, I have received the report from you.
Is Naruto getting along with the others?
Well, he's doing okay.
I've been busy lately.
I haven't had a chance to see him even once since his return.
I'm a little worried.
As you know, Iruka Sensei,
Uchiha Sasuke is also in our squad,
and Naruto sees him as a rival,
which is a little straining.
But, the result is that his abilities are developing significantly.
Almost to the point that he might reach yours, the one he respects.
I see...
I wonder what it is?
Damn it, right now?
These guys...
Konohamaru!
That hurt, brat!
Stop It. We'll get scolded later.
I'm sorry, I was just fooling around.
Who are these two?
Hey! Let go of that hand!
So these are Genins of Konoha.
Let's play with them before some noisy people come.
Let go!
You're pretty lively, brat.
Why you...
What was that?
Konoha's Genins are weaker than I thought.
These guys are foreign.
Why are they here?
Konohamaru.
Konohamaru-chan!
Konohamaru-kun!
It... it hurts...
Hey! If you don't let go of him, I won't forgive you! You Idiot!
You're the Idiot!
What are you gonna do by getting him worked up?
You're pissing me off.
I hate short people anyway, and you're so impertinent for someone younger than me.
It makes me want to destroy you.
It's not on me.
What's with this guy? He's dangerous.
Well, after this little brat, the short brat over there is next.
Stop!
What do you think you're doing in someone else's Village?
Sasuke-kun!
He's pretty handsome.
Bro.
Another brat to piss me off.
Get lost.
Wow, so cool!
Naruto, you're so lame.
S-Stupid. I would've beaten him too.
Liar!
Sasuke, you!
Why are you always, always interfering like this.
Hey, come down here you brat!
You're the kind of smart ass brat that I despise the most.
Wait! You aren't thinking of using Karasu are you?!
Kankuro, stop.
You're an embarrassment to our village.
G-Gaara...
When did he get next to me?
He was as quiet as Kakashi.
There is no other reason to summon you here other than...
As I assume you already understand based on the faces you can see around.
So it's already that time.
The other Lands have already been notified, right?
I've seen them here and there in the village.
Then, when will it be?
In a week.
That's very sudden.
Then, I will make the formal announcement.
Seven days from today...
On the first day of July, the Chuunin Exams will begin!
♪ Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
♪ Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
♪ Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
♪ Break into the contents, never falling down.
♪ My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve,
♪ Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
♪ A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
♪ Waiting is wasting for people like me.
♪ Don't try to live so wise.
♪ Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
♪ Don't dry with fakes or fears,
♪ 'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
♪ Don't try to live so wise.
♪ Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
♪ Don't dry with fakes or fears,
♪ 'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
♪ Don't try to live so wise.
♪ Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
♪ Don't dry....