Come on!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
Damn! It's been a while since
I've fought in such bad conditions.
And I'm worried about Sasuke and Naruto too.
Stay calm, Think...
Where will he strike?
Oh no!
Too late!
The broken seal
The broken seal.
That was Sakura's voice!
Did something happen?
What's that Kakashi doing?
Sa... kura...
Damn it, I must do something.
I'll do something about it.
T-This guy...
Here I go.
It's pointless to struggle.
Naruto, behind you!
Naruto!
It's impossible for you to get out of here.
Absolutely.
Can you stand up, Naruto?
Y-Yeah.
From now on don't waste your Chakra!
You're playing right into his hands.
I know.
Damn it!
If things continue like this it's going to be really bad.
I...
I have to do something.
My eyes are getting used to his movement...
It's about the time I put an end to this.
What?
Stand up you idiot!
I'm aiming for a vital spot,
but he's parrying all of them.
I know...
You're so persistent!
A coincidence...
No, that's not it.
On the contrary, he's fighting while covering for his friend.
Surely my movements...
That boy... he can see something.
What in the world?
Okay, in that case.
He disappeared.
Where, where did he disappear to?!
Naruto! Don't faint!
I can't cover for you any more than I am now!
Who asked you to cover for me.
It seems that kid has reached his limits.
Amazing,
that's an amazing move.
You move well.
But I'll stop you with the next one.
Motor function.
Reflexes, ability to judge a situation.
All of these things should be at their limits!
He's coming!
Calm down.
Focus.
And... See everything.
He saw through everything?!
No way.
Those eyes...
It can't be...
Sharingan.
You are...
Only a little, but...
I saw it.
So you also have the power of a Kekkei Genkai.
What a kid...
It's not perfect yet,
but to think that in the middle of a battle
he was able to awaken his power.
If that's the case, I can't fight him much more.
This Jutsu uses a lot of Chakra.
There are also limits to retaining the teleportation speed.
Besides, the longer the fight continues,
then more my movements will be read by him.
In fact, his eyes have already captured me.
It would be foolish to aim straight at him.
In that case...
I'll use that kid to lure him in!
What?!
Let me make it in time!
Kakashi Sensei!
You were late to guard yourself Kakashi.
Your whole hearted intent to help
those kids has gone to your head,
and it seems to have clouded your Sharingan with even heavier fog.
Even though you have those impressive eyes,
your ability to read your enemy's
movements is getting cloudy.
Entertain me some more, Kakashi.
I want to repay my debt in an amusing way.
Don't worry.
Anytime now Haku is going to defeat those kids.
You better apologize to them in tears when you are in the next world for your lack of strength.
Sasuke-kun will be defeated?
That's not true.
Sasuke-kun is...
Damn!
Not by that guy!
He won't be defeated!
DAMN!
Naruto won't either!
That's right.
I... believe in their strength.
Naruto is the Number One Hyperactive Knucklehead Ninja.
And Sasuke is...
from Konoha's most superior clan.
That can't be!
Yes, his name is Uchiha Sasuke.
He possesses the Kekkei Genkai of the Uchiha clan.
He's a Ninja genius.
He's the remaining survivor of that tragic clan?!
No wonder he advances so quickly.
But...
The same goes for Haku.
Nobody has ever beaten that secret Jutsu of Haku's.
Not one person in the past.
Well then.
It's about time I settled this too.
Sakura, don't move from here.
Uh... ah... okay!
I'm going to put an end to this!
For god's sake, you...
just won't quit dragging my feet, will you?
You did it!
Sasuke.
W-What kind of expression is that?
You... idiot...!
W-Why?!
You protected me?!
How the hell should I know?
Sasuke...! Sasuke! Sasuke!
You...
I hated you...
Why? Why?
Why... me...?
I didn't ask for your help!
I don't know.
My body moved of its own accord...
Idiot.
Sasuke!
That man.
Until I've defeated... my brother.
I absolutely refuse to die.
That's what I decided, but...
You, don't die.
He...
To protect someone dear to him...
he would jump in knowing it was a trap.
He's a Shinobi worthy of respect.
Is this the first time you faced a friend's death?
This is the way of the Shinobi.
Shut up.
Even though I...
hated you too.
I won't forgive you.
I'm going to kill you!
What is this Chakra?!
It can't be...
For Chakra to be taking on a form.
And... what a terrible Chakra.
The wound on his hand...
It's healing instantly.
This boy...
Who in hell is he?
Is it Zabuza?
No!
This sinister Chakra was once...
It can't be!
What is this Chakra?
It feels unpleasant.
Kakashi?
No, it's too big to be Kakashi's.
Who is it?
Naruto!
Oh no.
At a time like this...
The seal has broken?
I have to hurry.
He's coming!
♪ Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
♪ Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
♪ Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
♪ Break into the contents, never falling down.
♪ My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve,
♪ Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
♪ A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
♪ Waiting is wasting for people like me.
♪ Don't try to live so wise.
♪ Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
♪ Don't dry with fakes or fears,
♪ 'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
♪ Don't try to live so wise.
♪ Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
♪ Don't dry with fakes or fears,
♪ 'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
♪ Don't try to live so wise.
♪ Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
♪ Don't dry....