N-Now this was unexpected!
That took all of one minute!
And yet AR-D and RM-C were still
able to make a powerful statement!
They got totally owned, didn't they?
That wall of light.
That's gonna be trouble.
It's going to take an extraordinary
assault to get through that one.
Excuse me.
Did you see that match just now?
Saw it.
Those puppets are controlling
over five Manadites concurrently.
That's beyond a human's control,
but artificial intelligence can handle it!
Hey, hold up, Dad.
Is that Uncle Souichi, by any chance?
Hey, is that you, Ayato?
It's been a long time!
Long time no see!
So Dad, what's up?
Right, I sent you a new gun.
Did you get it?
Nope, not yet.
Meaning that it won't get there
in time for your first match.
Could you go over to Customs to check?
Okay. But it won't be a problem.
I've got the Arcwandels, so I'll be fine.
Of course you can!
As long as you're wielding
one of my guns, you can't lose!
Okay, I'll be waiting to hear
good news from you!
He hasn't changed one bit, huh?
Yeah. I'll be heading out to Customs, then.
Then I'll go with you!
I'm gonna see if I can sneak
into their press conference.
What should we do?
Raise a glass to our first victory.
Actually, we can't afford to rest
on our laurels like that, can we?
Why don't we get a little practice in?
Roger that!
Hey, hey!
Good job, you two!
That was a great performance!
You are too kind, Master.
Well, what else could you expect, right?
What kind of attitude
is that before our master?
You should be ashamed.
RM-C, are you serious?
Of course I am.
There's no need to hold back against
anyone who disrespects our master.
Now, now, why don't you
let him off the hook now, RM-C?
Very well.
Master, I have a question.
Sure, what is it?
In terms of specs, we're more or less equal,
so why is it that I'm helpless against RM-C?
Oh, well, that can't be helped!
As the saying goes,
"Woman is Nature's contrivance for
perpetuating its highest achievement...
whereas Man is Woman's contrivance for fulfilling
Nature's behest in the most economical way."
People had such a way with
words in the olden days!
Meaning that because I am a male-type,
I can never defeat RM-C, a female-type?
It would appear so.
But anyway, we should
head back to our waiting room,
or Camilla will get tired of waiting.
Well, then, I suppose it can't be helped.
Well, of course I can't tell you
that RM-C's your limiter, can I?
The Tyrant Vampire Princess
Let's get going!
Wait, hold up a second!
We're not gonna get there in time
for the start of the match anyway,
so I'll let them know
that we're running late.
Right...
It's not your fault, Julis.
I wanted to practice
till the last second, too.
Take that!
What's that? A scuffle?
That's...
Irene Urzaiz.
You know her?
She's a Page One at Le Wolfe.
Jeez, settling old scores
is a relic of the past!
Shut up!
If we don't, we'll lose face!
So annoying!
Hey! This isn't a sideshow!
AYATO AMAGIRI
SEIDOUKAN ACADEMY
Just as I thought.
If it isn't Murakumo...
What do you want with
my tag partner, Lamirexia?
Glühen Rose, huh?
I have no business
with you. Take a hike.
I can't do that.
Since brawling in the middle of
a crowd is beyond dangerous.
They're the ones who started
that fight just now.
Remember where you are!
One false move, and
you could be disqualified!
H-Hey, Julis!
All right, then, why don't you
tell me what you would do?
You reacted better than
I thought you would.
Hey, you!
Oh, crap!
Really, Sister!
Fighting without permission
again! Seriously!
P-Priscilla!
I'm so sorry!
My sister's caused you so much trouble.
Oh, no, it's not like...
All right, Sister! You apologize, too!
W-Why should I?
Come on!
I'm truly sorry!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Uh, right...
I'll be sure to give her an earful.
All right, let's go, Sister.
Okay, okay...
She called her "Sister,"
so does that mean...
I think there's an entry
in the data Claudia sent me.
PRISCILLA URZAIZ
LE WOLFE ACADEMY
Priscilla Urzaiz.
She's unranked,
and there isn't a shred of data on her
except that she's Irene's partner.
By the way, why did you
provoke her like that just now?
Irene said to me, "I have
no business with you."
Even though I was the one
who made the complaint against her!
Meaning that she had some
kind of reason to target you.
But I don't even know her.
Knowing Le Wolfe, they could very well
have something evil up their sleeve.
I wanted to fish around
for some clues, but...
Right.
What's wrong?
Saya and Kirin's match...
It's already started!
Just listen to the roar of the crowd!
And no wonder!
She might've just lost
her title the other day,
but Ms. Toudou of Seidoukan
Academy is the Super Rookie
who reached Rank #1
as a junior high student!
Oh, wow!
Apparently, despite her slight stature,
she's got an air of perfect composure...
Nanna-yan, Nanna-yan...
that one's Ms. Toudou!
The little one is Saya Sasamiya!
For real?
She's in high school?
Well, someone's screwed!
Now that was a huge blunder...
...beyond offensive.
And Ayato isn't here, either.
They said they're on their way.
But anyway...
They look quite competent, don't they?
Well, we'll figure it out.
34-type Wave Motion Heavy Gun,
Modified Arcwandels!
Which do you want to take on?
Whichever one, I don't mind.
Then I'll take the bigger one.
Roger that.
Phoenix Festa, Block L,
Round 1, Match 2...
Let the battle begin!
Badge broken.
Well, that was over fast!
The winner of this fleeting
battle is Ms. Toudou!
Nanna-yan! The little one's
putting on a good show herself!
What's going on here?
Burst.
And it's over!
Winners, Saya Sasamiya and
Kirin Toudou of Seidoukan Academy!
V.
So it's not as if the gun is just hard?
Right.
I've adapted it to use it as an energy field
to suppress some of the output.
So that's why you were able to
withstand all that close combat.
Yeah.
But it's not as if you're a student of
the Amagiri Shinmei-style, right?
I watch and learn.
But yeah, Ayato did teach me a little.
I'm heading out now.
Oh, wait, you should
dry yourself off properly!
Wh-What is it?
What... what... what are you doing?
Since ancient times, they say that
massaging increasing the size of your breasts.
That couldn't be more wrong!
No fair.
But what can I do?
Sorry we got here late.
W-We're very sorry, but
could you please wait just a bit?
You're finally here, huh?
We really are sorry, but the match...
We won.
DAY 5
All righty! Day 5 of the Phoenix Festa!
Round 2 starts today!
Now, then...
I left everything to you in Round 1.
So now it's my turn!
Gotcha!
Hello, everybody!
We are from Queenvail,
the school for goddesses!
Ranked #37 and 54!
They call us Non-sugar!
All of you... thank you!
We're going to do our best!
All right, let the battle begin!
Let's go!
Flame of Torokia,
scale the castle walls...
Burn down the Nine Scourges...
Burst into bloom, Primrose!
Badge broken.
Even I'm capable of this much...
Come out... Semiserata!
End of match!
Ms. Riessfeld has seized victory
through her rock-solid tactical game!
Even as she attacked,
she was luring her opponent
into a setting-type trap, huh?
Well, I guess that does it.
Good job, Julis.
Well, not that I fought long enough
for it to feel like a job.
By the way, what are your
plans for the rest of the day?
If I could, I'd like to go to Saya and
Kirin's match to cheer them on, but...
By the time we reach the venue,
it will be over, probably.
A-And besides, we still
haven't had lunch, right?
Okay, then let's get that
out of the way real quick...
Julis?
Actually, I... Um...
Sandwiches, huh?
Th-They're exceedingly simple.
Don't get your hopes up too high!
W-Well?
It's really good, Julis!
You don't say!
So you cook, too, Julis. I had no idea.
W-Well, this much I can handle.
Aren't you having any, Julis?
Well, of course I will, but...
I don't like being treated
unfairly, you know.
Unfairly?
Well, you know, uh...
To do it for Sasamiya and
Toudou, and not for me...
That just doesn't
stand to reason, does it?
Well, it's not as if I absolutely
need you do it, but...
Uh, by any chance...
Uh, you too, Julis?
Okay, then... Excuse me...
I-I know!
Why don't we see how
the other matches turned out?
Run, Randy!
Oh...
Their match was today, too?
All right, first to strike is
the Lester-Randy team!
Both Lester and Randy are keeping
their distance from Irene...
What could their purpose be, I wonder?
The Gravi-Sheath is a powerful Ogre Lux
with the ability to control gravity.
But since it's apparently the type of weapon
that's effective against targeted locations,
I believe they're trying to avoid being subjected
to those effects by constantly moving.
And the Gravi-Sheath's most glaring flaw
is that it's a gas-guzzler!
They say that no student has ever
been able to withstand its side-effects.
In other words, the longer we drag this
fight out, the greater our advantage!
And while we're buying time...
Let's see what this girl's made of!
Every last one of you... springing
the same tired old strategy on me!
Randy!
I'm telling you, that's so pedestrian!
I'll get to you later.
Come back here, you...
Do you give up?
Yeah, right!
I see.
Rendered unconscious.
Okay, that's one.
Hey, you're just as tough as I thought!
Raging Axe of Distant Thunder.
Who do you think you're dealing with?
Take that, bitch!
Blast Nemea!
Sister!
How do you like that?
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Damn... guess I have no choice.
In recognition of your skills,
I'm going to show you
what it's like when I go all out.
What?
Sister...
My bad.
I'm taking a little.
What the heck is going on?
Most likely, that kid sister
must be a Regenerative.
Regenerative...
Someone with the power
to heal her own wounds?
Right. And if she's even capable of
regenerating lost blood, she's elite.
That's an unheard-of secret weapon.
See, the Gravi-Sheath...
It seeks blood in return for its powers.
With normal use, it drains
itself dry before you know it.
That's why it alters its wielder's
body, like you just saw,
allowing it to absorb blood
from an external source.
So you're literally a vampire, huh?
Now then, shall we?!
Go!
What the...
Oh, I intensified the gravity a little.
You can't escape!
If you want to catch my gravity balls,
at the very least you'll have to
bring an Ogre Lux with you!
Damn!
All right, you still want to fight?
Raging Axe of Distant Thunder?
All right.
I lose.
End of match!
Hey, MacPhail's flabbergasted.
Although we got ourselves an easy win.
Episode 11 - Power and Its Price
But listen, you guys, he's still a Page One.
He's really powerful.
He was just overmatched.
No, I mean, he just didn't
match up well with them.
Let's just leave it at that, all right?