Naruto is over here...
That thing is not human...
Sai, what are you doing?
Got it.
Continue to observe.
Sakura!
That's...Naruto...
Naruto!
That's...
I can't pierce through...
even with my snake sword...
This is what Master Jiraiya
was referring to when he said...
he's "like a small Nine-Tailed Beast."
Sakura's Tears
This is not like a Ninja battle,
but more like
a battle between monsters...
Naruto...
It's useless to go on fighting
with the snake sword...
What's the situation like?
Is Naruto dead?
Look at that...
I wonder if he still wants
to save Sasuke...
even in that state.
I am going to take back Sasuke,
no matter what!
It's my lifelong promise!
Sakura! I...will keep my promise,
no matter what!
To stand firm with what I say...
That's my Way of the Ninja...
By now, even his self-consciousness
is gone...
What a sad kid...
Wait! Sakura!
Don't get close to Naruto
in that state!
Naruto!
That's...that's enough!
I will save Sasuke, no matter what!
That's why...
Naruto, it's enough...!
Not good!
What is he trying to do?
Now is my chance...
Looks like it's about time...
As expected,
this body is rejecting me.
Too bad, but the fun ends here.
Patience... Patience now...
I have Sasuke with me...
Oh, uh...
Damn!
I didn't make it in time...
I won't let you step in.
You're rushing to conclusions.
I don't plan to fight you guys
anymore.
Actually... it's the opposite.
What do you mean?
We both have the same goal.
The Akatsuki are in the way.
If I let you live...
I think you might
just get rid of one more Akatsuki.
Naruto...
The wounds are healing
much slower than I expected...
but I can't stay
playing "volunteer" for long.
Lord Orochimaru is also
reaching his limit.
In exchange for helping you...
please get rid of as many
of the Akatsuki as you can...
That said, that is your teammate...
Take care of the rest.
It's time to leave, huh?
Now's the only chance...!
I am Danzo's man.
I am not your enemy...
I have something
to speak to you about.
Hokage Style: Elder Jutsu
10th Edict on Enlightenment!
Naruto...
Danzo...that doddering old fool
is still alive, huh?
So...
What do you want to talk about?
I have a message from Danzo
to Lord Orochimaru.
The truth is...
Before that...
Choose your words carefully
when you talk to me.
If not, you'll die.
I can only relay
what Danzo has told me.
If that does not satisfy you,
then I'll leave it up to you...