That's not fair!
You're easily using the Rasengan
even though it's my secret technique!
And I had such a rough time enduring
the Pervy Sage's harsh training.
Listen...
- We're just getting to the main issue...
- And you can do it just like that.
And with one hand at that...
And all I can do is spin it around
into shape with a clone...
Man, this is too much trouble...
Let me try.
Well, let's wait for him to
calm down a little more.
I didn't show you the Rasengan because
I wanted to brag about it or anything.
Yeah, right.
I told you the Rasengan is a Jutsu
with only the Change in Chakra Form
taken to the extreme, right?
Change in Chakra Form...?
And... a Jutsu with the Change in Chakra Nature
added to the Change in Chakra Form...
For example... Chidori.
Oh, more bragging, huh?
Not only does this Jutsu use the Change in Chakra
Nature to shift the Chakra Nature into lightning...
but it also uses Change in Chakra Form
to transform it
into an electrical discharge
and control its range and power.
Listen up. When you take Chakra and add in
Change in Chakra Form and Change in Chakra Nature...
the attack power of a Shinobi
rises dramatically.
Well, there are hardly any Shinobi who can use
both Change in Chakra Form and Nature, though.
I knew it. You're bragging.
You obtained the wind Change
in Chakra Nature in your training earlier.
And you already possess
the ultimate Change in Chakra Form.
Rasengan...
That's right.
Then that means...
I already have both?
Well...that's pretty much the case.
All right! Then it looks like I'll be able
to get a new Jutsu just like that!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
This is going to be a cinch!
If it were that easy, it wouldn't have been
necessary for me to develop the Chidori.
I wasn't able to combine
the Rasengan Change in Chakra Form
with my lightning Change in Chakra Nature.
Phenomenal technique is necessary to combine the
Change in Chakra Nature with the Change in Chakra Form.
Well, it might be better to say one needs
a phenomenal "ability" or "sense."
I wasn't the only one who
was not able to get this far.
It was the same even for
the teacher who invented this Jutsu.
Teacher?
That's right...
Even the Fourth Hokage
couldn't do it.
The Fourth Hokage took the Change in
Chakra Form to the highest possible level.
And that's the Rasengan.
Just a Change in Chakra Form
has an A-rank difficulty level.
Even I can somehow copy it
if it's just to this degree.
The problem is what comes after that.
The Fourth Hokage originally
developed the Rasengan
intending to add his own
Change in Chakra Nature to it.
Then that means the Rasengan
was a Ninjutsu still being developed?
That's pretty much the case.
Any Jutsu beyond that would be an S-rank
difficulty level or maybe even higher.
Furthermore,
it might be impossible to begin with...
I won't be able to teach you
what comes next.
You'll have to discover it for yourself.
Do you know... Do you know why
I'm telling you this, Naruto?
It's because
I believe you're the only Shinobi...
who can surpass the Fourth Hokage.
Well... That's enough talk for now.
I guess we'll start up training again
after a bit more rest.
Just what I'd expect from you, Kakashi.
Sure enough, you are a slick talker.
No...
I really do believe in him.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
The Next Step
Lady Tsunade!
We have received a message
from Team Asuma!
It seems...the two Akatsuki
are heading for a Collection Office.
Of the locations...
the nearest Collection Office is...
We're close!
At any moment...
we're going to fight the Akatsuki.
It'll be okay, Ino.
There's nothing to be afraid of as long as
we do as Asuma Sensei taught us.
Right.
Just kidding. Shikamaru said that
to me on a previous mission.
Choji...
Shikamaru's doing his best, too.
We've got to keep it together.
Asuma Sensei...
What kind of relationship did
you have with that Chiriku guy?
What's the deal all of a sudden?
A heavy smoker like you
hasn't smoked in two whole days.
You always stop smoking...
when something has happened.
You're so observant...
I'm far too soft if you can see
right through to my heart like that.
Well, I can always tell
what move you're going to make
when we play Shogi.
You haven't looked like this since
the Third Hokage passed away.
You know that Chiriku and I
were fellow members
of the Guardian Shinobi Twelve, right?
I guess you could say...
we were like you and Choji.
You won't stop smoking for long.
I won't stop smoking for long...huh?
Indeed, that's how it's gone until now.
Shikamaru, I appreciate you
worrying about me.
But I didn't stop smoking
because of Chiriku.
More importantly, the guys from Akatsuki
are good enough to kill Chiriku.
They probably have
a great deal of skill.
Stay sharp!
Okay, form the Rasengan
in teams of two.
And at the same time,
incorporate the wind Change in
Chakra Nature into the Rasengan.
Well, it's easy to say...
but I can't concretely tell you
to do this or that.
Naruto, you just have to think about it
and grasp this on your own.
Okay...shall we begin?
Right!
Create a "wind Change in Chakra Nature"
...with my Wind Chakra!
That being said...
how do we do that while creating
a Rasengan Change in Chakra Form?!
That's what I want to know!
Damn it!
That's reckless...
He just finished cutting the waterfall.
At just a time like this...
Umm...I could just say nothing.
But I'll be honest with you...
These food pills are really awful.
What?!
They're not awful!
I got creative with this...
so they'd be easy to consume...
What...?!
Then I'll eat one, okay?
I knew it...
Sure enough, he's quick to tire when
using his Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Damn it...
Let's go!
Right!
Incorporate wind Chakra into this.
Damn it!
This is impossible.
And here I need a ton of concentration
just for the Rasengan.
And then having to add
the Change in Chakra Nature to that...
It's like saying look to the left
and right at the same time.
Damn it!
This isn't the time to be throwing
in the towel already!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
H-Hey, where are you going?!
The bathroom?!
I guess it can't be helped.
We'll take a leak together.
This is the Collection Office.
Why put a secret door in a bathroom?
This way.
Put it here.
Okay.
Hurry up and get it done!
No doubt about it.
It is Chiriku.
You got yourself a big one
this time, Kakuzu.
Yeah...
Hey, this place stinks.
Let's get going, Kakuzu.
Wait. I'm going to count the money.
I'm never coming to a place
like this again.
I can't tell if the stench is
from the piss or the corpses.
I'll be outside.
We're almost...
at the Collection Office...
It's almost time...
Let's get ready.
It's all here.
I'll be counting on you...
for the next one, sir.
Sorry, but I won't be back for a while.
We're going to the Hidden Leaf
to look for a Jinchuriki.
Let me give you some advice.
You should ditch that partner of yours.
He doesn't seem interested in money.
I know that. Indeed, he has
no interest in money.
But nobody else is capable
of being my partner.
There's a reason for that.
A reason, huh?
Everyone else who teamed up
with me is dead.
When I have trouble with a partner,
I end up wanting to kill them.
But I can't kill him.
That's the reason.
Concentrate...
Like grinding
the two Chakra together...
Hey! Tenzo!
I know.
Naruto...
If Naruto keeps doing this, he'll...
And I can't keep stopping that
over and over again...
- I can't...
- No... This is the only way.
Whether or not his Jutsu
is completed rides on you.
I understand...
The Akatsuki...are up ahead.
Let's go!
Ohh, it stinks!
Being in a crap hole like that for five minutes
would soak my clothes in the stench.
Took you long enough, Kakuzu.