Tales of a Gutsy Ninja -
Jiraiya Ninja Scrolls - Part 1
There are two bells...
The fact that there are
only two bells means...
One person will lose...
You're very sharp, Orochimaru.
Say! If I get a bell,
you'll go out with me.
If you lose,
don't bother me anymore.
All right! I'll do it!
So many openings...
Now!
I won the bet, Jiraiya!
You get to go to the log.
Shut up, flat-chested plywood Tsunade!
What'd you say?!
You egg-headed perv!!
Now, now. That's enough...
Tsunade and Orochimaru may go.
Okay!
You are hopeless...
How can a ninja keep falling
into such obvious traps?!
Can't help it...
Perhaps what you lack
is a purpose...
Huh?!
Let's see now...
Yes! We'll try this!
Wh-What?!
Don't get so excited. Just watch.
Ninja Art: Summoning Jutsu!
Awesome!
The Summoning Jutsu...
You make a blood contract with an animal,
and summon them at will using the Transportation Technique.
I want to make a contract
with that one too!
That, you can't do.
Huh?
In the same way that every man is destined to a different fate,
so too is the animal to whom he is intertwined.
Then which is my animal?
Before you can make a contract,
you need to be more adept at molding chakra and sealing.
What? Not more training!
You will always find the answer
in your training!
Jiraiya had found a purpose and from that day on,
he began taking his training seriously. However...
Mold more chakra...
Study up on sealing...
I must master
the Transportation Technique...
Dammit!
When will I be able to
make a contract?
Why do I put up with
this rough training?
If I were to have a boyfriend,
I'd choose Orochimaru over an egghead perv like you.
The answer is simple!
I just have to become the ultimate ninja
and sweep Tsunade off her feet!
Now that that's settled,
there's no time to waste!
Ah...
So he's discovered his purpose
for becoming a ninja.
And not just Tsunade,
I'm gonna get all the pretty girls to myself.
Let's see...
Concentrate my chakra and...
the seal is boar, dog,
bird, monkey, sheep...
Wait! There's no telling what will happen if you use the
Transportation Technique without making a contract first!
Go!
Where am I...?
Hold it right there!
I, the great Master Jiraiya,
shall take over this fight!
Heh! I guess that'll do!
Hmmm...
A human child.
Huh?! A-A talking toad!
And what about you?
To think, a human would really come to Mount Myoboku...
What do you mean?!
Lord Fukasaku!
It's a human child.
Oh...so you've arrived.
You talk as though
you've been expecting me.
Yes, I knew you were coming.
The Great Lord Elder predicted it.
A human child will stumble
into Mount Myoboku,
and I will give that child the power
of the toad and a prophecy.
That is the dream which
I dreamt of myself...
My very own prophecy.
If that human is me...
then what is my prophecy?!
Well... I don't know.
Don't know?
You must stay here and train,
and wait for the Great Lord Elder's prophecy.
H-Hold it!
I made up my mind to become strong
so that I'll be popular with women...
There's no point in getting popular
with frogs!
Quit complaining!
This is your destiny.
My destiny?!
Yes. You managed to come
to Mount Myoboku.
This is proof that you were indeed
the chosen one.
The chosen one, eh?
Training here and becoming strong...
That's pretty tempting too.
From this day forward,
Jiraiya divided his time between
Mount Myoboku, the land of toads,
and the Hidden Leaf Village...
He spent the days of his youth
in both Sage and ninjutsu training.
However...
It was not to be as simple as
Jiraiya had thought.
I've definitely gotten stronger
since coming here.
But...
Tsunade is as cold as ever.
Not just that...
If I was destined to be the chosen one,
should my purpose simply be to impress a girl?
Is that the only reason why
I'm trying to become strong?
Jiraiya! Jiraiya!
Yeah?
Jiraiya, the Great Lord Elder
has summoned you.
The Great Lord Elder...?
Hurry up.
He has seen your prophecy!
For real, Bunta?!
As summoned.
Ah, good. I'm glad you've come!
Huh?
Who're you again?
Great Lord Elder, it's Jiraiya!
This is Jiraiya!
Oh, that's right! Right!
My, how you've grown...
Gah, you're the one who summoned him,
ya great senile old geezer!
Senile old geezer?!
Ma, how dare ya call
the Great Lord Elder a senile old geezer!
Now now, let's not fight.
Spouses oughta get along...
By the way...
Who're you, again?
Jiraiya-boy.
The Great Lord Elder had
a dream about you.
As you are aware,
it is a prophecy.
So listen carefully.
Yes, sir!
I shall now tell you.
In my dream...
you, who are solely pervy, will still
manage to become a splendid ninja.
And in time, you will have
your own disciple...
Solely pervy...?
Can't believe he remembers
that particular detail...
That disciple will become a ninja who will
bring about a great change to the ninja world.
That is what I saw in my dream.
A great change?
Either great stability
or great destruction.
The likes of which this world
has never seen before.
One of those two.
One of those two?
What does that mean?
You will guide that revolutionary.
The day will come when you will
be forced to make a critical choice.
Choice?
Your choice shall decide
which way the change goes.
What must I do...?
In order to make the right choice?
In my dream, you traveled the world,
writing books.
Books? Whatever for?
I do not know either.
Perhaps it will be a journey around
the world to see all things in nature.
Great Lord Elder, have your prophecies
ever not come to pass?
No, never.
Jiraiya, you are leaving?
Yup!
At this point in my life, there's no way I can
guide someone who will be a revolutionary...
Let alone make the right choice.
Hmm...
I guess I need more time to see many more things,
and meet different people.
I see...
Just like in the Great Lord Elder's dream, I shall journey
throughout the world and perhaps, write a book.
It seems that is my destiny.
While Jiraiya journeyed and searched for the
meaning behind the Great Lord Elder's dream,
the state of the world grew
steadily more chaotic.
The peace that had prevailed among
the Five Great Nations became fragile.
Aggression between lands
increased as did internal strife,
and the people began to suffer.
Young man...
Why are you traveling?
I'm searching for my destiny.
Oh...?
Someone saw me in a dream.
And just like in that dream, I journey from land to land.
Oh my, what's the matter...?
Here, have one. It's milk candy.
A puppet?
Oh, this child tells me...
Destiny is not something you search for!
Destiny is something you latch onto
when it presents itself.
The age of war is coming.
Mechanical skills are useless in times of peace,
but some feudal lord may pay a high price for my services.
So he is a ninja too...
He has chosen to ride the wave
to the age of destruction.
But that will only...
What was that?!
This is just an ordinary village!
Why would a ninja...?!
This shuriken jutsu...
You are from the Fuma, aren't you?!
Why attack people who
are living in peace?!
You are also a ninja.
I am journeying in search of the one
who will become my disciple.
Humph! Why waste time
on such a tedious thing?!
The balance of power between lands has become
shaky and we are on the verge of a great war...
That village was also destroyed due
to a tip that ninja had infiltrated it.
Just because of a tip?!
It's destroy, or be destroyed.
We live in a world where
you'll die if you hesitate!
A Smoke Bomb!
You're pretty good.
If you are a ninja too,
I cannot let you live.
Just give up...
This is our fate as ninja.
Can I say something?
I don't feel like listening...
Just...die!!
Give up...
...on me giving up!
Even if you bring me down,
another assassin will attack the village...
As long as we are cursed to live in this ninja world,
there will be no peace.
The Great Toad Sage's
prophecy said that I am destined
to train the revolutionary
who will bring peace to this world.
However, I haven't even encountered
this disciple.
Already at this time,
battles were inevitably being fought.
Jiraiya was also forced to take
a short break from his journey
and returned to the Hidden Leaf Village.
We're at war...after all.
Orochimaru...
In order to erase this sadness
from the ninja world...
I must find the revolutionary...
I must choose the one
who will bring peace.
The flames of war finally drew
in Jiraiya and his comrades.
This would come to be known
as the Third Great Ninja War.
Shortly afterwards, the three would come
to be known as the "Legendary Sannin."
Tales of a Gutsy Ninja -
Jiraiya Ninja Scrolls -Part 2
I predict the Hidden Leaf shall
emerge victorious from this battle.
Therefore, I shall let you three live.
We don't want your sympathy!
We can still fight!
Jiraiya, stop!
You three are strong...
You survived even this battleground.
I, Hanzo, hereby name you
the "Hidden Leaf's Sannin."
In exchange for your lives,
tell me your names.
Will it really end with
the Hidden Leaf's victory like he said?
And if it does, then what?
Will you set out on another journey?
Maybe...
Set out on my travels and
write another book...
Why won't you settle down
in the village?
I feel as though
I haven't encountered it yet.
You mean, your destiny?
Quiet!
They're just kids.
Don't let your guard down.
Even little mice can be from
the Hidden Rain Village.
Don't hide. Show yourself!
What do you want?
Give me some food!
What about your parents?
They were killed by ninja
because of this war.
Here...have some bread.
Nagato, Konan, come on out!
They don't seem like bad guys.
Hey!
We already gave you food!
Why are you following us?!
Thank you. This is for you...
It's origami...
folded from the bread wrapping.
This is for us?
Teach us ninjutsu...
You're all ninja from
the Hidden Leaf, right?
Shall I kill these children?
Wha--?!
I've seen many war orphans.
It's pitiful.
They would be better off if we just put
them out of their misery right now...
Orochimaru, enough!
You go on ahead with Tsunade.
I'll stay here and look after them
for a while.
Huh?!
Just until they can take better
care of themselves...
It is the least I can do.
But...
This is also part of destiny...
Thank you for the food!
Grilled fish in an instant with
my Fire Style Jutsu.
Mm... Delicious!
Sensei! I've gotten the hang of fishing!
Hmm?
What's the matter, Nagato?
I just remembered my family...
And...
Stop crying! You're a man!
It's because of guys like you that men of
the Hidden Rain are considered cowards!
Things are unstable among three of the Great
Nations that surround the Hidden Rain Village.
But this war won't drag out much longer.
By the time you are grown,
there will be mutual understanding and peace will-
That's not fair!
We all lost our families!
If there is a mutual understanding,
it's only after they go through what we did!
That's what it means to get even, right?!
But...I know that's impossible.
That's why wars will never end!
I hate rain.
This land is always crying.
It's a coward!
I'm gonna change this land.
I'll protect everyone!
That's why Jiraiya Sensei...!
Please teach us ninjutsu!
I don't have any ideas for my novel...
If there is a mutual understanding,
it's only after they go through what we did!
That's why wars will never end!
I'll protect everyone!!
I want the hero to wipe away
the hatred and bring about peace...
Now then...how can I...?
Jiraiya Sensei, help!
Yahiko and Nagato are in trouble...!
Lead the way, Konan!!
I brought Sensei!
What happened?
This...
This leftover ninja told us to hand
over our food...and valuables.
Then Nagato...
He's a chunin from the Hidden Stone...
How did Nagato...?
Th-Those eyes...!!
He couldn't...possibly be...!
That shape... That ripple pattern...
I can't believe it!
That eye...
Said to hold the most noble of
the three great Visual Jutsu...
The Rinnegan!
The Sage of the Six Paths,
said to be the father of all ninja...
It is said that the Sage possessing the Rinnegan
eye developed all the jutsu known to us today.
Rumored to always appear when the world becomes
corrupt, capable of being both a godlike force of creation
and an all-obliterating instrument
of destruction.
I always believed it as a mere legend.
But here is someone who actually
possesses the Rinnegan!
I shall now tell you...
In my dream...
You, who are solely pervy, will still manage
to become a splendid ninja.
And in time, you will have
your own disciple...
That disciple will become a ninja who will
bring about a great change to the ninja world.
That is what I saw in my dream.
You will guide that revolutionary...
The day will come when you will be
forced to make a critical selection.
Could Nagato be this revolutionary?
Perhaps I have found my destiny.
I've decided to teach you ninjutsu.
R-Really?!
You may encounter another life-threatening
situation like that last time.
It is ninjutsu for self-defense.
Yes!
Thanks for saving us last time, Nagato!
Sorry I called you a coward!
Next time anything happens,
I'll protect you!
Th-Thanks, Yahiko.
Huh...? But Nagato is stronger
than you, Yahiko!
I'm gonna train starting now
and I'll become stronger!
You always exaggerate, Konan!
All right, let's start!
The first lesson is on molding chakra.
- Yes, Sensei!
Something's bothering you, eh?
Talk to me.
Sensei...
Is it about that incident?
That day...
When that man hurt Yahiko,
I was so mad at him.
Everything went blank in my head...
I didn't know what I was doing.
Before I realized it, the man was dead...
After that, I got so scared.
This hatred made me lose myself...
and I killed someone.
What I did was wrong!
There had to be a better way--!
Nagato...
I really don't know
if it was right or wrong.
But thanks to you, Yahiko didn't die.
You protected your friend.
That had to be the right thing to do.
No one can blame you for that.
When you are hurt, you learn to hate.
On the other hand, when
you hurt someone, you are resented.
But you start to feel guilty as well.
Understanding such pain enables
you to be kind to others...
That's what makes us human.
What do you mean by that...?
It's called growing up.
Growing up? What do you mean?
That, you need to figure out yourself.
Konan and I were crying because
we were so hungry and Yahiko saved us.
He stole food from others to feed us.
I just want to protect those two.
No matter what kind of pain
I have to endure.
I see.
"TALES OF A GUTSY NINJA" BY JIRAIYA
Water Style: Raging Waves!
Paper Shuriken!
Wind Style: Gale Palm!
We did it!
How's that, Sensei?!
You're even able to take down
my Shadow Clone now, eh?
Now I can return to my village
without any worries.
- Huh?
You are on your own from now on.
You've done well these past three years!
Don't cry, Yahiko.
Or people will call you a coward.
Konan... You're gonna grow up
to be a beauty.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
This is a poor land.
And there's more sadness
and tough times up ahead.
But now, you have the strength
to change this land.
Nagato... You three have grown up.
Don't you agree?
Thank you, Sensei.
Even after Jiraiya returned to the village,
the Third Great Ninja War raged on.
Tsunade! Orochimaru! Ready?!
Yeah!
- Summoning Jutsu!
The Hidden Leaf's Sannin distinguished
themselves in many battles...
leaving legends in their wake.
All this fighting...
How long must it continue?
What must be done to stop the war?
Humph... As if there's a way to stop it.
Hate only gives birth
to even more hate.
But...!
I don't know how to stop it.
But peace will certainly come.
As long as there are those who
believe that, there is hope.
Oh, what's the matter?
What's wrong?
Those three have died.
I've tried my best to make
the right choices.
I believed that was what destiny
had in store for me.
Jiraiya...
And finally...
I thought I did what was right.
But perhaps,
I was wrong yet again.
You'll find it
as long as you keep believing.
Yes... I guess I'm still in
the middle of my journey.
The Third Great Ninja War dragged on and the
one who guided Hidden Leaf Village to victory
was another one of Jiraiya's disciples...
Minato Namikaze.
That was long. Too long...
What will you do from now on?
Let's see...
Maybe set out on another journey.
Maybe I'll find a disciple who
can change the world.
Is that your destiny?
The destiny of Jiraiya?
Well, I guess you could say that...
Humph... What a strange man you are.
Hmm? You walk the path of the ninja.
Don't you want someone
to take over after you?
To gather all the jutsu in this world
and master them...
That is my only goal.
Even if you master them all,
humans are not immortal.
She's right.
I wonder about that...