[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-11-11 15:22:10
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: cn.normal.aside,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0C0C0C0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,40,10,1
Style: jp.normal.aside,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.normal.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: cn.normal.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.note,汉鼎繁中圆,20,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.once,汉鼎繁中圆,20,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,30,30,10,1
Style: jp.美国.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H000080FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.日本.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H005F5F5F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.英国.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00404080,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.法国.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00FF8080,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.中国.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H008080FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.俄罗斯.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00800040,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.德国.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00408000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.意大利.sub,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00C080FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.英国.aside,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00404080,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.美国.aside,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H000080FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.法国.aside,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00FF8080,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,40,1
Style: jp.俄罗斯.aside,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00800040,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,40,1
Style: cn.美国.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140080FF,&H0053A9FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.日本.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H146F6F6F,&H00AFAFAF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.英国.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14404080,&H005353A6,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.英国.aside,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14404080,&H005454A7,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.法国.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14FF8080,&H00FFA6A6,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.美国.aside,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H140080FF,&H003399FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.中国.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H148080FF,&H00A4A4FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.法国.aside,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14FF8080,&H00FFA2A2,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.俄罗斯.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14800040,&H00BB005E,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.俄罗斯.aside,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14800040,&H00E80074,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.德国.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14408000,&H004E9B00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.意大利.sub,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14FF80FF,&H00FFBBFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: cn.song,汉鼎简特圆,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14FF80FF,&H00FFB9FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: jp.song,DFPRuLeiA-W5,25,&H00FF80FF,&HF0000000,&H14FFFFFF,&H00DFDFDF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,汉鼎繁中圆,25,&H0000EA75,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: title,汉鼎繁中圆,25,&H0000E171,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.68,0:04:20.43,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ねぇねぇパパ ワイン頂戴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.43,0:04:22.27,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ねぇねぇママ ねぇねぇママ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.27,0:04:24.03,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昔に　食べた　ボルネーゼの
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.03,0:04:26.18,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの味が　忘れられないんだぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.18,0:04:29.74,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まるかいて地球　まるかいて地球
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.74,0:04:33.50,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まるかいて地球 僕ヘタリア
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.50,0:04:40.44,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 一筆で　見える すばらしい世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.44,0:04:48.67,jp.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長靴で乾杯だ！ ヘタリア
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.68,0:04:20.43,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 爸爸 红酒拿来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.43,0:04:22.27,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 妈妈 呐呐妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.27,0:04:24.03,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前吃的意面配肉酱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.03,0:04:26.18,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美味好难忘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.18,0:04:29.74,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球团团转 地球团团转
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.74,0:04:33.50,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圆圆地球上 有我意呆利
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.50,0:04:40.44,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放眼看世界 精彩又美好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.44,0:04:48.67,cn.song,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用长靴来干杯！ 意呆利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.83,0:00:52.16,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诸神字幕 [翻译]死胖子 我冷血 koki [校对]Lucifer [时间]我不是团子 [发布&压制]嘟嘟V
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.83,0:00:52.16,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【黑塔利亚】又名百无一用意呆利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.04,0:00:03.64,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいか　手榴弾の使い方を教えておく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.99,0:00:05.24,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まず　ピンを外し
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.50,0:00:07.32,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地面などに叩き付けて発火させる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.77,0:00:15.49,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして敵陣地に投擲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.29,0:00:17.85,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とう言う順序だが　できそうか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.17,0:00:19.15,jp.意大利.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　分かった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.72,0:00:21.53,jp.意大利.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それなら俺も頑張ればできそう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.04,0:00:24.52,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こら　こつち投げ…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.06,0:00:32.58,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あー　逆だ！　逆だ！　早く投げろ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.92,0:00:34.41,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こう投げないと　お前が「ドン」して　
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.22,0:00:36.07,jp.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あー
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.33,0:00:55.59,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遂に完璧なゆで卵が作れる機械を発明したぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.01,0:01:00.48,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我が大英帝国の英知を結集させて作った最先端のゆで卵製造器で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.19,0:01:02.80,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,構想に数年と開発に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.95,0:01:07.35,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とま―　そんなわけで長年の苦労の甲斐あって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.65,0:01:11.28,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うまいゆで卵がほかの国にはまねできないような技術で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.58,0:01:16.41,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヘタリア
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.73,0:01:19.51,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遂にビール泡が綺麗に出る機械を発明したぞ　我が…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.55,0:01:25.13,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,てめぇー！　ビールをぶつける必要ねぇだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.35,0:01:27.14,jp.法国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いーや　ぶつける必要あるでーす…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.66,0:01:29.58,jp.中国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日の連合国は平和ある
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.86,0:01:30.45,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヘタリア
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.89,0:01:36.88,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気紛れで始めた倉庫掃除
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.95,0:01:42.97,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもそれは　深く眠っていた俺の記憶の断片を呼び戻した
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.17,0:01:46.63,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いい事も…　悪い事も…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:56.03,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もしかして　あの時の…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.67,0:02:06.96,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なぁ　イギリス
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.35,0:02:09.78,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり俺　自由を選ぶよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.58,0:02:11.70,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう子供でもないし　
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.30,0:02:14.24,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の弟でもない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.67,0:02:17.78,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,たった今俺は　君から独立する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.44,0:02:29.24,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,認めん…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.59,0:02:42.30,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だからお前は詰めが甘いんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.27,0:02:44.82,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばーか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.06,0:02:45.90,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,う、撃てー！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.58,0:03:01.11,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撃てるわけねぇだろ　ばか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:07.79,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生　何でなんだよ　くそ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.03,0:03:10.93,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イギリス
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.12,0:03:13.03,jp.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帰るぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.65,0:03:22.34,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.48,0:03:33.18,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんなに　大きかったのにな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.63,0:03:43.65,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あー　アメリカさん　そこでしたか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.31,0:03:47.65,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　何か埃とかゴミとか凄くてね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.46,0:03:51.90,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全然掃除捗らなくて　今日は止めることにしたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.52,0:03:54.36,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へぇー　大変でしたね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.82,0:03:57.20,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっ　じゃあコーヒーここで飲みますか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.80,0:03:59.27,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　そうしようか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.16,0:04:04.70,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古い物見てると色々思い出して
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.90,0:04:05.90,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捨てらんないんだよな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.31,0:04:10.22,jp.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か俺も　おっさんになったのかなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.06,0:04:14.59,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大人になったんですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.69,0:04:54.24,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だこれ　手作りの兵隊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.30,0:04:56.47,jp.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か可愛い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.81,0:04:58.77,jp.美国.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イギリスが来た　早くそれ隠してくれー！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.04,0:00:03.64,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 现在我来教你使用手榴弹的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.99,0:00:05.24,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 拔下栓子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.50,0:00:07.32,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砸到地面上引爆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.77,0:00:15.49,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后扔到敌方阵营
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.29,0:00:17.85,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个顺序你能做到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.17,0:00:19.15,cn.意大利.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.72,0:00:21.53,cn.意大利.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是那样的话 我努力一下还是能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.04,0:00:24.52,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 不要往这边扔…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.06,0:00:32.58,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊~ 反了 反了 快点扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.92,0:00:34.41,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不扔掉你就要轰得一声爆掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.22,0:00:36.07,cn.德国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.33,0:00:55.59,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于发明出了能做出完美煮鸡蛋的机器了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.01,0:01:00.48,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台集结了我大英帝国的智慧的最新型的煮鸡蛋机
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.19,0:01:02.80,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用了数年来构思和开发…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.95,0:01:07.35,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 长年的辛苦得到了回报
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.65,0:01:11.28,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美味的煮鸡蛋 其他国家所无法模仿的技术…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.58,0:01:16.41,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑塔利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.73,0:01:19.51,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于发明出了能让啤酒冒出好看泡沫的机器了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.55,0:01:25.13,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 没必要用啤酒撞我的头吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.35,0:01:27.14,cn.法国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 有这必要
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.66,0:01:29.58,cn.中国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的联合国也很和平阿鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.86,0:01:30.45,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑塔利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.89,0:01:36.88,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心血来潮而开始的仓库扫除
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.95,0:01:42.97,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那却唤起了我那沉睡已久的记忆片段
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.17,0:01:46.63,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是美好的记忆还是悲伤的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:56.03,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道 是那个时候的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.67,0:02:06.96,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 英国
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.35,0:02:09.78,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎样果然我还是要选择自由
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.58,0:02:11.70,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不是小孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.30,0:02:14.24,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是你的弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.67,0:02:17.78,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我就要从你那里独立！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.44,0:02:29.24,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不允许
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.59,0:02:42.30,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你这人总是太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.27,0:02:44.82,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.06,0:02:45.90,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射 射击
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.58,0:03:01.11,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能下得了手 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:07.79,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 为什么啊　可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.03,0:03:10.93,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英国　
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.12,0:03:13.03,cn.英国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.65,0:03:22.34,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.48,0:03:33.18,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身影 以前明明是那么高大…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.63,0:03:43.65,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 美国先生 原来你在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.31,0:03:47.65,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 总觉得灰尘和垃圾好多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.46,0:03:51.90,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全打扫不干净　今天就先这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.52,0:03:54.36,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 真够辛苦的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.82,0:03:57.20,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那么要在这里喝咖啡吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.80,0:03:59.27,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 就这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.16,0:04:04.70,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了以前的东西 想起了好多事啊　
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.90,0:04:05.90,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是舍不得扔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.31,0:04:10.22,cn.美国.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵 我是不是已经变成大叔了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.06,0:04:14.59,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是变得成熟了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.69,0:04:54.24,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？　手制的士兵？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.30,0:04:56.47,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.81,0:04:58.77,cn.美国.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英国来了　快点把那个藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.01,0:01:51.72,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国的仓库扫除
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,00:02:02
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.33,0:02:03.36,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1775年--1783年　美国独立战争
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.95,0:04:18.60,cn.note,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国的仓库扫除 END
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.29,0:05:00.37,cn.normal.sub,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集待续
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,cn.normal.aside,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
