Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Don't Be Dense, Be Sharp.
Don't be dense, be sharp.
She's amazing!
She beat Ooe, the ace of the swim team!
Didn't that Ooe guy go to some training
camp abroad to get even better?
It wasn't a real competition,
but she still won...
She's really too perfect.
Let's redo that.
What?
On your marks,
get set...
Wait, President?
The backstroke?
But why?
But I've gotta admit...
Getting a proper look...
her body is really...
beautiful.
C-Crap, did I get caught staring?!
She's amazing!
She beat Ooe, the ace of the swim team!
Shirota-kun.
Usually you badger me, all,
"Why did you redo that?"
But you kept quiet today.
I-I just didn't have the time to ask...
I see.
Well, there was no big reason, really.
I just figured it would be worth leaving
more of an impression when I won.
Incidentally, which style left more
of an impression on you?
Crap!
What should I answer?!
If tell her honestly that it was the backstroke,
I'd basically be confessing that
I was ogling her body!
What do I do?!
They do say one's eyes say
as much as one's mouth...
But I've never seen anyone
speak volumes with their back.
Jeez...
You're really such a pervert, Shirota-kun.
Eh, ah, well... Oh, right!
Forget that!
How did you redo that?
You're not wearing underwear!
Is your imagination only good
for thinking about sexual things?
Well, I suppose I can give you
a small hint just this once...
My upper body.
U-Upper body?
T-There's something r-raised on one side...
Were they...
The things called p-pasties?!
Oh, is something wrong?
You seem to be bent over a bit.
Oh, it's nothing.
Are you not feeling well?
I-I'm fine!
Really?
That's good, then.
Please don't go anywhere
after classes are over.
See ya.
What am I doing here?
I don't know where to look!
What's the matter, Shirota-kun?
Why are you so tense?
Um, President?
Why did you bring me here?
I'm starting to run low on underwear at home,
so I thought I should buy
a couple of pairs now.
Which pair is better?
Err, uhh... either is fine!
I know you're surrounded by your
favorite thing, underwear,
but you still shouldn't get overly excited.
I'm not!
Besides, I only came here
because you ordered me to!
Huh, well, isn't that very sober of you.
Then this is perfect.
Please pick out a pair of
underwear that suits me.
Say what?!
Since you're putting underwear on me,
wouldn't it be more satisfying
to pick out a pair yourself?
What do you mean, "satisfying"?!
What are you getting all flustered about?
I thought you could carry things out soberly
as long as you were ordered.
F-Fine!
I know she knows that I can't do this calmly!
I'll just pick something to get it over with.
These ones, then.
So nonchalantly picking those ones
really goes to show that you're a perv.
Huh?
Wha?!
I can't believe you want me
to be in class wearing that.
That's some fetish you have.
N-No!
Not that one! I made a mistake!
They sell stuff like this in normal stores?!
I have to choose properly!
Oh.
She's pure and clean in my mind, so... white?
Huh.
No, she's dark on the inside, so.... black.
But she does have a kind side...
so... pink or a warm color?
Huh.
That's a pretty blue,
but what made you pick these ones?
Well, there's no particular reason...
So, what do you think?
I'll decide after trying them on.
What?! Try them on?!
It's fine.
U-Um...
I probably shouldn't be here
while you try them on.
You're the one who'll be putting
them on me after I buy them,
so you should certainly see
how it feels to put them on.
By the way, I'm wearing thicker tights,
so even without underwear,
you can't see anything, right?
Wha? N-No underwear?!
Please don't show me that so casually!
Oh, my bad.
Let me do it again more dramatically then.
That's not what I meant!
Don't you see?
I just figured it'd be easier
to put on if I pull this up like so.
For a sober person like you,
it shouldn't matter what I'm wearing, right?
She's teasing me with that again.
I can't let her mock me forever...
Even I have some pride!
Of course, I'll be putting them on you soberly—
Go ahead.
Huh?!
Shirota-kun?!
That was a shock.
I can't believe you fainted.
I'm sorry.
Given that you're such a sober person,
it certainly wasn't that you got too excited.
So you must not be feeling well, right?
I don't even know what to say.
Oh, right, I never got a chance to ask...
Why did you pick that blue underwear?
Well, like I said, there's no real reason.
Tell me the truth.
I won't let you out until you do.
Because you inhabit such a high echelon,
it made me think of the blue sky.
Also because you're as unfathomable as the sea.
That's why I thought blue would be perfect.
Now that I say it out loud,
it's such a childish reason!
I see.
No reaction?!
That reminds me that I picked them
without even asking what she likes...
Um, President,
don't you like them?
Well, I won't be putting them on, of course.
F-Figures.
I mean...
if I did,
it won't be the "Eternal Virgin Road" any more.
Okay, Shirota-kun.
We're going to the next lingerie shop.
What? You're buying more?!
Please Put Them On,
Takamine-san
Oh man.
I totally caught a cold.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye!
I should get home quickly.
President?
Pull yourself together, Shirota-kun.
I live close, so I'll take you to your house.
Thank you.
Huh, you live a lot more
neatly than I expected.
I'm impressed, Shirota-kun.
Th-Thanks.
Oh, such a shame.
Is something wrong?
I thought there would be
a dirty folder in here,
and I'd learn all about
your sexual proclivities.
Ahh!
P-Please!
So, where did you hide your pervy folder?
Did you come in to search my room?!
Of course not.
This is closet maintenance.
Kurota-kun, if you break,
it will have an adverse effect
on my life too, right?
I thought that, before you
become properly useless,
I thought I'd do maintenance— I mean, nurse you.
Are you eating properly?
No, my appetite hasn't been so good...
Then I'll make something for you.
What? No, I couldn't ask you to do that.
Oh?
I didn't know closets could decline kindness.
They can't, can they?
R-Right.
Well then.
Should I wear nothing
but an apron while cooking?
Sorry, what?!
You're into that, aren't you, Shirota-kun?
N-Not particularly!
While we're at it,
I could feed you like that as well.
And once you're done eating,
you'll probably have worked up a sweat,
so I'll gently wipe off your
whole body with a steamed towel.
Still wearing only the apron.
Go to bed right after, and you'll
have your energy back in no time.
Oh, but maybe something else
might be full of energy before that.
A-At least spare me the teasing when I'm sick!
"Something else might be full of energy"...
Are you some middle-aged man?!
I can take care of my own body,
so please go home before you catch my cold!
You're right.
You make a good point.
I'll redo this.
Shirota-kun.
I went ahead and used the ingredients
and apron in the kitchen.
And I did put the steamed towel in a wrap,
but let me know if it
gets cold and I'll reheat it.
R-Right.
I'll be cleaning up,
so I'll be back to check on you
around the time you're done eating.
Could it be that she undid making fun of me?
It's good!
Why is she...
mocking me for sport one moment
and then being so kind to me the next?
Or...
is it just her way of making sure
I function well as her closet?
Shirota-kun, did you finish eating?
Yes.
How was the food?
Did you like it?
Yes, it was delicious.
I see. That's good.
Is this the so-called carrot and stick?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Lying down next to you.
What?!
When you have a fever,
it's important to keep
your body warm, is it not?
Yes, but...
Oh, I see.
Huh?
I undid trying so hard in today's PE class.
I did put on deodorant, of course...
But now I definitely should not
smell like sweat.
That's not what I was concerned about!
Oh, I'm sorry...
Maybe you would have preferred
if I smelled even sweatier?
It has nothing to do with your sweat!
There you go again, poking fun at me...
Please stop it!
I can sleep on my own!
I'm not poking fun.
I'm merely doing what's necessary
as the owner of my closet.
You can just think of me as nothing
more than a big hot water bottle.
That's easy for you to say...
But the person at my back right now...
is the most beautiful girl at school,
wearing nothing but her school uniform,
with no bra or panties...
Not thinking about that is impossible!
What are you going to do
if I get some weird idea?!
Or is that also part of you making fun of me?!
I don't get it.
I don't understand what you're thinking!
There's one thing I'd like to tell you.
I think I might have gone a bit too far teasing you.
Regarding your physical condition, too.
I might not have been thoughtful enough.
I'm sorry.
What are you—
Oxytocin.
When skin touches skin,
oxytocin is released and helps you relax.
This should help you fall asleep easier.
I'm going so far to help you.
You'd best fall asleep instead
of thinking about pointless stuff.
Otherwise I'll have you sent to the trash heap.
Those words were quite typical for her
as the owner of a closet.
But I faintly but surely
heard her say "I'm sorry."
And though I had my face buried in the chest
of the most beautiful girl at school,
I didn't feel aroused. Instead, I felt safe.
Maybe she really did worry about me.
That thought made me realize...
that the goddess of the school
and the owner of the closet...
President Takamine Takane,
was also a human girl.
Do you think you'll be able to sleep, Shirota-kun?
Yes.
May I ask you something?
What is it?
When you're being nice to me,
is that the carrot part of the carrot and stick?
Or do you have some...
W-Well...
What about you?
Which would make you happier?
Shirota-kun?
Sleep well, Shirota-kun.
Let's go over there!
Yeah!
Wait up!
Milk for Her and Him
I'm home.
...is that the carrot part of the carrot and stick?
Or do you...
Oh, Kuro.
Come here.
Sheesh.
Does he really think I'd go that far
for someone I don't care about?
Don't you agree?
President?
You seem to be sound asleep,
so I'll go home for today.
There's still rice porridge in the fridge,
so please eat it when you get hungry.
Get well soon.
Hot!
The president today was a little...
I feel like my fever's
about to come back.