Nohara
(Shinnosuke Nohara)
Saitamaken
I'm sorry
"Rakuga Kingdom" release commemoration! ＞
Today
Pun
30 minutes about the movie! ＞
Nazu
Straw
Special
"If you laugh with Ora-SP">
World
Suku
I will save the world →
Konkai
Named after this movie →
First of all
Story
From the story of graffiti>
By
Big
It was a big hit
Newlywed
"Honeymoon Hurricane" →
Smallpox
First broadcast on TV! ＞
Minoga
undefined
Nohara
・ ～ (Shinnosuke Nohara)
"Zo-U-san Zo-U-san"
slope
Yo
・ ～ "If you read it upside down
Sa-nzo Sa-nzo "
Kansei
carry out!
Next
Next is Snake!
Naga
・ ～ "Long snake
Long-long-long-long-long "
Ah ... Ah!
Who
Who does this!
Oh !?
・ ～
What should I do…
Kaa
If my mom finds out ...
(Misae Nohara) Shinnosuke ~!
Hey!
Bad ... Bad zo ...!
Shincha-n.
Giku!
What
what have you been up to?
Eka
Or
Oh, drawing? What did you draw
Ah ~!
Wow!
What ... what?
Eh ... oh ...
Nana
Go
(Himawari Nohara crying)
O
I got up.
Already…
Oh
Over
Is
Because you make a loud voice.
Yes yes.
・ ～
Yes Yes. I won't cry anymore.
Guo!
・ ～
what are you doing?
(Sunflower) Taya?
And
Playing saury without swimming.
Hmm ...
Oto
(Sound of turning on the TV)
Ufufufu ...
(Sunflower) Tapping ...
Hmm?
I want to.
Ah!
Free time!
Taya.
Oops!
Gugu ... Gugu ...
Tapping ...
Oh?
Hit it.
Ahaha Aha Ahaha ...
Hmm? What are you doing?
Hiki
2 ... Playing two saury.
I see.
Haa ...
Ah
"Hey, I met you again."
Taya !?
Ah, ah, ah ...
Be quiet!
Aya!
Uo ~!
I don't fight.
I want to.
Ah ...
Tapping ....
"Thank you"
No!
Underground
Himacha-n It's close.
・ ～
Haa ...
Ahahahaha ...
Mother
of
I want to drink Pusslite.
Refrigerator
It's in the fridge.
I
Or ... Mom put it in
With push light →
full
I want to have a drink.
Eh?
Ama
What are you spoiling for?
Ehe ~.
Draw
Hide it with this ...
Huh ...!
At all
Ta
Not enough ...
Well
Please wait.
Yes.
Don't you drink
Also
Bring it here.
Already ... see.
Thank you very much.
Hmm?
"Bah ... I got caught ...? 》
O
You see, the crayon has fallen.
Before
Ho
Oh, I wanted it before.
I
What are you talking about.
Katazu
Please clean it up properly.
Hey.
(cry)
Ara Hima-chan
Are you sleeping again?
(cry)
Ai.
Alright
Let's sleep ~.
Abu
It was dangerous ...
I
Uh ... I want to go pee.
Now
I ... something to hide now ...
What to hide ...
(Shiro) An An!
Oh! White!
Ne
Ah, I finally slept ...
that?
Ku-n.
Work
Ah ~ I did a good job ~.
Shinnosuke! White
home
Inside
Ah
Don't put it in your house!
why?
Family
Ichiin
Even Shiro is a member of the family!
Properly for white
garden
You have a house in your garden, right?
Shiro is good here!
Let's go
Another lifetime
Ugo
I don't want to move here!
Disagreeable
You see, you don't like it.
Haha-n you By the way ...
Ora ... nothing ...
Sanpo
Shiro's walk
Trouble
It's a hassle !?
eh…?
Modo
Return to the white garden!
Neiki
(Sleeping)
Hunk ...!
Hmm ...! Ugh ...
Alright!
Next time
What are you doing this time ...
Moyoga
Also ... It's a remodeling.
Change the look ... →
The table looks like this
Ta
It's not hard to eat rice!
Flowerpot
Bring back the flowerpots too!
At all
Anyway, definitely leave it as it is!
《I'm hiding this guy ...》
Mi
Nice
That's right. If you look closely, it's nice
Shall I leave it as it is?
Right?
By the way →
Kamen
"Action Kamen" coming soon
Jikan
Isn't it time?
That's right!
Uh ... Mom, turn on the TV.
By the way
Not such a place
Before
What if I saw it earlier?
Today
Kyo ... Today
I want to see it from here.
Hmm ...
Haa ...
Yes snack.
Oh chocobi!
While watching "Action Kamen"
What if I eat?
Eat Eat ~!
Then please.
Uh ...
Haya
When
What's wrong? Come get it soon.
UU….
Maybe you don't need it?
Then mom, let's eat it ~.
Ah!
Ah.
Ah ...!
Hmmm delicious!
Let's eat more!
Ah! No!
It took!
Huh!
Ah!
Dirty
Already! If you get dirty
Shojiki
I
Be honest!
If not on purpose
Ok
Even moms don't get angry.
While saying so
I'm not angry.
Sandanbara
Adult
That's why adults with three-tiered belly
Shinyo
I can't trust you.
Yokei
The three-tiered belly is superfluous!
Look, get angry!
You
Maybe it's because I cheat!
Kyuteigaka
(Court painter)
Would you like to draw something with this?
Hi
Ega
What I drew starts to move
Mysterious
Mysterious Crayon>
Kusa
smell!
(Brief) I am →
Shinpin
Isn't it new !?
Nanako Sister!
Su
(Fake Nanako) I like it.
that?
Top
(Buriburizaemon) I'm in trouble
Nakama
Misu
Don't abandon your friends.
I
... what do you say, Barka!
Wow!
First to me
Let me eat something.
Kasukabe
Heiwa
Yonin
Yusha
Maka
Leave it to the four heroes! ＞
Eiga
<"Movie Crayon Shin-chan">
<"Movie Crayon Shin-chan"
If you laugh with Ora ~>
(Buriburizaemon)
Daikatsu
undefined
Shuyaku
I'm almost the main character, so →
Good
Please prepare well>
Naga
thing
There was a drifter>
Nohara
(Shinnosuke Nohara)
Ugh ... it's flowing.
Oh ... even if it ’s just a butt
It's flowing.
Robuta
I got it from an old pig →
Suku
Yo
Is
Call the hero of salvation
Also
I had maracas>
(Ohana) Oh!
What?
Well
Collat! Wait!
(Ohana) Oh!
Oh yeah.
Yes.
Car!
I got a sign!
Different
... is different!
War
O
I'm being chased by a bad guy!
Jo
Young lady
To
Mainly
Did you think you could escape?
Idea
Draw
Don't put out what you're hiding!
What are you hiding ...?
Also
Maybe a crotch elephant?
Woman
I'm a woman!
Nega
Add
Please! help!
It can't be helped ...
(Maracas)
(Buriburizaemon)
Hero of salvation →
Kenzan
Buriburizaemon visit!
・ ～
Uh ...
You can do this ...
(Buriburizaemon) Hmm ...
Don't run away!
Come on ... Come on
Get that out quickly!
Eh!
Chikara
Ki
I'll ask you by force!
Aitetete ...!
(Marumo) That's it!
Girl child
Open
For girls and children
Big
man
There is no big man!
What
Who are you?
Yojinbo
Marumo, a bouncer.
Wow ah ~!
Huh!
Guwa ...!
Oh…!
Obo
Remember ...!
Oh ~ cool zo!
Kuchi
I ran away or not as much as my mouth.
What?
You also ran away!
Everyone
Everyone doesn't seem to be injured.
That's Atai's line ...
Abu
Dangerous place
Thank you very much!
Zero
Shokuji
Thank you for your meal.
Huh ... Atai is a bouncer.
Cash
If you get cash
That's fine.
Please have a meal at home.
Ki
I don't feel like giving out cash ...
Chichi
Daughter
(Ohana's father) Daughter Hana
Dangerous place →
Thank you very much.
(Buriburizaemon) What?
Want
Don't do much.
This guy is really
It's not a big deal.
But they
On earth
What
Aim
What on earth were you aiming for?
People
That is this person's elephant ...
That's why it's different!
I was aiming
Morning sickness
Probably this.
eh?
what? It.
Wow
Or
Daidai ivy
Handed down to my home for generations
Maoubin
This is the "Devil Bottle Bottle Opener".
Over
Now
Susennen Mae
(Voice of Hana's father) Thousands of years ago →
Chi
This place
Maou
Yes
It was dominated by the Demon King.
Alone
Yusha
But one hero
Bottle
When
This
I trapped the Demon King in a bottle.
(Voice of Hana's father) The lid of the bottle is →
Igai
Other than this bottle opener
Ah
It cannot be opened.
Go
afterwards
Umi
There
Shizu
The bottle was sunk to the bottom of the sea.
Saikin
What
But recently somebody
Mi
It seems that the Demon Bottle was found.
Today
Morning sickness
What hit Hana today
Renchu
Those guys.
hand
I
Get a bottle opener
Are you going to open the lid of the bottle?
What if that happens?
Lid
How about
This land is again under the control of the Demon King ...
Please!
Please with us
Mamo
Please protect this bottle opener!
I would like it too!
If you protect me ...
How much can you put out?
Two
(2 people) Please have a meal at home.
Oh!
Do you care about cash for anything?
Ugo
Hmm ... It only works with cash
Wonder
Human
I'm a sad person.
what?
yen
That's 10 yen.
What !? I did it! lucky!
In the middle
Even small change works immediately
Pig
Sad pig ...
Jikan
It's time.
One day
I only have 3 hours a day
World
I can't stay in this world.
Then Ora
Steller sea lion
I'll deliver it to the policeman.
Oh!
That's me!
Kekkyoku
After all
Fast
Ta
A guy who is of no use ...
Dan
Flower
Go
(Speaking voice of Cheongmage group)
Very much
Soto
Mostly
Enemy
It's hard! There are many enemies outside!
Why did you find out here !?
Sena
Tsu
Something is on my back!
Kogata Denpa Hasshinki
Small radio transmitter ...!
I got caught in this ...
When
When attached
Didn't you notice?
I'm sorry ...
Already! I'm scared.
What's that back?
Butterfly
Nuu! Ultra-small transmitter!
When on earth !?
Where is the ultra-small!
Yesterday
I've been with you since yesterday.
"Ah, ah…
Inside
People
Can you hear the people inside? "
House
Mawa
(Chonmage boss) Around the house
We
Hoi
We, the Cheongmage group, surrounded us.
Kazo
so
I have to come out after counting 10 →
How
Bazooka cannon
Mima
I'm sorry for you ~.
(Boss) "1 2 ..."
(Ohana's father) Marumo-san!
Yuka
did
What's under my floor?
secret
Tsuuro
Oh, a secret passage!
(Ohana's father) Look
Shunouko
It's a storage.
Elbow
Jiman
Proud of this emergency!
Underground
This is the underground passage!
Haya
Come on soon!
Cheeks.
(Boss) "7 8 9 ..."
U
"10! Shoot!"
Pronunciation
(Explosion sound)
Chijo
I'll be on the ground soon!
Ki
(Boss) Where did those guys disappear !?
boss!
I
Guchi
Here is the entrance to the underground passage!
They got me….
Tsuu
Where on earth are you going?
Oh?
Ah ... over there.
Too
Ho
Dig a passage farther!
Tochu
Tsuka
I got tired on the way ...
Huff Huff ...
Now open the Demon King bottle →
Dominate the world with the power of the Demon King!
Well ... if you put out the Demon King
Hametsu
The world will be ruined!
shut up!
Hostage
My daughter will be taken hostage!
rattan
Father!
Oh ... Hana!
You guys →
feed
For vulture food
I hope it will be!
Nana
Go
(cry)
It's a cheongmage vulture.
It's complicated ...
(Boss) Hahaha! Farewell!
Hana ~! Uh ...!
Should be
Chi! It's off.
Alright!
Let's call Buriburizaemon!
(Maracas)
Ugh! Ugh ...!
Ohhhhh!
Ah…?
why
Tsuka
I'm even caught up to you!
Tanin
garden
Ki
A little from a tree in someone else's garden
I just gave you a mandarin orange.
Dorobo
Don't be a thief
useless!
About
Mostly why only in a pinch
Don't call me!
For that
Probably a salvation hero!
To the cheongmage group
Uba
I was robbed>
Is
What will happen ...? ＞
<"Movie Crayon Shin-chan"
If you laugh with Ora ~>
O
Za
After being left behind →
Already
Ta
It's been a long time>
Nana
Oto
(Tummy ringing sound)
I'm hungry ...
Well ... no more ...
Ne
Do not sleep!
Morning sickness
You will be attacked by vultures!
eh?
Guet! Gua!
Ahhhh!
Hie ~! Oh!
Ta
No ... stop! Even if I eat
It's not delicious!
Ki
Ah ... I'm out.
I've done it!
Untie Atai!
It's time.
eh?
A little
A little useful!
Uh ... uh?
(Marumo) I want to ...!
Or
Oops! Yakisoba ~!
What is it?
How
This yakisoba is hard!
Gununununu ...!
I did it with Shinnosuke!
Ahhhh!
Two
Well
This
I got involved with them →
Really
Already
reason
Really sorry!
Kama
It doesn't matter to us
Please run away!
Ora Hana-chan
I'll help you!
eh….
Attai is also being killed
Let's
Ah
It doesn't suit your gender to run away.
Hmm ... Really !?
Alright ...!
Gwa!
Gwah!
Huh ...
Eh!
Guet! Guet!
Come on
guidance
I'll guide you to the hideout!
Gwa ...
Shuppatsu Shinko
Departure progress!
Zu
Eggplant pickled in bran!
(Boss) Huff Huff Huff ...
Finally
Ki
It's time to open the Demon Bottle.
Hey Demon Bottle?
Refrigerator
In the fridge
Hi
It is chilled.
Bath
Ah
Yeah. Then after the bath
Edamame
Cute with edamame ... →
It's not beer!
Don't chill!
Excuse me….
Alright, open it!
Or
The boss has something written on it.
Before
Kuda
"Please shake well before opening
From Yusha "
Kaju
Is it 100% fruit juice?
Shiji
But
Let's follow the instructions for the time being.
Good luck good luck ...
Good ...!
Keihoon
(Alarm sound)
Tehen
The boss is hard!
Shinnyu
Someone has invaded!
what!?
(Alarm sound)
Ah!
There it is!
Maka
Saki
Leave this to Atai first!
H ... yes!
bra!
(Alarm sound)
Take it!
Haha!
Teeee!
Ugh ...! Guhuh ...
Fufufufufufu ...
It's hard to do.
Sensei
Bouncer teacher!
(Bouncer)
Next
Will I be the next person?
Buji
Is Hana safe?
No way ...!
Disagreeable
I ... I hate ...!
(Boss) Hehehehehehe.
Hey!
Car! Help me!
Hana ~!
Straw
Go
(Hana's laughter)
eh?
Fufufufu ...!
(Hana's father) Hana ...?
Oh dad.
Oh!
Me ... insanely
You're relaxing.
Kama
Free time
I don't have time to be held hostage
Watch it on TV.
Ora was also good hostage ...
Yup….
Alright! later
When
Modo
Just get the bottle opener back!
Lid
Wow
Saga
Let's search in two parts!
Ora hostage is better ...
Ohhhhh!
・ ～
Haha ...
Subaya
What a quick move ...
Ikihito
Mida
Moreover, I'm not out of breath ...!
I
It's about time to go from here.
Kee!
Oops! there were!
Let's run away.
That's it.
Kae
Let's get it back.
Shin-chan pass!
Hey!
Bow
Boy pass!
Hey!
thank you!
Oh idiot!
I got the boss back!
well done.
(whistle)
(2 people) What?
Offside!
It's offside ... yes.
silly!
Ah….
Tei!
Huhhhhh ... that guy
It looks like it's useless anymore.
Shit!
Huh ... remember it well.
Tao
Defeat Kisama
Nana
My name is ...
Ugh ...!
Shogekion
(Impact sound)
Mr!
Or
…won.
Ha ha ha ha ...
I can't escape anymore.
Alright!
(Maracas)
See ginseng!
Buriburizaemon Pass!
Leave it to me!
Oops!
Tahhh!
Ah! silly!
Is it different?
Ah!
Well ... the Demon King ...!
The Demon King is coming out!
Ha ha ha ha ...!
Uniform
Dream
Finally my dream of conquering the world
Wonder
It's time to come true!
Ah…?
Ichidou
(All) What? Hmm ...?
(Devil's Cough)
(Ohana)
Yowa
Me ... I'm really weak!
What the hell
If you stay in the bottle for thousands of years
Toshito
Even an eagle gets old.
Ah ... that ...
Then what about world domination?
Chikara
Saw
Do you want to take that power?
Such ...!
The remaining power is at best
Ikken
Ta
Is it about building a house ...
Well then
Chi
It should be noted that
Please fix my house.
Bow
By the way, there is also an Atai stick!
Yes ...
Yubi
Nana
(Ringing finger)
By now
(Demon King) Nowadays
Originally
It will be restored.
Hooray! Thank you.
And the eagle
Sawa
Can I take care of you here?
Senyo
Caregiver
It became a nursing care facility exclusively for the Demon King>
Wow! It's really back!
I'm happy.
so
Ryo
Okumanen
Or
Help fee 10 billion yen Loan is also possible.
Temee wouldn't do anything.
Come on
Thank you for your meal at home ~.
Last
To the last
You're not going to give out cash, right?
undefined
Every time
The journey of the drifter Shinnosuke is →
Cold
Mu
As the wind turns, as the wind turns
Continued
It continued>
Well
O
Wait, is this the end?
Katsuya
I ’m active
Isn't it from now on!
"Crayon Shin-chan"
Ji
Pun
Latest movie release commemoration →
"Honeymoon Hurricane
Ushina
～ Lost Hiroshi ～ ”→
First broadcast on TV! ＞
undefined
Zessan Koukachu
Gekitotsu
"Crash! With Rakuga Kingdom
Yonin
Yusha
Almost four heroes ”→
Comic and novelize
Make a set →
Chusen
Mei
To all 30 people by lottery →
I'll give you a present>
Bangou
Denwa
I'm waiting ~>
(Hiroshi Nohara)
U
Taiken
Bow
Dad's batch co-i>
(Hiroshi)
powder
Well
Strain
Put your hips and knead! ＞
(Hiroshi)
Yakyu
・ ～