Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Even That Which Isn't Visible From There
Even that which isn't visible from there.
One day, during summer break...
President, what's up?
I bet you don't have any plans this weekend.
We're going to visit a campus.
That's out of the blue.
Aogaku is doing open campus tours right now.
The entrance exams are next year,
but I figured I'd check it out
in case I'm interested.
Well, I am free.
But Aogaku, huh?
I don't see myself ever making it there.
They're all smart and well-dressed.
True.
Didn't even miss a beat!
By the way, what are your future plans?
Going to college? Or work?
Well, I suppose with your specs,
you won't really have a meaningful choice.
Well, I hadn't really decide—
Bzzzzz, Shirota is out!
In this situation,
the only valid answer is:
"As your closet, I intend to follow
Takamine-sama wherever you goes."
Normal people don't talk like that!
Well, even if you end up on a different path,
I'll have you continue being my closet.
The only way that would be possible is if I go
to the same university or become a NEET!
As long as my requirements are met,
you are free to do what you want to do.
Can you really call it "free"
with those restrictions?!
Oh, right, speaking of open,
I bought something kind of fun.
What is it?
Huh?
President
Would you like to
switch to a video call?
It's an open bra.
B-B-But why are you wearing it?!
And why is only the open part in view?!
I was trying it on because I bought it online.
The shop staff seemed embarrassed
when I bought a micro bikini in person.
Isn't it usually the person
buying it who's embarrassed?!
I mean, this is really your fault.
I-I'm sorry?
Remember the first pair of underwear you
picked out when we went shopping together?
Because of that, I've been curious
about how open lingerie feels.
I, I mean I didn't really pick that out...
By the way,
the panties looks like this.
You didn't have to show me!
Please don't push the end call button
just because it's in the way.
If you did, the only thing you'd see
is your own confused face.
I'm not that stupid!
Though, if you do make it
into the same university as me,
you might get a chance to see them.
What do you mean?
I used to
adore and
believe in
President...
Woot lmao
Cuckold
Camp
Takamine
Takane
After being sweet-talked into joining
a club at the university's welcoming party,
it turns out to be a sex club.
And while my mouth keeps saying no,
I awaken to the pleasures of the flesh.
In the end, I might become a super slut
who wears this kind of underwear
daily to seduce men.
That just sounds like
a porno summary!
P-Please don't do that.
Don't join a club like that, even as a joke.
If you don't want me
to accept such invitations,
then how about this...
Come to the same university as me and
be both my closet and my bodyguard.
If you manage to do that,
as a reward, I might even show you
that which isn't visible from there.
T-There you go again, making fun of me...
You know that's essentially
impossible with my academic abilities...
Hey, Kuro!
President?
Call Ended
Consider this payment up front.
If you don't get accepted into
my university, you'll be punished.
Consider this payment up front.
If you don't get accepted into my university,
you'll be punished.
That's ridiculous!
A few days later,
I decided to join the president
on the open campus tour.
I made it here before her today.
She has no reason to be
angry at me this time.
Oh, Shirota-kun.
How uppity of you to arrive before me.
That's so unreasonable!
Let's walk around a bit before the
department information sessions begin.
S-Sure.
She's looking the part.
I bet nobody nobody would
bat an eye if she said
she was a student at Aoyama.
Shirota-kun?
I know I must look like a
dazzling university student right now,
but shouldn't your attention be directed
at the university itself?
I-I wasn't...
I mean, whether or not I can have a brilliant
life on campus might even depend on you.
Sorry? What do you mean by that?
Don't you remember what I suggested?
You come along to my university
and be my bodyguard and closet.
If you can't manage to do that...
I will be forced to change
in the lecture hall myself,
which will be filmed by someone.
They will then blackmail me with that...
Why are you even changing
in the lecture hall to begin with?!
And then one thing leads to another,
I voluntarily drop out of university,
No. 1 Takane-chan
Favorite Acts
Eternal Virgin Road
Least Favorite Add-Ons
Taking panties home
Work Schedule
and end up the No. 1 sex worker in Kabukicho.
What are all the things that lead to that?!
Besides, none of that
would be a problem if you just
undid the fact that someone filmed you.
Wow.
You're a genius.
Why don't you play along? You're so boring.
I can hear you.
Anyway, let's move on.
What are your plans, really?
Huh?
For the future.
By the way, what are your future plans?
Going to college? Or work?
Well, I hadn't really decide—
I know you said you hadn't decided yet,
but it's not like you haven't
thought about it, right?
You don't have to butter me up and say you
"want to attend the same university as me."
Just tell me what you've come up with so far.
I promise I won't laugh
at anything you say.
Your face is already laughing!
Well, I'm thinking maybe work.
For now...
Is there a reason for that?
Well, my little sister has her entrance
exams for high school next year.
I was thinking that if we both moved
to new schools at the same time,
it'd be tough on the family budget.
So, since I don't have anything
I particularly want to study at university,
maybe it's better to work
and bring in some money instead of
half-heartedly going to university.
And I kind of want to repay
my parents... or something.
I didn't expect you to have
put so much thought into it.
Well, it's not nailed down or anything.
I suppose, for helping your
parents out financially,
a part-time job will suffice.
What's more, you'll be able to arrange
your shifts to prioritize being my closet.
All right, that settles your future.
I'm locked into part-time jobs?!
Auditorium this way
The information session about the university
and its departments is about to begin.
President, it's about to begin.
President?
Oh, right. Let's go.
University Information Session
That concludes the information session.
If anybody has a question,
please raise your hand.
Yes, in the very back.
The lady with the long hair.
Could you discuss if there are any benefits
to graduating top of the class from
your institution, and what they are?
But she hasn't even gotten in yet!
Well, at graduation, you'd be presented
with a certificate of merit
and, while it's not guaranteed,
there have been cases where professors
wrote letters of recommendation
for future employers.
Thank you for the information.
I will take that into consideration.
Top of the class, huh?
I can always count on you to think big.
Are there any more questions?
It doesn't need to be
a question like we just had.
It could be a question about
the lectures, facilities, or dorms.
I've decided.
Decided what?
I'm redoing it.
Redoing what?!
If anybody has a question,
please raise your hand.
Yes, in the very back.
The lady with the long hair.
Could you discuss if there are any benefits
to graduating top of the class from
your university, and what they are?
Well, at graduation you'd be presented
with a certificate of merit
and, while it's not guaranteed,
there have been cases where professors
wrote letters of recommendation
for future employers.
Thank you for the information.
I will take that into consideration.
Um, what did you redo?
I changed "institution" to "university".
With the word "institution" it might be
momentarily unclear that I meant this school.
Your institution
Your university
That's so minuscule!
More importantly,
you've got a job to do.
Right here?!
What are you worried about?
Take a good look around.
The tables are arranged in an arc.
The chance of being seen from the sides is low.
President
Shirota
From the front, the backrests block the view.
There's basically no risk of being spotted.
I guess that's true, but...
Well then, get to it.
The next one will be the last question.
Does anyone have anything else?
While the chance is low, it's not 100% safe.
I need to get this done quickly.
Um, President...
I can't put them on if your legs are crossed.
Could you open them a bit, please?
I guess I have to.
There you go.
You don't need to spread them like that!
You sure are complaining a lot for a closet.
I know you know what I meant!
Hold on.
You didn't put them on properly.
How many times has this happened now?
Oh, I'm sorr—!
Didn't I tell you?
You don't have to worry about anything else.
So just put them on slowly
and surely... please.
It's a good school.
That was a good use of my time.
R-Right...
But was it really necessary
to undo saying "institution"?
I'm pretty sure the faculty member
wasn't confused by that.
"God is in the details."
If I don't pay attention to things like that,
I won't be able to become a god.
You're trying to become a god?!
Further, I thought I should make the most of it.
I mean, of you.
What do you mean?
If you get a job and our paths diverge...
continuing this relationship will be difficult.
So I thought...
I ought to let you serve me as much as I can.
But you said I have to continue
even if I have work.
What? I was obviously joking.
Did you really think I would
seriously be so tyrannical?
You didn't think so, did you?
Depending on your answer,
I might sew your mouth shut.
Tyrant!
Anyway, that's where it's at.
But don't get too excited about being set free.
There's a little over a year until then.
I'm going to get the most out of you.
No...
in fact, I'm going to use you up.
You'd better prepare yourself.
Come, let's go home.
This relationship that I'd been
forced into wasn't going to go on forever.
Having an end in sight should
have been something to celebrate.
Yet...
If you get a job and our paths diverge...
continuing this relationship will be difficult.
So I thought...
I ought to let you serve me as much as I can.
I didn't feel ready to celebrate.
Please Put Them On,
Takamine-san
The day after the campus tour,
there was mandatory attendance
for all students at school.
But I couldn't forget the image
of the president's gloomy face,
and I had trouble getting enough sleep.
It was so brief, though.
Maybe it was just my imagination.
Yeah, she looks kind of off...
Good morning, President.
Good morning, Shirota-kun.
What is it?
It's morning.
Could you please refrain from looking
like you're about to go to bed?
Did I imagine it?
Your face looks like a shriveled balloon
that's been left in a ditch for a month.
Wasn't just "shriveled balloon" enough?!
What is it? Why are they...
Now, snap out of it.
We're about to miss the train.
Oh, yeah.
Um, President...
your skirt's...
My skirt? What about—
Could you please not misinterpret things?
What?
It's cool biz.
Cool biz?!
Yes.
I considered going to school without
a skirt to help curb CO2 emissions,
but I made a compromise
for the sake of decency.
How is this decent?!
Oh, so what?
I'm the only one who gets to see your panties!
Is that how your possessiveness
is rearing its ugly head now?
Oh, fine then. I'll stop it.
Happy now?
Are your desires satisfied now?
That was weird even for how
eccentric the president is, right?
But I can't imagine she'd make
a blunder like this either.
Huh?
She's missing one sock?!
Did she forget?
But would she ever make such a mistake?
Is she not feeling well or something?
I didn't think it'd be so
full during summer break.
Of course.
For the workforce,
there's no such thing as a long break.
That'll be true of you in
a couple years, too, correct?
We'll soon arrive at Wakaba. Wakaba is next.
Shouldn't you keep that in mind?
You're probably right.
It must be that she's
having an off day today.
There might be even more oopsies that will
damage the image people have of her.
I need to find them before we get to school.
Now arriving at Wakaba.
Are you telling me...
she's not wearing one?!
Is there a chance it's on purpose?
No, what kind of high school student
goes to school without a bra?!
She hasn't realized
she forgot to put one on!
H-How do I tell her?!
Shirota-kun, maybe you think I didn't notice,
but you're staring at my breasts too hard.
Y... No, I mean...
It is true that my breasts are attrac—
Wh-When did you notice?!
Phew! She realized!
That this shirt is from first year?!
No, not that!
Well, it's because... Right!
It's because all my
other clothes are in the laundry!
Still...
What do you think of how tight it is?
I have to hand it to myself,
developing this much in just one year.
Don't do that!
That's not what I mea—
Those who've seen my naked breasts will
retain the memory of "things that happened."
I-I-I'm sorry!
It was a reflex, and...
Redo.
It's my room.
She's redoing the whole day.
When I met her for the second time that day,
she was back to her usual self.
Toushin
High School
And then, the next day...
So I didn't just imagine it...
that look on her face that day.
Maybe, for her, it's the same feeling
as becoming attached to a tool
you've grown used to.
Still,
if she was not being her usual self yesterday
because her mind was a mess like mine was...
On the other hand,
attending lessons at a cram school
isn't going to get me accepted
into the same school as her.
Even in the one-in-a-million chance...
the one-in-a-billion chance I
do get in, what about the tuition?!
This isn't a good plan!
No!
I have to take action,
or nothing will change!
I'll cross that bridge when I get there!
Ow.
I'm sorry!
I was distracted!
Oh, no, I was looking at my phone, too.
Wait, is that you, Kou-chan?
Huh?