Nobody got you the way I do
Whatever demons u fighting through
When you need somebody to turn to
Nobody got you the way I do
I’d take the fall
If ever you feel like there’s no one at all
Ah yea and
I’d stay through the night
When you got monsters tryna take you alive
There ain’t no people or lines
That i wouldn’t cross if u need me to
I’m out here steppin on mines
And I think it’s finally time that you knew
Nobody got you the way I do
Whatever demons u fightin through
When you need somebody to turn to
Nobody got you the way I do
Nobody got u without no shade
I’ll take the good and the bad all day
When you need somebody to turn to
Nobody got you the way I do
Nobody Nobody Nobody
Got you the way I do
Nobody got you the way I do